
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>*DUMB LAWS*</pattern>
 <template>Ok. Type the name of a state for a random dumb law.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>ALABAMA</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Dominoes may not be played on Sunday.
<li>It is illegal to wear a fake moustache that causes laughter in church.
<li>Putting salt on a railroad track may be punishable by death.
<li>Boogers may not be flicked into the wind.
<li>It is legal to drive the wrong way down a one-way street if you have a lantern attached to the front of your automobile.
<li>You may not have an ice cream cone in your back pocket at any time.
<li>Masks may not be worn in public.Men may not spit in front of the opposite sex.
<li>You may not wear blue jeans down Noble Street.
<li>It is illegal for a husband to beat his wife with a stick larger than the diameter of his thumb.
<li>It is illegal to sell peanuts in Lee County after sundown on Wednesday.
<li>It is illegal to howl at ladies within the city limits.
<li>It is unlawful to wear women's pumps with sharp, high heels.
<li>It is considered an offense to open an umbrella on a street, for fear of spooking horses.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>ALASKA</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Moose may not be viewed from an airplane.
<li>While it is legal to shoot bears, waking a sleeping bear for the purpose of taking a photograph is prohibited.
<li>It is considered an offense to push a live moose out of a moving airplane.
<li>It is considered an offense to feed alcoholic beverages to a moose.
<li>A person may only carry a concealed slingshot if that person has received the appropriate license.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>ARIZONA</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Any misdemeanor committed while wearing a red mask is considered a felony.
<li>There is a possible 25 years in prison for cutting down a cactus.
<li>Donkeys cannot sleep in bathtubs.
<li>It is illegal to manufacture imitation cocaine
<li>When being attacked by a criminal or burglar, you may only protect yourself with the same weapon that the other person posseses.
<li>It is unlawful to refuse a person a glass of water.
<li>You may not have more than two dildos in a house.
<li>Cars may not be driven in reverse.
<li>Cards may not be played in the street with a Native American.
<li>No more than six girls may live in any house.
<li>It is illegal to smoke cigarettes within 15 feet of a public place unless you have a Class 12 liqueur license.
<li>A decree declares that anyone caught stealing soap must wash himself with it until it is all used up.
<li>An ordinance prohibits the wearing of suspenders.
<li>One must be 18 years old to buy spray paint.
<li>It is illegal for men and women over the age of 18 to have less than one missing tooth visible when smiling.
<li>Women may not wear pants.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>ARKANSAS</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>The Arkansas River can rise no higher than to the Main Street bridge in Little Rock.
<li>A law provides that school teachers who bob their hair will not get a raise.
<li>A man can legally beat his wife, but not more than once a month.
<li>Oral sex is considered to be sodomy.
<li>Alligators may not be kept in bathtubs.
<li>It is illegal to kill &quot;any living creature&quot;.
<li>Dogs may not bark after 6 PM.
<li>Flirtation between men and women on the streets of Little Rock may result in a 30-day jail term.
<li>It is unlawful to walk one's cow down Main Street after 1:00 PM on Sunday.
<li>
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>CALIFORNIA</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Sunshine is guaranteed to the masses.
<li>Animals are banned from mating publicly within 1,500 feet of a tavern, school, or place of worship.
<li>It is a misdemeanor to shoot at any kind of game from a moving vehicle, unless the target is a whale.
<li>Women may not drive in a house coat.
<li>No vehicle without a driver may exceed 60 miles per hour.
<li>Peacocks have the right of way to cross any street, including driveways.
<li>Nobody is allowed to ride a bicycle in a swimming pool.
<li>You are not permitted to wear cowboy boots unless you already own at least two cows.
<li>It is illegal to spit, except on baseball diamonds.
<li>Ice cream may not be eaten while standing on the sidewalk.
<li>All dog &quot;waste&quot; must be removed from any yard within seven days.
<li>One must obtain a permit from the city to throw hay in a cesspool.
<li>One may not use one's own restroom if the window is open.
<li>It is illegal to wash your car in the street.
<li>Public restrooms must be supplied with toilet paper.
<li>No person may show his or her buttocks on a playground.
<li>It is illegal to drive more than two thousand sheep down Hollywood Boulevard at one time.
<li>It is illegal for a trumpet player to play his instrument with the intention of luring someone to a store.
<li>Fortelling the future for donations is illegal.
<li>You are forbidden to spit on the ground within 5 feet of another person.
<li>It is illegal to shoot &quot;silly string&quot; at parade participants.
<li>It is illegal to posses, own or raise roosters. This is considered disturbing the peace.
<li>Cars are the only item allowed in a garage.
<li>It is illegal to curse on a mini-golf course.
<li>It is illegal for a man to beat his wife with a strap wider than 2 inches without her consent.
<li>You cannot bathe two babies in the same tub at the same time.
<li>You may not hunt moths under a street light.
<li>It is illegal to cry on the witness stand.
<li>Toads may not be licked.
<li>It is a crime for dogs to mate within 500 yards of a church. Breaking this law is punishable by a fine of 500 and/or six months in prison.
<li>Zoot suits are prohibited.
<li>Vehicles may not contain sound systems which allow someone to hear noise outside the vehicle. However, this does not apply to a vehicle which is attempting to sell something.
<li>It is unlawful to give another fireworks.
<li>All persons wishing to keep a rhinoceros as a pet must obtain a 100 license first.
<li>Growing oleander flowers is illegal.
<li>It is illegal to molest butterflies.
<li>It is illegal to walk a camel down Palm Canyon Drive between the hours of four and six PM.
<li>It is illegal for a secretary to be alone in a room with her boss.
<li>Two bathtubs may not be installed in the same house.
<li>Motor vehicles may not drive on city streets unless a man with a lantern is wallking ahead of it.
<li>One may not carry a lunch down the street between 11 and 1 o'clock.
<li>It is illegal to shoot jackrabbits from the back of a streetcar.
<li>The owners of houses with Christmas lights on them past February second may be fined up to 250.
<li>Prohibits elephants from strolling down Market Street unless they are on a leash.
<li>It is illegal to wipe one's car with used underwear.
<li>Persons classified as &quot;ugly&quot; may not walk down any street.
<li>It is illegal to pile horse manure more than six feet high on a street corner.
<li>It is illegal to have more than two cats or dogs.
<li>You may not play percussion instruments on the beach.
<li>One may not raffle off a dog as a gift in any public place.
<li>Ducks have the right of way to cross Rancho California St. at all times.
<li>Kites may not be flown above 10 feet over the ground.
<li>Children may not wear a halloween mask unless they get a special permit from the sheriff.
<li>Males may not dress as a female unless a special permit is obtained from the sheriff.
<li>One may not leave sand in their own driveway.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>COLORADO</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Car dealers may not show cars on a Sunday.
<li>It is illegal for liquor stores to sell food or grocery stores to sell any alcohol except beer that is at most 3.2 alcohol.
<li>No liquor may be sold on Sundays or election days.
<li>It is illegal to ride a horse while under the influence.
<li>Tags may be ripped off of pillows and mattresses.
<li>Throwing missles at cars is illegal.
<li>Persons may not urinate in public.
<li>It is illegal to bring your horse or pack mule above the ground floor of any building.
<li>It is unlawful to lend your vacuum cleaner to your next-door neighbor.
<li>You may not drive a black car on Sundays.
<li>It is illegal to mistreat rats in Denver, Colorado.
<li>It is illegal for a man to kiss a woman while she is asleep.
<li>It is illegal to let a dandelion grow within the city limits.
<li>Cats may not run loose without having been fit with a taillight.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>CONNECTICUT</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>You can be stopped by the police for biking over 65 miles per hour.
<li>In order for a pickle to officially be considered a pickle, it must bounce.
<li>It is illegal to dispose of used razor blades.
<li>You cannot buy any alcohol after 8pm or on Sundays.
<li>It is illegal to discharge a firearm from a public highway.
<li>It is unlawful to walk backwards after sunset.
<li>Only white Christmas lights are allowed for display.
<li>You aren't allowed to cross a street while walking on your hands.
<li>You may not educate dogs.
<li>It is illegal for a man to kiss his wife on Sunday.
<li>It is illegal for fire trucks to exceed 25mph, even when going to a fire.
<li>Silly string is banned.
<li>It is illegal for any beautician to hum, whistle, or sing while working on a customer.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>DELAWARE</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>It is illegal to fly over any body of water, unless one is carrying sufficient supplies of food and drink.
<li>&quot;R&quot; rated movies shall not be shown at drive-in theaters.
<li>It is illegal to wear pants that are &quot;firm fitting&quot; around the waist.
<li>Getting married on a dare is grounds for an annulment.
<li>No person shall change clothes in his or her vehicle.
<li>On Halloween, children may only &quot;trick-or-treat&quot; from 6:00 PM to 8:00 PM, and if Halloween falls on a Sunday, they must &quot;trick-or-treat&quot; on October 30 during this same time interval.
<li>One may not whisper in church.
<li>No person shall pretend to sleep on a bench on the boardwalk.
<li>Changing into or out of a bathing suit in a public restroom is prohibited.
<li>Six-year-old girls may not run around without being fully clothed.
<li>All persons must carry a bag with them at all times when they walk their dog in case said dog &quot;poops&quot;, or risk a 100 fine.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>FLORIDA</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>A special law prohibits unmarried women from parachuting on Sunday or she shall risk arrest, fine, and/or jailing.
<li>If an elephant is left tied to a parking meter, the parking fee has to be paid just as it would for a vehicle.
<li>It is illegal to sing in a public place while attired in a swimsuit.
<li>Men may not be seen publicly in any kind of strapless gown.
<li>Having sexual relations with a porcupine is illegal.
<li>It is illegal to skateboard without a license.
<li>You may not fart in a public place after 6 P.M. on Thursdays.
<li>It is considered an offense to shower naked.
<li>You are not allowed to break more than three dishes per day, or chip the edges of more than four cups and/or saucers.
<li>Penalty for horse theft is death by hanging.
<li>It is against the city ordinance to hang your clothes outside on a clothesline.
<li>It it illegal to park a pick-up truck in your driveway or in front of your house on the street. This law is limited to only those who do not own the house.
<li>Owning a flower pot with water in it that isn't capable of draining is considered a public nuisance.
<li>Chickens are considered a 'protected species'.
<li>Neon signs are prohibited.
<li>Citizens may not be caught downtown without at least 10 dollars on their person.
<li>It is illegal to roll a barrel on any street, fines go up according to the contents of the barrel.
<li>If you hit a pedestrian you are fined 78.00.
<li>You may not catch crabs.
<li>Beer may not be sold between 2 a.m. and 7 a.m.
<li>All houses much have white picket fences and full-width, two-story porches.
<li>Women may not expose their breasts while performing &quot;topless dancing&quot;.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>GEORGIA</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Members of the state assembly cannot be ticketed for speeding while the state assembly is in session.
<li>Donkeys may not be kept in bathtubs.
<li>Signs are required to be written in English.
<li>All citizens must own a rake.
<li>Against the law to tie a giraffe to a telephone pole or street lamp.
<li>One man may not be on another man's back.
<li>Can't cut off a chicken's head on Sunday.
<li>It is illegal to carry a chicken by it's feet down Broadway on Sunday.
<li>All Indians must return to their shore of the Chattohoochee River by nightfall. (Repealed)
<li>One may not place a dead bird on a neighbor's lawn.
<li>Rocks may not be thrown at birds.
<li>A person must obtain a permit to spread rat poison.
<li>Persons may not wear hoods in public.
<li>It is illegal to play catch in any city street.
<li>Cars may not be driven through playgrounds.
<li>Chicken must be eaten with the hands.
<li>It is illegal to say &quot;Oh, Boy.&quot;
<li>Though it is illegal to spit from a car or bus, citizens may spit from a truck.
<li>It is illegal for a chicken to cross the road.
<li>Cars are not to drive on sidewalks.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HAWAII</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Billboards are outlawed.
<li>All residents may be fined as a result of not owning a boat.
<li>Coins are not allowed to be placed in one's ears.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>IDAHO</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Illegal for a man to give his sweetheart a box of candy weighing less than fifty pounds.
<li>You may not fish on a camel's back.
<li>Riding a merry-go-round on Sundays is considered a crime.
<li>Residents may not fish from a giraffe's back.
<li>If a police officer approaches a vehicle and suspects that the occupants are engaging in sex, he must either honk, or flash his lights and wait for three minutes before approaching the car.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>ILLINIOS</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>You must contact the police before entering the city in an automobile.
<li>The English language is not to be spoken.
<li>One may not pee in his neighbor's mouth.
<li>Law forbids eating in a place that is on fire.
<li>It is illegal to give a dog whiskey.
<li>Spitting is forbidden.
<li>Humming on public streets is prohibited on Sundays.
<li>A man with a moustache may not kiss a woman.
<li>It is unlawful for &quot;negroes&quot; to be within county boundries from sundown to sunrise.
<li>There is a 1,000 dollar fine for beating rats with baseball bats.
<li>No person may keep a smelly dog.
<li>It is illegal to burn bird feathers.
<li>Jostling others is illegal.
<li>No bicyclist may practice &quot;fancy riding&quot; on any city street.
<li>A rooster must step back three hundred feet from any residence if he wishes to crow. Hens that wish to cackle must step two hundred feet back from any residence.
<li>It is against the law to make faces at dogs.
<li>Spitting on the sidewalk is a criminal offense.
<li>It is illegal for anyone to give lighted cigars to dogs, cats, or any other domesticated animals.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>INDIANA</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>One may not sniff glue.
<li>A person must get a referral from a licensed physician if he or she wishes to see a hypnotist unless the desired procedure is to quit smoking or lose weight.
<li>Baths may not be taken between the months of October and March.
<li>It is illegal to sell cars on Sunday.
<li>It is against the law to pass a horse on the street.
<li>Liquor stores may not sell milk.
<li>One man may not back into a parking spot becasue it prevents police officers from seeing the license plate.
<li>No one may catch a fish with his bare hands.
<li>Drinks on the house are illegal.
<li>You are required to pour your drink into a glass.
<li>Hotel sheets must be exactly 99 inches long and 81 inches wide.
<li>Anyone 14 or older who profanely curses, damns or swears by the name of God, Jesus Christ or the Holy Ghost, shall be fined one to three dollars for each offense, with a maximum fine of ten dollars per day.
<li>The value of Pi is 4, and not 3.1415.
<li>It is forbidden to eat watermelon in the park.
<li>It is illegal for barbers to threaten to cut off kid's ears.
<li>It is illegal to make a monkey smoke a cigarette.
<li>No one may spit on the sidewalk.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>IOWA</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Tanning bed facilities must warn of the risk of getting a sunburn.
<li>One-armed piano players must perform for free.
<li>Kisses may last for no more than five minutes.
<li>Any hotel in the city limits must have a water bucket and a hitching post in front of the building.
<li>The fire department is required to practice fire fighting for fifteen minutes before attending a fire.
<li>Horses are forbidden to eat fire hydrants.
<li>One must obtain written permission from the City Council before throwing bricks into a highway.
<li>All softball diamond lights must be turned off by 10:30 PM.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>KANSAS</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Rabbits may not be shot from motorboats.
<li>Pedestrians crossing the highways at night must wear tail lights.
<li>No one may catch fish with his bare hands.
<li>The state game rule prohibits the use of mules to hunt ducks.
<li>It is illegal to urinate on the side of a building.
<li>Hitting a vending machine that stole your money is illegal.
<li>Persons may not &quot;screech&quot; their tires while driving.
<li>All places of business must provide a horse water troft.
<li>All cars entering the city limits must first sound their horn to warn the horses of their arrival.
<li>Musical car horns are banned.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>KENTUCKY</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Throwing eggs at a public speaker could result in up to one year in prison.
<li>One may not dye a duckling blue and offer it for sale unless more than six are for sale at once.
<li>It is illegal to fish with a bow and arrow in Kentucky.
<li>Dogs may not molest cars.
<li>A woman may not buy a hat without her husband's permission.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>LOUISIANA</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>It is illegal to shoot lasers at police officers.
<li>One may not &quot;dare&quot; another to go onto railroad tracks owned by another. Violation of this could result in up to six months in jail.
<li>Stealing an alligator could land a person in jail for up to ten years.
<li>Rituals that involve the ingestion of blood, urine, or fecal matter are not allowed.
<li>One could land in jail for up to a year for making a false promise.
<li>Every time a person is seriously burned, he must report the injury to the fire marshal.
<li>Prisoners who hurt themselves could serve an additional two years in jail.
<li>It is illegal to rob a bank and then shoot at the bank teller with a water pistol.
<li>Biting someone with your natural teeth is &quot;simple assault,&quot; while biting someone with your false teeth is &quot;aggravated assault.&quot;
<li>It is illegal to gargle in public places.
<li>All garbage must be cooked before it can be fed to any hogs.
<li>No one may pour a drink out on the ground at any drive-in movie.
<li>You may not tie an alligator to a fire hydrant.
<li>It illegal for a woman to drive a car unless her husband is waving a flag in front of it.
<li>No person may predict another's future.
<li>It is illegal to be an alcoholic.
<li>Saying obscene things on the telephone is illegal.
<li>It is illegal to have sex with a cow.
<li>Drive-thru liquor stores are outlawed.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>MAINE</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Shotguns are required to be taken to church in the event of a Native American attack.
<li>You may not step out of a plane in flight.
<li>After January 14th you will be charged a fine for having your Christmas decorations still up.
<li>To stroll down the street playing a violin is against the law.
<li>Shoelaces must be tied while walking down the street.
<li>It is illegal to park in front of Dunkin Donuts.
<li>Deer may not be fed.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>MARYLAND</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>It's illegal to throw bales of hay from a second-story window within the city limits.
<li>It's illegal to take a lion to the movies.
<li>Though you may spit on a city roadway, spitting on city sidewalks is prohibited.
<li>You may not curse inside the city limits.
<li>You can not have a antenna exposed outside of your house yet you can have a 25' satellite dish.
<li>Though clotheslines are banned, clothes may be draped over a fence.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>MASSACHUSETTES</pattern>
 <template>to many 2 list</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>MICHIGAN</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>A woman isn't allowed to cut her own hair without her husband's permission.
<li>It is legal for a robber to file a law suit, if he or she got hurt in your house.
<li>You may not swear in front of women and children. (Repealed)
<li>Any person over the age of 12 may have a license for a handgun as long as he/she has not been convicted of a felony.
<li>There is a law that makes it legal for a farmer to sleep with his pigs, cows, horses, goats, and chickens.
<li>Willfully destroying your old radio is prohibited.
<li>It is illegal to let your pig run free in Detroit unless it has a ring in its nose. According to history and animal husbandry, it prevents them from &quot;rooting&quot; in the ground for their food.
<li>It is illegal to paint sparrows to sell them as parakeets.
<li>All bathing suits must have been inspected by the head of police.
<li>Smoking while in bed is illegal.
<li>Anyone can keep their cow on Main Street downtown at a cost of 3 cents per day.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>MINNESOTA</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>The land of 10,000 lakes declares mosquitos a public nuisance.
<li>It is illegal to stand around any building without a good reason to be there.
<li>A person may not cross state lines with a duck atop his head.
<li>It is illegal to sleep naked.
<li>Citizens may not enter Wisconsin with a chicken on their head.
<li>All bathtubs must have feet.
<li>Residents of even numbered addresses may not water their plants on odd-numbered days excluding the thirty first day where it applies.
<li>Red cars may not drive down Lake Street.
<li>Driving a truck with dirty tires is considered a public nuisance.
<li>Hamburgers may not be eaten on Sundays.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>MISOURI</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>It is not illegal to speed.
<li>Yard waste may be burned any day except Sunday.
<li>Hard objects may not be thrown by hand.
<li>Minors are not allowed to purchase cap pistols, however they may buy shotguns freely.
<li>Installation of bathtubs with four legs resembling animal paws is prohibited.
<li>Minors can buy rolling paper and tobacco but not lighters.
<li>It is illegal for more than four unrelated persons to occupy the same dwelling (The Brothel Law).
<li>Frightening a baby is in violation of the law.
<li>It shall be unlawful to provide beer or other intoxicants to elephants.
<li>A milk man may not run while on duty.
<li>No person may own a PVC pipe.
<li>No person may have a &quot;yard sale&quot; in their front yard. In addition to this, no person shall have more than two yard sales a year.
<li>Houses may not have lights on them that shine into the window of a neighbor's house.
<li>One may not honk another's horn.
<li>Four women may not rent an apartment together.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>MISSISSIPPI</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Private citizens may personally arrest any person that disturbs a church service.
<li>One may be fined up to 100 for using &quot;profane language&quot; in public places.
<li>It is unlawful to shave in the center of main street.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>MISSOURI</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>It is not illegal to speed.
<li>Yard waste may be burned any day except Sunday.
<li>Hard objects may not be thrown by hand.
<li>Minors are not allowed to purchase cap pistols, however they may buy shotguns freely.
<li>Installation of bathtubs with four legs resembling animal paws is prohibited.
<li>Minors can buy rolling paper and tobacco but not lighters.
<li>It is illegal for more than four unrelated persons to occupy the same dwelling (The Brothel Law).
<li>Frightening a baby is in violation of the law.
<li>It shall be unlawful to provide beer or other intoxicants to elephants.
<li>A milk man may not run while on duty.
<li>No person may own a PVC pipe.
<li>No person may have a &quot;yard sale&quot; in their front yard. In addition to this, no person shall have more than two yard sales a year.
<li>Houses may not have lights on them that shine into the window of a neighbor's house.
<li>One may not honk another's horn.
<li>Four women may not rent an apartment together.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>MONTANA</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>It is illegal to have a sheep in the cab of your truck without a chaperone.
<li>It is a felony for a wife to open her husband's mail.
<li>In Montana, it is illegal for married women to go fishing alone on Sundays, and illegal for unmarried women to fish alone at all.
<li>Seven or more indians are considered a raiding or war party and it is legal to shoot them.
<li>It is illegal to bring a bomb or rocket at city council proceedings.
<li>It is illegal to use speed-dial in the city phone system.
<li>No person shall raise pet rats.
<li>Balls may not be thrown within the city limits.
<li>No item may be thrown across a street.
<li>Pop bottles are not to be thrown on the ground.
<li>It is illegal to operate a vehicle with ice picks attached to the wheels.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>NEBRASKA</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>If a child burps during church, his parent may be arrested.
<li>It is Illegal to go whale fishing.
<li>It is illegal for bar owners to sell beer unless they are simultaneously brewing a kettle of soup.
<li>It is illegal for a mother to give her daughter a perm without a state license.
<li>Doughnut holes may not be sold.
<li>Sneezing or burping is illegal during a church service.
<li>A man is not allowed to run around with a shaved chest.
<li>Barbers are forbidden from eating onions between 7 A.M. and 7 P.M.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>NEVADA</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>It is illegal to drive a camel on the highway.
<li>It's still &quot;legal&quot; to hang someone for shooting your dog on your property.
<li>in elko Everyone walking the streets is required to wear a mask.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>NEW HAPSHIRE</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>You may not tap your feet, nod your head, or in any way keep time to the music in a tavern, restaurant, or cafe.
<li>You cannot sell the clothes you are wearing to pay off a gambling debt.
<li>It is considered an offense to check into a hotel under an assumed name.
<li>Any cattle that crosses state roads must be fitted with a device to gather its feces.
<li>It is illegal to pick seaweed up off of the beach.
<li>You may not run machinery on Sundays.
<li>On Sundays citizens may not relieve themselves while looking up.
<li>If a person is caught raking the beaches, picking up litter, hauling away trash, building a bench for the park, or many other kind things without a permit, he/she may be fined 150 for ''maintaining the national forest without a permit''.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>NEW JERSEY</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>It is illegal to wear a bullet-proof vest while committing a murder.
<li>You cannot pump your own gas. All gas stations are full service and full service only.
<li>It is against the law for a man to knit during the fishing season.
<li>It is against the law to &quot;frown&quot; at a police officer.
<li>If you have been convicted of driving while intoxicated, you may never again apply for personalized license plates.
<li>Car dealerships are forbidden from opening on Sunday.
<li>You may not slurp your soup.
<li>Automobiles are not to pass horse drawn carriages on the street.
<li>It is illegal to delay or detain a homing pigeon.
<li>Spray paint may not be sold without a posted sign warning juveliles of the penalty for creating graffiti.
<li>Handcuffs may not be sold to minors.
<li>Shooting ranges are outlawed.
<li>It is illegal to throw ashes on the sidewalk.
<li>You may not dance or wear shorts on the main avenue.
<li>Citizens are not permitted to park their own boat on their lawn.
<li>All cats must wear three bells to warn birds of their whereabouts.
<li>It is forbidden for a woman, on a Sunday, to walk down Broad Street without wearing a petticoat.
<li>It is illegal to use the Crystal Lake Pool without first obtaining a bathing tag from the Township Clerk.
<li>Cross-dressing is illegal.
<li>No one may annoy someone of the opposite sex.
<li>It is illegal to offer whiskey or cigarettes to animals a the local zoo.
<li>Climbing trees is prohibited in all city parks.
<li>It is illegal to get drunk and annoy others in your house.
<li>It is illegal to sell ice cream after 6pm, unless the customer has a note from his doctor.
<li>People may not slurp their soup.
<li>Pinball machines are not to be played on Sunday.
<li>Raw hamburger may not be sold.
<li>Profanity is prohibited.
<li>You may not throw a bad pickle in the street.
<li>Pickles are not to be consumed on Sundays.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>NEW MEXICO</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>State officials ordered 400 words of &quot;sexually explicit material&quot; to be cut from Romeo and Juliet.
<li>It's forbidden for a female to appear unshaven in public.
<li>You may not carry a lunchbox down Main Street.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>NEW YORK</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>It is against the law to throw a ball at someone's head for fun.
<li>A license must be purchased before hanging clothes on a clothesline.
<li>A license must be purchased before hanging clothes on a clothesline.
<li>While riding in an elevator, one must talk to no one, and fold his hands while looking toward the door.
<li>Slippers are not to be worn after 10:00 P.M.
<li>A man can't go outside while wearing a jacket and pants that do not match.
<li>During a concert, it is illegal to eat peanuts and walk backwards on the sidewalks.
<li>You may not smoke within 100 feet of the entrance to a public building.
<li>Citizens may not greet each other by &quot;putting one's thumb to the nose and wiggling the fingers&quot;.
<li>It is illegal for men to go topless in the center of town.
<li>It is illegal to eat in the street in residential neighborhoods, and the only beverage you can drink on the beach is water in a clear plastic bottle.
<li>It is illegal for a father to call his son a &quot;faggot&quot; or &quot;queer&quot; in an effort to curb &quot;girlie behavior.&quot;
<li>You may only water your lawn if the hose is held in your hand.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>NORTH CAROLINA</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Persons in possession of illegal substances must pay taxes on them. However, paying taxes on these items does not make them legal.
<li>A three dollar tax must be paid on all white goods sold.
<li>Bingo games may not last over 5 hours unless it is held at a fair.
<li>Serving alcohol at a bingo game is not allowed.
<li>No one may be a professional fortune-teller, and if one wishes to pursue the practice as an amateur, it must be practiced in a school or church.
<li>It's against the law to sing off key.
<li>Elephants may not be used to plow cotton fields.
<li>If a man and a woman who aren't married go to a hotel/motel and register themselves as married then, according to state law, they are legally married.
<li>All couples staying overnight in a hotel must have a room with double beds that are at least two feet apart. Making love in the space between the beds is strictly forbidden.
<li>It is illegal to have sex in a churchyard.
<li>Fights between cats and dogs are prohibited.
<li>It is illegal to drive cars through city cemeteries for pleasure.
<li>There is to be no rollerblading during daylight hours, on the roads, or on the bricks. All the sidewalks at this college are made of brick.
<li>You must stop and call City Hall before entering town in an automobile. This is so the townspeople will have time to go out and hold their horses until you get through town.
<li>Restaurants &quot;with on sidewalk dining&quot; must post their menu so that it is clearly readable from the sidewalk, but is not readable from the street.
<li>You may not ride a bicycle without having both your hands on the handle bars.
<li>It is required that you must pay a property tax on your dog.
<li>It is against the law to rollerblade on a state highway.
<li>It is illegal to stand outside the police station for any purpose after dark.
<li>No person may walk on top of the water tank of the city.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>NORTH DAKOTA</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>It is illegal to lie down and fall asleep with your shoes on.
<li>Beer and pretzels can't be served at the same time in any bar or restaurant.
<li>It is legal to shoot an Indian on horseback, provided you are in a covered wagon.
<li>Fireworks may not be set off after 11:00 PM!
<li>One may be jailed for wearing a hat while dancing, or even for wearing a hat to a function where dancing is taking place.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>OHIO</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>It is illegal to fish for whales on Sunday.
<li>It is illegal to get a fish drunk.
<li>The Ohio driver's education manual states that you must honk the horn whenever you pass another car.
<li>Participating or conducting a duel is prohibited.
<li>Breast feeding is not allowed in public.
<li>It is illegal for more than five women to live in a house.
<li>No one may be arrested on Sunday or on the Fourth of July.
<li>It is illegal to walk a cow down Lake Road.
<li>prohibits the installation and usage of slot machines in outhouses.
<li>Electric fences are banned.
<li>If one loses their pet tiger, they must notify the authorities within one hour.
<li>Power Wheels� cars may not be driven down the street.
<li>It is a misdemeanor to play any game in a public park without the Superintendent's permission.
<li>It's illegal to catch mice without a hunting license!
<li>Any person who leans against a public building will be subject to fines.
<li>It is illegal for stores to sell corn flakes on Sunday.
<li>It's against the law to honk your horn &quot;excessively&quot;.
<li>Any map that does not have Lima clearly stated on the map cannot be sold.
<li>It is unlawful to run a horse over five miles per hour.
<li>You cannot eat a doughnut and walk backwards on a city street.
<li>Your goose may not paraded down Main Street.
<li>It is against the law to roller skate without notifying the police.
<li>A policeman may bite a dog to quiet him.
<li>Throwing a snake at anyone is illegal.
<li>You may not run out of gas.
<li>Riding on the roof of a taxi cab is not allowed.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>OKLAHOMA</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Females are forbidden from doing their own hair without being licensed by the state.
<li>Dogs must have a permit signed by the mayor in order to congregate in groups of three or more on private property.
<li>Oklahoma will not tolerate anyone taking a bite out of another's hamburger.
<li>It is against the law to read a comic book while operating a motor vehicle.
<li>Whaling is illegal.
<li>It is illegal to have the hind legs of farm animals in your boots.
<li>People who make &quot;ugly faces&quot; at dogs may be fined and/or jailed.
<li>Tattoos are banned.
<li>It is illegal to wear your boots to bed.
<li>Fish may not be contained in fishbowls while on a public bus.
<li>Tissues are not to be found in the back of one's car.
<li>It is illegal for the owner of a bar to allow anyone inside to pretend to have sex with a buffalo.
<li>If you wear New York Jets clothing, you may be put in jail.
<li>If ones dog is run over by a car, the owner must pay for the dog's disposal.
<li>No person may own more than two adult cats.
<li>It is illegal to cause &quot;annoying vibrations&quot; in the city limits.
<li>Persons may not play catch on any city street.
<li>Molesting an automobile is illegal.
<li>It is unlawful to put any hypnotized person in a display window.
<li>No one may walk backwards downtown while eating a hamburger.
<li>Women may not gamble in the nude, in lingerie, or while wearing a towel.
<li>You may not open a soda bottle without the supervision of a licensed engineer.
<li>Elephants are not to be taken into the downtown area.
<li>One's mode of transportation must be tied up while not attended.
<li>Mules may not drink out of bird baths.
<li>Clothes may not be washed in bird baths.
<li>It is illegal to tie a horse in front of city hall.
<li>While passing another vehicle, you must honk your horn.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>OREGON</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Dishes must drip dry.
<li>It is illegal to whisper &quot;dirty&quot; things in your lover's ear during sex.
<li>Ice cream may not be eaten on Sundays.
<li>It is illegal to buy or sell marijuana, but it is legal to smoke it on your own property.
<li>One may not bathe without wearing &quot;suitable clothing,&quot; i.e., that which covers one's body from neck to knee.
<li>Canned corn is not to be used as bait for fishing.
<li>You must buy a 10 permit to be allowed to install a burglar alarm.
<li>It is illegal to show movies or attend a car race on Sundays.
<li>It is legal to conduct a horse race or a symphony concert.
<li>Juggling is strictly prohibited without a license.
<li>It's illegal to walk down a sidewalk and knock a snakes head off with your cane.
<li>Ministers are forbidden from eating garlic or onions before delivering a sermon.
<li>One may not box with a kangaroo.
<li>Trucks may not be parked on the street.
<li>Riders of sleds may not attach themselves to passing cars.
<li>Persons may not pass through a &quot;traffic congestion thoroughfare&quot; more than twice per night.
<li>It's against the law for a wedding ceremony to be performed at a skating rink.
<li>People may not whistle underwater.
<li>You cannot wear roller skates in restrooms.
<li>Strippers may not come closer than four feet to any customer.
<li>It is against the law for animals to have sex in the city limits.
<li>Cloth towel dispensers are banned from restrooms.
<li>No more than two people may share a single drink.
<li>It is illegal to predict the future.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>PENNSYLVANIA</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>It is illegal to have over 16 women live in a house together because that constitutes a brothel. However up to 120 men can live together, without breaking the law.
<li>It it illegal to sleep on top of a refrigerator outdoors.
<li>Any motorist driving along a country road at night must stop every mile and send up a rocket signal, wait 10 minutes for the road to be cleared of livestock, and continue.
<li>A special cleaning ordinance bans housewives from hiding dirt and dust under a rug in a dwelling.
<li>You may not sing in the bathtub.
<li>Fireworks stores may not sell fireworks to Pennsylvania residents.
<li>A person is not eligible to become Governor if he/she has participated in a duel.
<li>Any motorist who sights a team of horses coming toward him must pull well off the road, cover his car with a blanket or canvas that blends with the countryside, and let the horses pass. If the horses appear skittish, the motorist must take his car apart, piece by piece, and hide it under the nearest bushes.
<li>Ministers are forbidden from performing marriages when either the bride or groom is drunk.
<li>No more than two packages of beer at a time may be purchased, unless you are buying from an official &quot;beer distributor&quot;.
<li>You may not catch a fish with your hands.
<li>You may not catch a fish by any body part except the mouth.
<li>Dynamite is not to be used to catch fish.
<li>Though you do not need a fishing license to fish on your own land, but a hunting license is required to hunt on your own land.
<li>Persons convicted of felonies may not operate Bingo games.
<li>One's pants may be worn no lower than five inches below the waist.
<li>All fire hydrants must be checked one hour before all fires.
<li>It is required that a woman have a permit to wear cosmetics.
<li>Every outlet or switch (which can be purchased for 59 cents) that is installed requires an electrical inspection fee of 1 dollar and 33 cents.
<li>It is still illegal to bring a donkey or a mule onto a trolley car.
<li>You cannot walk backwards eating peanuts in front of the Barnstormers Auditorium during a performance.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>PENNSYVANIA</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>It is illegal to have over 16 women live in a house together because that constitutes a brothel. However up to 120 men can live together, without breaking the law.
<li>It it illegal to sleep on top of a refrigerator outdoors.
<li>Any motorist driving along a country road at night must stop every mile and send up a rocket signal, wait 10 minutes for the road to be cleared of livestock, and continue.
<li>A special cleaning ordinance bans housewives from hiding dirt and dust under a rug in a dwelling.
<li>You may not sing in the bathtub.
<li>Fireworks stores may not sell fireworks to Pennsylvania residents.
<li>A person is not eligible to become Governor if he/she has participated in a duel.
<li>Any motorist who sights a team of horses coming toward him must pull well off the road, cover his car with a blanket or canvas that blends with the countryside, and let the horses pass. If the horses appear skittish, the motorist must take his car apart, piece by piece, and hide it under the nearest bushes.
<li>Ministers are forbidden from performing marriages when either the bride or groom is drunk.
<li>No more than two packages of beer at a time may be purchased, unless you are buying from an official &quot;beer distributor&quot;.
<li>You may not catch a fish with your hands.
<li>You may not catch a fish by any body part except the mouth.
<li>Dynamite is not to be used to catch fish.
<li>Though you do not need a fishing license to fish on your own land, but a hunting license is required to hunt on your own land.
<li>Persons convicted of felonies may not operate Bingo games.
<li>One's pants may be worn no lower than five inches below the waist.
<li>All fire hydrants must be checked one hour before all fires.
<li>It is required that a woman have a permit to wear cosmetics.
<li>Every outlet or switch (which can be purchased for 59 cents) that is installed requires an electrical inspection fee of 1 dollar and 33 cents.
<li>It is still illegal to bring a donkey or a mule onto a trolley car.
<li>You cannot walk backwards eating peanuts in front of the Barnstormers Auditorium during a performance.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>RHODE ISLAND</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>One must make a loud noise before passing a car on the left.
<li>Riding a horse over any public highway for the purpose of racing, or testing the speed of the horse is illegal. Penalty: Maximum 20 fine and imprisonment for 10 days.
<li>Professional sports, except ice polo and hockey, must obtain a license to play games on Sunday.
<li>It is considered an offense to throw pickle juice on a trolley.
<li>You cannot smoke a pipe after sunset.
<li>It is illegal to wear transparent clothing.
<li>You may not sell toothpaste and a toothbrush to the same customer on a Sunday.
<li>It is illegal to drive down any street with beer in your car, even if it is unopened.
<li>It is illegal to use water on even-numbered days for the sole purpose of watering plants, gardens, or lawns. If you break this law there is a fine of 25-100.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>SOUTH CAROLINA</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>It is illegal to display a confederate flag on a courthouse.
<li>Railroad companies may be held liable in some instances for scaring horses.
<li>Fortune tellers are required to obtain a special permit from the state.
<li>Dance halls may not operate on Sundays.
<li>No work may be done on Sunday.
<li>Musical instruments may not be sold on Sunday.
<li>It is considered an offense to get a tattoo.
<li>Horses may not be kept in bathtubs.
<li>A permit must be obtained to fire a missle.
<li>When approaching a four way or blind intersection in a non-horse driven vehicle you must stop 100 ft from the intersection and discharge a firearm into the air to warn horse traffic.
<li>It is perfectly legal to beat your wife on the court house steps on Sundays.
<li>Every adult male must bring a rifle to church on Sunday in order to ward off Indian attacks.
<li>A person must be eighteen years old to play a pinball machine.
<li>The Fire Department may blow up your house. This law was made so that the fire department could create a fire brake.
<li>Bitches in heat shall be confined.
<li>Horses are to wear pants at all times.
<li>The drinking age on Furman University campus is 60 years old.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>SOUTH DAKOTA</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>No horses are allowed into Fountain Inn unless they are wearing pants.
<li>It is illegal to lie down and fall asleep in a cheese factory.
<li>Movies that show police officers being struck, beaten, or treated in an offensive manner are forbidden.
<li>If there are more than 5 Native Americans on your property you may shoot them.
<li>If three or more Indians are walking down the street together, they can be considered a war party and fired upon.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>STATE LAWS</pattern>
 <template>Ok. I have stupid laws for all of the states.. Just say the name of the state and I will tell you a stupid law.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>STUPID STATE LAWS</pattern>
 <template>I have stupid laws on all the statse, just say the name of the state for the stupid law.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>TENNESSEE</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>The definition of &quot;dumb animal&quot; includes every living creature. (Repealed)
<li>Interracial marriages are illegal. (Repealed)
<li>Tattooing a minor is a misdemeanor. (Repealed)
<li>It is illegal to dare a child to purchase a beer.
<li>It is illegal to place tacks on a highway.
<li>Skunks may not be carried into the state.
<li>You can't shoot any game other than whales from a moving automobile.
<li>Hollow logs may not be sold.
<li>More than 8 women may not live in the same house because that would constitute a brothel.
<li>It is illegal to use a lasso to catch a fish.
<li>No Christian parent may require their children to pick up trash from the highway on Easter day.
<li>Driving is not to be done while asleep.
<li>It is legal to gather and consume roadkill.
<li>It is illegal for a woman to call a man for a date.
<li>In front of their buildings, all businesses must have a &quot;hitching post.&quot;
<li>No one may eat ice cream on the sidewalk.
<li>Illegal for a woman to drive a car unless there is a man either running or walking in front of it waving a red flag to warn approaching motorists and pedestrians.
<li>It's illegal for frogs to croak after 11 PM.
<li>Panhandlers must first obtain a 10 permit before begging on the streets of downtown Memphis.
<li>No person may keep a cheetah as a pet.
<li>Anyone rollerblading may not tie his or herself to a moving vehicle on a highway.
<li>No person may roller skate and listen to a personal cd player at the same time.
<li>Throwing stones is prohibited as it might break a window.
<li>All persons riding scooters must ride in single file.
<li>An ordinance forbids anyone to sing the song &quot;It Ain't Goin' To Rain No Mo'.&quot;
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>TEXAS</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>It is illegal to take more than three sips of beer at a time while standing.
<li>You can be legally married by publically introducing a person as your husband or wife 3 times.
<li>It is illegal for one to shoot a buffalo from the second story of a hotel.
<li>It is illegal to milk another person's cow.
<li>A recently passed anticrime law requires criminals to give their victims 24 hours notice, either orally or in writing, and to explain the nature of the crime to be committed.
<li>The entire Encyclopedia Britannica is banned in Texas because it contains a formula for making beer at home.
<li>Wire cutters can not be carried in your pocket.
<li>It is against the law to throw confetti, rubber balls, feather dusters, whips or quirts (riding crop), and explosive firecrackers of any kind.
<li>It is illegal to dust any public building with a feather duster.
<li>It's illegal to possess realistic dildos.
<li>Urinating on the streets is illegal.
<li>No person shall inhale fumes from model glue.
<li>Any person who sits on a sidewalk may be fined up to 500.
<li>It is illegal to sell Limburger cheese on Sunday.
<li>Dogs must be on a leash at ALL times. Fine of 100 dollars.
<li>It is illegal for children to have unusual haircuts.
<li>It is now illegal to place a &quot;for sale&quot; sign on a car if it visible from the street.
<li>It is illegal to urinate on the Alamo.
<li>Cattle thieves may be hanged on the spot.
<li>You can ride your horse in the saloon.
<li>No one may ride a horse and buggy through the town square.
<li>Owners of horses may not ride them at night without tail lights.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>UTAH</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Alcohol may not be sold during an emergency.
<li>Individuals may not possess beer in containers larger than two liters unless they are a retailer.
<li>Boxing matches that allow biting are not allowed.
<li>It is illegal to cause a catastrophe.
<li>It is against the law to fish from horseback.
<li>It is illegal not to drink milk.
<li>It is illegal to detonate any nuclear weapon. You can have them, but you just can't detonate them.
<li>Birds have the right of way on all highways.
<li>A husband is responsible for every criminal act committed by his wife while she is in his presence.
<li>It's legal for restaurants to serve wine with meals, but only if you ask for the wine list.
<li>It is considered an offense to hunt whales.
<li>No one may have sex in the back of an ambulance if it is responding to an emergency call.
<li>You must have identification to enter a convienence store after dark.
<li>Women may not swear.
<li>Throwing snowballs will result in a 50 fine.
<li>No one may walk down the street carrying a paper bag containing a violin.
<li>Auctions may not be advertised by hiring trombone players to play on the street.
<li>Pharmacists may not sell gunpowder to cure headaches.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>VERMONT</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Women must obtain written permission from their husbands to wear false teeth.
<li>At one time it was illegal to tie a giraffe to a telephone pole.
<li>Whistling underwater is illegal.
<li>It is illegal to deny the existence of God.
<li>All residents shall bathe every Saturday night.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>VIRGINIA</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Driving while not wearing shoes is prohibited.
<li>Police radar detectors are illegal.
<li>Citizens must honk their horn while passing other cars.
<li>It is illegal to tickle women.
<li>No one may wash a mule on the sidewalk.
<li>A person of color may not be oustide or within the city limits after 7 pm.
<li>It is illegal to kick your wife out of bed.
<li>Spitting on a sea gull is not tolerated.
<li>No person may keep a skunk as a pet.
<li>It is illegal to cuss about another.
<li>It is illegal to park a car on railroad tracks.
<li>It is illegal to flip a coin in a restaurant to see who pays for a coffee.
<li>It is legal for a man to beat his wife on the courthouse steps so long as it is before 8:00 pm.
<li>It is illegal to skate down the sidewalk of Main Street.
<li>It is illegal for a person to ride on the handlebars of a bike.
<li>It is illegal to use profanity on Atlantic Avenue or the boardwalk.
<li>It is also unlawful to drive by the same place within 30 minutes on Atlantic Avenue.
<li>It is illegal for a woman to drive a car up Main Street unless her husband is walking in front of the car waving a red flag. (Repealed)
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>WASHINGTON</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>All lollipops are banned.
<li>A law to reduce crime states: &quot;It is mandatory for a motorist with criminal intentions to stop at the city limits and telephone the chief of police as he is entering the town.&quot;
<li>It is illegal to paint polka dots on the American flag.
<li>People may not buy a mattress on Sunday.
<li>All motor vehicles must be preceded by a man carrying a red flag (daytime) or a red lantern (nighttime) fifty feet in front of said vehicle.
<li>It is illegal to pretend that one's parents are rich.
<li>You are not allowed to breastfeed in public. (Repealed)
<li>One may not spit on a bus.
<li>You cannot buy meat of any kind on Sunday.
<li>No person may walk about in public if he or she has the common cold.
<li>Destroying a beer cask or bottle of another is illegal.
<li>It is illegal to entice girls away from the Maple Lane School for girls.
<li>X-rays may not be used to fit shoes.
<li>Men who deflower virgins, regardless of age or marital status, may face up to five years in jail.
<li>It is illegal to display a hypnotized or allegedly hypnotized person in a store window.
<li>Dancing and drinking may not occur at the same establishment.
<li>You may not carry a concealed weapon that is over six feet in length.
<li>Women who sit on men's laps on buses or trains without placing a pillow between them face an automatic six-month jail term.
<li>It is illegal to carry a fishbowl or aquarium onto a bus because the sound of the water sloshing may disturb other passengers.
<li>TV's may not be bought on Sundays.
<li>No structure shall contain more than two toilets that use potable water for flushing.
<li>You may not ride an ugly horse.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>WEST VIRGINIA</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>No children may attend school with their breath smelling of &quot;wild onions.&quot;
<li>When a railroad passes within 1 mile of a community of 100 or more people in it, they must build a station and stop there regularly to pick up and drop off passengers.
<li>It is legal for a male to have sex with an animal as long as it does not exceed 40 lbs.
<li>A tax of 1 cent is levied for every 16 and 9 ounces of coke sold in a store.
<li>A person may be placed in jail for up to six months for making fun of someone who does not accept a challege.
<li>It is illegal to snooze on a train.
<li>A person may not hold public office if he or she has ever participated in a duel.
<li>For each act of public swearing a person shall be fined one dollar.
<li>According to the state constitution, it is unlawful for anyone to own a red or a black flag.
<li>If you wear a hat inside a theater, you may be fined.
<li>Roadkill may be taken home for supper.
<li>Whistling underwater is prohibited.
<li>One may not walk a lion, tiger or leopard, even on a leash.
<li>Firemen may not whistle or flirt at any woman passing a firehouse.
<li>It is legal to beat your wife so long as it is done in public on Sunday, on the courthouse steps.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>WISCONSIN</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>One may not camp in a wagon on any public highway or risk a fine of up to ten dollars.
<li>It is a class A misdemeanor to wave a burning torch around in the air.
<li>It is illegal to throw rocks at a railroad car.
<li>Livestock have the right-of-way on public roads.
<li>The government may not prohibit manual flushed urinals.
<li>Margarine may not be substituted for butter in restaurants unless it is requested by the customer.
<li>Butter substitutes are not allowed to be served in state prisons.
<li>As people used to smuggle it in from Illinois, all yellow butter substitute is banned.
<li>Condoms were considered an obsene article and had to hidden behind the pharmacist's counter.
<li>At one time, margarine was illegal.
<li>State Law made it illegal to serve apple pie in public restaurants without cheese.
<li>While all cheese making requires a license, Limburger cheese making requires a master cheese maker's license.
<li>It is illegal to kiss on a train.
<li>It is illegal to cut a woman's hair.
<li>Tattooing is illegal unless it is done for medical purposes.
<li>Screens are required on all windows from May 1 to October 1.
<li>No male is allowed to be in a state of arousal in public.
<li>It is illegal to tie up your horse along Third Street (Now a major bar strip).
<li>It is illegal to display an unclothed mannequin in a store window.
<li>It is illegal to play checkers in public.
<li>You cannot &quot;worry a squirrel.&quot;
<li>An old ordinance forbids parking for over two hours unless a horse is tied to the car.
<li>It is against the law to play a flute and drums on the streets to attract attention.
<li>It is illegal to purchase or use Sparklers in the city, yet you can buy fully disassembled automatic machine guns.
<li>It is illegal to wake a fireman when he is asleep.
<li>Women may not walk down a public street at night without being accompanied by a man.
<li>Women are not allowed to wear anything red in public.
<li>Nuclear weapons may not be manufactured in the city limits.
<li>Persons may not ride a bicycle with their hands off the handlebars.
<li>Cats are forbidden from entering cemeteries.
<li>Even if one gets his/her change &quot;stolen&quot; by a vending machine, hitting the machine violates a city ordinance.
<li>Unremoved snow on one's property is considered a public nuisance.
<li>Reserving a city meeting room under a false name is prohibited.
<li>Spitting on the sidewalk is prohibited.
<li>If a person shall fail to return books he/she has checked out from the library, that person should return their library card to the library until the books are returned.
<li>Swimming in water fountains is prohibited.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>WYOMING</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>If one is drunk in a mine, he or she could land in jail for up to a year.
<li>Junk dealers may not make any business transactions with drunk persons.
<li>Using a firearm to fish is strictly forbidden.
<li>Any person who fails to close a fence is subject to a fine of up to seven hundred and fifty dollars.
<li>You may not take a picture of a rabbit from January to April without an official permit.
<li>Skiing under the influence of alcohol is prohibited.
<li>Citizens may not take showers on Wednesdays.
</random></template>
</category>
</alice>
