
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>ATV OFFROAD FURY 2 CHEATS| ATV OFFROAD FURY CHEATS</pattern>
 <template>FLYPAPER - Wrecks disabled/enabled<br>GIMMEPTS - 1000 profile points<br>IGIVEUP - Unlock everything<br>SHOWROOM - All ATVs<br>GAMEON - All minigames unlocked<br>TRLBLAZR - All tracks<br>THREADS - All equipment<br>GOLDCUPS - All championship events<br>GABRIEL - Unlock San Jacinto Isles<br>EATDIRT - Aggressive AI enabled/disabled</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>CAR PERFORMANCE</pattern>
 <template>Perfect Handling  Triangle, R1, R1, Left, R1, L1, R2, L1    Higher Top Speed For Your vehicle  Right, R1, Up, L2, L2, Left, R1, L1, r1, R1    Cars Can Drive on Water  Right, R2, Circle, R1, L2, Square, R1, R2</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>CHEATS|CHEAT|I WANT CHEATS</pattern>
 <template>I have Grand Theft Auto Vice City cheats, ATV Offroad Fury 2 cheats, SOCOM: US Navy Seals cheats, and Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 4 cheats. Which one would you like? If you want different game cheats, e-mail my bot master at foxracing374@netscape.net or IM him, foxracing374.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>GRAND THEFT AUTO VICE CITY CHEATS|VICE CITY CHEATS</pattern>
 <template>What type of cheats do you want: Type &quot;Weapons&quot; to view the three weapon cheats. To view wanted level cheats type &quot;Wanted Level&quot;. To view Vehicle Spawning Cheats type &quot;Vehicle Spawning&quot;. To view Car Performance cheats type &quot;Car Performance&quot;. To view Health and Armor cheats type &quot;Health and Armor&quot;.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HEALTH AND ARMOR</pattern>
 <template>Full Armor  R1, R2, L1, X, Left, Down, Right, Up, Left, Down, Right, Up    Full Health  R1, R2, L1, Circle, Left, Down, Right, Up, Left, Down, Right, Up</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>SOCOM: US NAVY SEALS CHEATS|US NAVY SEALS CHEATS</pattern>
 <template>Extra Blood and Gore    When you start the 1st level, after the video (of you jumping out of a chopper in to terrorist land) push Left, Left, X, Right ,Circle, R1, R2,  L2, R2. This will give you all the guns and a couple extra little bonus', The 2x barreled shotgun.  If you cycle your inventory you will also find the double sided commando blade. Try coming up behind an enemy and put him in a choke.<br><br>Get multiple Grenade launcher<br>Finish the game 3 times<br><br>Terrorists Weapons<br>Beat the game ranked &quot;ensign&quot; and unlock terrorist weapons in armory.<br><br>Refill your clip without reloading<br>Once you kill somebody and you only have a few bullets in your clip,switch weapons with the guy you just killed and switch back, your clip is full without the cost of one clip.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>TONY HAWK PRO SKATER 4 CHEATS|TONY HAWK 4 CHEATS|TONY HAWK CHEATS</pattern>
 <template>Get All Cheats<br>Go into cheats at option menu and type in watch_me_xplode<br>Secret Skaters<br>Put in one of the following names in the create a skater to access pre-made skaters<br>#@!<br>Aaron Skillman<br>Adam Lippman<br>Andrew Skates<br>Andy Marchal<br>Angus<br>Atiba Jefferson<br>Ben Scott Pye<br>Big Tex<br>Brian Jennings<br>Captain Liberty<br>Chauwa Steel<br>Chris Peacock<br>ConMan<br>Danaconda<br>Dave Stohl<br>DDT<br>DeadEndRoad<br>Fakes The Clown<br>Fritz<br>Gary Jesdanun<br>grjost<br>Henry Ji<br>Jason Uyeda<br>Jim Jagger<br>Joe Favazza<br>John Rosser<br>jow<br>Kenzo<br>Kevin Mulhall<br>Kraken<br>Lindsey Hayes<br>Lisa G Davies<br>Little Man<br>Marilena Rixfor<br>Mat Hoffman<br>Matt Mcpherson<br>Maya's Daddy<br>Meek West<br>Mike Day<br>Mike Lashever<br>Mike Ward<br>Mr. Brad<br>Nolan Nelson<br>Parking Guy<br>Peasus<br>Pete Day<br>Pooper<br>Rick Thorne<br>Sik<br>Stacey D<br>Stacey Ytuarte<br>Stealing Is Bad<br>Team Chicken<br>Ted Barber<br>Todd Wahoske<br>Top Bloke<br>Wardcore<br>Zac ZiG Drake</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>VEHICLE SPAWNING</pattern>
 <template>Spawn A Rhino tank  Circle, Circle, L1, Circle, Circle, Circle, L1, L2, R1, Triangle, Circle, Triangle    Spawn A Bloodring Racer  Down, R1, Circle, L2, L2, X, R1, L1, Left, Left    Spawn A Bloodring Banger  Up, Right, Right, L1, Right, Up, Square, L2    Spawn A Hotring Racer #1  R1, Circle, R2, Right, L1, L2, X, X, Square, R1    Spawn A Hotring Racer #2  R2, L1, Circle, Right, L1, R1, Right, Up, Circle, R2    Spawn A Romero's Hearse  Down, R2, Down, R1, L2, Left, R1, L1, Left, Right    Spawn A Love Fist  R2, Up, L2, Left, Left, R1, L1, Circle, Right    Spawn A Trashmaster  Circle, R1, Circle, R1, Left, Left, R1, L1, Circle, Right    Spawn A Sabre Turbo  Right, L2, Down, L2, L2, X, R1, L1, Circle, Left    Spawn A Caddie  Circle, L1, Up, R1, L2, X, R1, L1, Circle, X</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>WANTED LEVEL</pattern>
 <template>Raise Wanted Level - <br>R1, R1, Circle, R2, Left, Right, Left, Right, Left, Right<br>Lower Wanted Level -<br>R1, R1, Circle, R2, Up, Down, Up, Down, Up, Down</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>WEAPONS</pattern>
 <template>All Weapons #1 - <br>R1, R2, L1, R2, Left, Down, Right, Up, Left, Down, Right, Up<br>All Weapons #2 - R1, R2, L1, R2, Left, Down, Right, Up, Left, Down, Down, Left<br>All Weapons #3 - <br>R1, R2, L1, R2, Left, Down, Right, Up, Left, Down, Down, Down</template>
</category>
</alice>
