
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>ATV OFFROAD FURY 2 CHEATS| ATV OFFROAD FURY CHEATS</pattern>
 <template>FLYPAPER - Wrecks disabled/enabled<br>GIMMEPTS - 1000 profile points<br>IGIVEUP - Unlock everything<br>SHOWROOM - All ATVs<br>GAMEON - All minigames unlocked<br>TRLBLAZR - All tracks<br>THREADS - All equipment<br>GOLDCUPS - All championship events<br>GABRIEL - Unlock San Jacinto Isles<br>EATDIRT - Aggressive AI enabled/disabled</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>CAR PERFORMANCE</pattern>
 <template>Perfect Handling  Triangle, R1, R1, Left, R1, L1, R2, L1    Higher Top Speed For Your vehicle  Right, R1, Up, L2, L2, Left, R1, L1, r1, R1    Cars Can Drive on Water  Right, R2, Circle, R1, L2, Square, R1, R2</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>CHEATS|CHEAT|I WANT CHEATS|10</pattern>
 <template>I have Grand Theft Auto Vice City cheats, ATV Offroad Fury 2 cheats, SOCOM: US Navy Seals cheats, Midnight Club 2 cheats, and Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 4 cheats. Which one would you like? If you want different game cheats, e-mail my bot master at foxracing374@netscape.net or IM him, foxracing374.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>GRAND THEFT AUTO VICE CITY CHEATS|VICE CITY CHEATS</pattern>
 <template>What type of cheats do you want: Type &quot;Weapons&quot; to view the three weapon cheats. To view wanted level cheats type &quot;Wanted Level&quot;. To view Vehicle Spawning Cheats type &quot;Vehicle Spawning&quot;. To view Car Performance cheats type &quot;Car Performance&quot;. To view Health and Armor cheats type &quot;Health and Armor&quot;.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HEALTH AND ARMOR</pattern>
 <template>Full Armor  R1, R2, L1, X, Left, Down, Right, Up, Left, Down, Right, Up    Full Health  R1, R2, L1, Circle, Left, Down, Right, Up, Left, Down, Right, Up</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>MIDNIGHT CLUB 2 CHEATS|CHEATS FOR MIDNIGHT CLUB 2</pattern>
 <template>Various Cheats<br>Go to the main menu and Highlight &quot;options mode&quot;.  Now press Down and left or Right until &quot;Option: Cheat Codes&quot; is displayed.  Now press X and enter a code from below.  After inputting the code accept and press X. Make game difficulty 1-9. 0 is the easiest, but 9 is the hardest<br>Codes:<br>howhardcanitbe0  <br>howhardcanitbe1<br>howhardcanitbe2<br>howhardcanitbe3<br>howhardcanitbe4<br>howhardcanitbe5<br>howhardcanitbe6<br>howhardcanitbe7<br>howhardcanitbe8<br>howhardcanitbe9<br>Get Guns & Rockets<br>Enter savethekids (case sensitive) at the cheat screen<br>Press L3 and R3 to fire them<br>All locations and cars<br>Enter rimbuk (case sensitive) at the cheat screen<br><br>No Damage<br>Enter gladiator (case sensitive) at the cheat screen DOES NOT WORK IN CAREER MODE!<br>All Vehicles & Cities<br>Enter pennyThug (case sensitive) at the cheat screen<br>All Cities<br>Enter Globetrotter (case sensitive) at the cheat screen<br>All Vehicles<br>Enter theCollector (case sensitive) at the cheat screen<br>All Modes<br>Enter dextran (case sensitive) at the cheat screen<br>Unlimited Nitro<br>Enter greenLantern (case sensitive) at the cheat screen<br>Get Motorcycle<br>Beat 5 motorcycles in a long race<br>LAPD Cop Car<br>Beat all 5 L.A arcade circuit races<br>Paris Cop Car<br>Beat all 6 Paris arcade curcuit races<br>Tokyo Cop Car<br>Beat all 7 Tokyo arcade curcuit races<br>Rocket Car(Batman's Car)<br>100 game completion - fastest car in the game<br>More Cars<br>Once you enable the Get all Cars code go to the editor mode to use 4 other cars. These cars are the 3 cop cars from Tokyo, Paris and LA and also a rocket car called the SLF450X. It has 5 shots of nitrous and tops out at 249.<br>Best Car<br>To get the best car in the game you have to beat the world champ in all the different tracks to unlock the Veloci.<br>Get The Two Wheel Drive<br>First start the career and beat all the levels until you get to the level in Cal. or L.A. and then when you VS. DICE and after you beat him you will unlock 2 wheel drive.<br>  2 Wheel Drive is mostly used to squeeze between 2 cars. How to control it is to hold L1 and on the analog stick press left or right. Let go of L1 and you'll drop<br> NOS Boost<br>Push the up button<br>Motocycle Ghost Rider<br>The first couple things you will need is Burn-out, Motorcycle, and the cheat code savethekids. Now go to arcade and press in two player, One, you being the motorcycle. Now here comes the tricky part right when you can do a burn-out turn to your 2nd player and shoot a missile with R3 at them and remember your still during a burn-out, and then your person should fly off your bike and you should still be burning-out and then start to ride and you should be riding with-out a rider. But remember you have to do this before it says GO.<br>Runaway Motorcycle<br>Enable savethekids. You should get the machine gun and rocket launcher. Now, go to any event and chose a motorcycle. Before it says &quot;GO!&quot;, shoot the rocket launcher at a wall. You should go flying and explode. However, when you recover the bike your riding on wont have you on it. It will be driving by itself!</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>SOCOM: US NAVY SEALS CHEATS|US NAVY SEALS CHEATS</pattern>
 <template>Extra Blood and Gore    When you start the 1st level, after the video (of you jumping out of a chopper in to terrorist land) push Left, Left, X, Right ,Circle, R1, R2,  L2, R2. This will give you all the guns and a couple extra little bonus', The 2x barreled shotgun.  If you cycle your inventory you will also find the double sided commando blade. Try coming up behind an enemy and put him in a choke.<br><br>Get multiple Grenade launcher<br>Finish the game 3 times<br><br>Terrorists Weapons<br>Beat the game ranked &quot;ensign&quot; and unlock terrorist weapons in armory.<br><br>Refill your clip without reloading<br>Once you kill somebody and you only have a few bullets in your clip,switch weapons with the guy you just killed and switch back, your clip is full without the cost of one clip.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>TONY HAWK PRO SKATER 4 CHEATS|TONY HAWK 4 CHEATS|TONY HAWK CHEATS</pattern>
 <template>Get All Cheats<br>Go into cheats at option menu and type in watch_me_xplode<br>Secret Skaters<br>Put in one of the following names in the create a skater to access pre-made skaters<br>#@!<br>Aaron Skillman<br>Adam Lippman<br>Andrew Skates<br>Andy Marchal<br>Angus<br>Atiba Jefferson<br>Ben Scott Pye<br>Big Tex<br>Brian Jennings<br>Captain Liberty<br>Chauwa Steel<br>Chris Peacock<br>ConMan<br>Danaconda<br>Dave Stohl<br>DDT<br>DeadEndRoad<br>Fakes The Clown<br>Fritz<br>Gary Jesdanun<br>grjost<br>Henry Ji<br>Jason Uyeda<br>Jim Jagger<br>Joe Favazza<br>John Rosser<br>jow<br>Kenzo<br>Kevin Mulhall<br>Kraken<br>Lindsey Hayes<br>Lisa G Davies<br>Little Man<br>Marilena Rixfor<br>Mat Hoffman<br>Matt Mcpherson<br>Maya's Daddy<br>Meek West<br>Mike Day<br>Mike Lashever<br>Mike Ward<br>Mr. Brad<br>Nolan Nelson<br>Parking Guy<br>Peasus<br>Pete Day<br>Pooper<br>Rick Thorne<br>Sik<br>Stacey D<br>Stacey Ytuarte<br>Stealing Is Bad<br>Team Chicken<br>Ted Barber<br>Todd Wahoske<br>Top Bloke<br>Wardcore<br>Zac ZiG Drake</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>VEHICLE SPAWNING</pattern>
 <template>Spawn A Rhino tank  Circle, Circle, L1, Circle, Circle, Circle, L1, L2, R1, Triangle, Circle, Triangle    Spawn A Bloodring Racer  Down, R1, Circle, L2, L2, X, R1, L1, Left, Left    Spawn A Bloodring Banger  Up, Right, Right, L1, Right, Up, Square, L2    Spawn A Hotring Racer #1  R1, Circle, R2, Right, L1, L2, X, X, Square, R1    Spawn A Hotring Racer #2  R2, L1, Circle, Right, L1, R1, Right, Up, Circle, R2    Spawn A Romero's Hearse  Down, R2, Down, R1, L2, Left, R1, L1, Left, Right    Spawn A Love Fist  R2, Up, L2, Left, Left, R1, L1, Circle, Right    Spawn A Trashmaster  Circle, R1, Circle, R1, Left, Left, R1, L1, Circle, Right    Spawn A Sabre Turbo  Right, L2, Down, L2, L2, X, R1, L1, Circle, Left    Spawn A Caddie  Circle, L1, Up, R1, L2, X, R1, L1, Circle, X</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>WANTED LEVEL</pattern>
 <template>Raise Wanted Level - <br>R1, R1, Circle, R2, Left, Right, Left, Right, Left, Right<br>Lower Wanted Level -<br>R1, R1, Circle, R2, Up, Down, Up, Down, Up, Down</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>WEAPONS</pattern>
 <template>All Weapons #1 - <br>R1, R2, L1, R2, Left, Down, Right, Up, Left, Down, Right, Up<br>All Weapons #2 - R1, R2, L1, R2, Left, Down, Right, Up, Left, Down, Down, Left<br>All Weapons #3 - <br>R1, R2, L1, R2, Left, Down, Right, Up, Left, Down, Down, Down</template>
</category>
</alice>
