
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>VIRUS JOKE</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Adam and Eve virus: Takes a couple of bytes out of your Apple.
<li>Airline virus: You're in Dallas, but your data is in Singapore.
<li>Anita Hill virus: Lies dormant for ten years.
<li>Arnold Schwarzenegger virus: Terminates and stays resident. It'll be back.
<li>AT&T virus: Every three minutes it tells you what great service you are getting.
<li>The MCI virus: Every three minutes it reminds you that you're paying too much for the AT&T virus.
<li>Bill Clinton virus: This virus mutates from region to region and we're not exactly sure what it does.
<li>Bill Clinton virus: Promises to give equal time to all processes: 50 to poor, slow processes; 50 to middle-class processes, and 50 to rich ones. This virus protests your computer's involvement in other computer's affairs, even though it has been having one of its own for 12 years.
<li>Congressional Virus: Overdraws your computer.
<li>Congressional Virus: The computer locks up, screen splits erratically with a message appearing on each half blaming the other side for the problem.
<li>Dan Quayle virus: Prevents your system from spawning any child processes without joining into a binary network.
<li>Dan Quayle virus: Simplye addse ane ee toe everye worde youe typee..
<li>David Duke virus: Makes your screen go completely white.
<li>Elvis virus: Your computer gets fat, slow, and lazy and then self destructs, only to resurface at shopping malls and service stations across rural America.
<li>Federal bureaucrat virus: Divides your hard disk into hundreds of little units, each of which do practically nothing, but all of which claim to be the most important part of the computer.
<li>Freudian virus: Your computer becomes obsessed with marrying its own motherboard.
<li>Gallup virus: Sixty percent of the PCs infected will lose 38 percent of their data 14 percent of the time (plus or minus a 3.5 percent margin of error).
<li>George Bush virus: Doesn't do anything, but you can't get rid of it until November.
<li>Government economist virus: Nothing works, but all your diagnostic software says everything is fine.
<li>Jerry Brown virus: Blanks your screen and begins flashing an 800 number.
<li>Madonna virus: If your computer gets this virus, lock up your dog!
<li>Mario Cuomo virus: It would be a great virus, but it refuses to run.
<li>Michael Jackson virus: Hard to identify because it is constantly altering its appearance. This virus won't harm your PC, but it will trash your car.
<li>New World Order virus: probably harmless, but it makes a lot of people really mad just thinking about it.
<li>Nike virus: Just Does It!
<li>Ollie North virus: Turns your printer into a document shredder.
<li>Oprah Winfrey virus: Your 200MB hard drive suddenly shrinks to 80MB, and then slowly expands back to 200MB.
<li>Pat Buchanan virus: Shifts all your output to the extreme right of your screen.
<li>Paul Revere virus: This revolutionary virus does not horse around. It warns you of impending hard disk attack---once if by LAN, twice if by C:.
<li>Paul Tsongas virus: Pops up on December 25 and says, &quot;I'm not Santa Claus.&quot;
<li>PBS virus: Your PC stops every few minutes to ask for money.
<li>Politically correct virus: Never calls itself a &quot;virus&quot;, but instead refers to itself as an &quot;electronic microorganism&quot;.
<li>Richard Nixon virus: Also known as the &quot;Tricky Dick Virus&quot;, you can wipe it out but it always makes a comeback.
<li>Right To Life virus: Won't allow you to delete a file, regardless of how old it is. If you attempt to erase a file, it requires you to first see a counselor about possible alternatives.
<li>Ross Perot virus: Activates every component in your system, just before the whole thing quits.
<li>Ted Kennedy virus: Crashes your computer but denies it ever happened.
<li>Ted Turner virus: Colorizes your monochrome monitor.
<li>Terry Randle virus: Prints &quot;Oh no you don't&quot; whenever you choose &quot;Abort&quot; from the &quot;Abort, Retry, Fail&quot; message.
<li>Texas virus: Makes sure that it's bigger than any other file.
<li>UK Parliament virus: Splits the screen into two with a message in each half blaming other side for the state of the system.
<li>Warren Commission virus: Won't allow you to open your files for 75 years.
<li>
</random></template>
</category>
</alice>
