
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>*</pattern>
 <template>Hey! this is l)nas's Bot  <br><u>Menu</u></br><br> Passwords  <br> Glitches  <br> News On Shiba's ~CodeSpy~</br> <br> type either of those! i got what you want!  <br> but if i dont have what you need just visit our site! http://glitchdnas.tk/ (we will have it their!)</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*(UTK)HIMSELF*</pattern>
 <template>(utk)Himself password: Michael</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<CXIIIS>DEADLY*</pattern>
 <template><cxiiis>Deadly password: black1</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<RGLA>SNAKEMAN*</pattern>
 <template><RGLA>SnakeMan password is: TRANS420</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<RGLA>SNAKEMAN*|*SNAKEMAN*</pattern>
 <template><RGLA>SnakeMan password: TRANS420</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*ACE!*</pattern>
 <template>ACE! password: khiry</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*ACE!*|ACE</pattern>
 <template>ACE! Password: khiry</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*AGENT 009*</pattern>
 <template>Agent 009 password: 123abc   <br> if that does not work it is abc123</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*ALL BOOT GLITCHES*|*6.)ALL BOOT GLITCHES*|*6*|ALL BOOT GLITCHES</pattern>
 <template><br>Crossroads Boot Room Glitch: <br>(1): Be a Terrorist <br>(2): From Terrorists go left down the narrow <br>alleyway were there will be yellow-orange baskets. <br>(3): Jump on the basket that is on it's side and the game will freeze.</br> <br>Claymore Boot Most Of People In Room Glitch: <br>(1): Be a Seal <br>(2): Get Claymores and plant them in a straight line <br>(3): Got to the part of the line where the most explosiveness will happen. <br>(4): Take out a grenade <br>(5): Unplug your ethernet cord, throw the grenade near u and wait for everything to explode, including the claymores.Then plug your ethernet cord back in. Try to commit suicide with the grenade not the claymores but it works well either way.</br> <br>One Vote Claymore Glitch <br>(1): Be a Seal <br>(2): Get claymores <br>(3): Plant all 4 claymores in a square <br>(4): Go in the middle of the square <br>(5): Hit circle and go to teamates <br>(6): Higlight the name of the person u want booted <br>(7): Unplug your ethernet cord, vote the person off, dethonate the claymores and then put your ethernet cord back in.</br> <br>(Note): This glitch is not accurate. Sometimes u will boot the wrong people or person.</br> <br>Another Boot Room Claymore Glitch <br>(1): Be a Seal <br>(2): Get claymores <br>(3): Plant the claymores in a square <br>(4): Take out a grenade <br>(5): Stand in the middle <br>(6): Unplug your ethernet cord and throw the grenade <br>(7): Wait for everything to explode then put ur ethernet cord back in</br> <br>(Note): Try to commit suicide with the grenade not the claymores. It still works well both way </br></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*ALL WEPONS SELECTED*|*4.)ALL WEPONS SELECTED*|*4*|ALL WEPONS SELECTED</pattern>
 <template><br>1.put ur handgun quick2 </br>  <br>2.get as close to a turrent as possibe and get out rpg </br>  <br>3.unplug ur internet cord </br>  <br>4.get out handgun,shoot 4to8 times </br>  <br>5.plug cord in </br>  <br>6.keep hitting action buttom till u mount turret </br>  <br>7.shoot turret 5to10 times </br>  <br>8.dismount turret</br>  <br>  <br>  To See more codes that are not in this list &quot;visit http://glitchdnas.tk/ &quot; where we have all the new glitches</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*ASSASSIN 00*</pattern>
 <template>ASSASSIN 00 password: 12345</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*AUTO HG*|*10.)AUTO HG*|*10*|AUTO HG</pattern>
 <template>have out ur smoke grnades, take somones model 18, Then have someone kill you.  <br>  <br>  To See more codes that are not in this list &quot;visit http://glitchdnas.tk/ &quot; where we have all the new glitches</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*AUTO M82ALA OR ANY GUN SD*|*12.)AUTO M82ALA OR ANY GUN SD*|*12*|AUTO M82ALA OR ANY GUN SD</pattern>
 <template>wat u need to do is for the m82 to be auto u will need a RPG, a model 18, and a M82A1A.       <br>1. have out ur m82 and go up to something u can climb       <br>2. take out RPG       <br>3. hilight ur model 18 by hiting r2 and unplug ur ethernet cable, take out the model 18 and climb the thing that u can climb.       <br>4. plug ethernet cable back in and climb up and down the climbble thing 2 times.       <br>5. nce u r done with this glitch u will have out a model18 on ur screen but on ever1 elses screen u will have out the m82a1a and when u shoot the model 18 ur m82a1a will be shootign on ever1 elses screen in full auto. (ask some1 wat gun u have out).       <br>this is the same with the m87 and TA. if u do this with a mark 23 SD instead of model 18 it will make ur gun silenced. but to do that instead of having out ur primary first u will have out ur handgun then u take out rpg hilight primary....ect.  <br>  <br>  To See more codes that are not in this list &quot;visit http://glitchdnas.tk/ &quot; where we have all the new glitches</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*BDOG*</pattern>
 <template>Bdog password: 22</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*BECOME A HOSTAGE*|*7.)BECOME A HOSTAGE *|*7*|BECOME A HOSTAGE</pattern>
 <template><br>1.)have 3 people in the game  <br>2.)2 people must be on Seals, the host and a player.  <br>3.)the player must do the skin glitch so he looks like a seal on terrorist  <br>4.)Everyone greens up  <br>5.)Host must leave durring loading screen  <br>6.)Once host comes back, The skin glitched player will be a hostage!  <br>  <br>  To See more codes that are not in this list &quot;visit http://glitchdnas.tk/ &quot; where we have all the new glitches</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*BECOME INVISABLE*|*29.)BECOME INVISABLE*|*29*|BECOME INVISABLE</pattern>
 <template><br>Ok, the host must be dead for this to work. the host also need a shotgun. You (assuming you are the host) wait until the round ends, right when the screen is freezing into the stat screen, unplug your ethernet cord. then when the clock hits 4, plug it back in. you will spawn, and be the only one there. now, while you are still spawned early, find the person to be invisible. if you time this right, this will work. you have to shoot them right as the lag is catching up, and you cant kill them, they have to be knocked over. if you do it right, they will be invisible...</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*BITCH*</pattern>
 <template>Stop with the bad name calling dick</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*BLACK-FOX*</pattern>
 <template>Black-Fox password: 123456</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*BRB*</pattern>
 <template>Ight, tell me when your back, meanwhile visit http://glitchdnas.tk/</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*BUCKDOG*</pattern>
 <template>Buckdog password: 22</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*BYPASS DNAS GLITCH*|*1.)BYPASS DNAS GLITCH*|1|BYPASS DNAS GLITCH</pattern>
 <template><br>This glitch will allow you to get online with all codebreaker codes. (now you can do everything that idot does without codemajic) some of you have probably seen me in e-seals with this one.</br>    <br>Requirements: you must have 2 psx2's, 2 copies of socom 2, 2 net adaptors and a router.    have psx2 #1 with codes installed and psx2 #2 without codes (systems must be side by side) i have to move my bedroom tv to my living room to do this.</br>    <br>Get both systems to the net config screen    start psx2 #2 loading, wait 5 seconds and start psx2 #1 (this time may vary according to your connection speed so try it with both systems clean a couple times to get the timing correct so you dont get banned) as soon as the dnas progress bar on psx2 #1 lags you quickly pull out both cords and put the cord from system #2 into system #1. </br>   <br>you have to get the timing on this one just right, what you want to see is the one systemdo its 1st lag on the progress bar at the same time as the second system is doing its last lag on the progress bar.</br>    <br>I practiced this about 15 times without codes before i did it with codes so dont blame me if you get banned trying it right off the bat. if you make it online without the codes on sytem #1 then you did it right. if it says net cable disconnected then you did it to slow.    this is the best glitch in the game and was found by me. as of right now only a few people know it (until now). if you dont have 2 psx2s dont bitch, and im sure alot of people will say this is bs so come to e-seals 6 tonight room dnasglitch time 8 pm central and i will prove it to all disbelievers.<br>    <br>I cant believe ive known this one for over a month now and noone else has figured it out because it is so simple. your basically just using one system to bypass the dnas and the second system gets the ok and your on.</br></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*CHAIN REACTION GLITCHES*|*26.)CHAIN REACTION GLITCHES*|*26*|CHAIN REACTION GLITCHES</pattern>
 <template>Get into Water tanks in back (way 1)   <br>do the ladder glitch from FF      <br>Get into water tanks in back (way 2)   <br>Get Rocket Launcher put it on quick two, take primary out go to top of ladder, press climb then L2 immedietly after      <br>Get into tall thing on sub   <br>Read above ( Get into Water tanks in back way 2)      <br>Get in bottom of sub   <br>Do above then go to edge of area your in prone and crawl into the bottom      <br>Get onto roof of level   <br>At Seals spawn, the right metal window thing, have some1 with a shotgun go prone at the far end (near wall) stand on his back with pistol out and let him shoot you above the kneecaps you will fly onto the window and you can just jump over the little wall.   <br>Note: you cannot shoot through the roof, it just shows sparks</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*COLT 44*</pattern>
 <template>Colt 44 password: boob</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*COOKIE CRISP*</pattern>
 <template>Cookie Crisp password: da</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*DIGGI*</pattern>
 <template>Diggi password: 123</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*FAG*</pattern>
 <template>..... i hate you to bitch now ask me for some glitches</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*GET INANYTHING U CAN CLIMB*|*18TO .)GET INTO ANYTHING U CAN CLIMB*|*18*|GET INTO ANYTHING U CAN CLIMB</pattern>
 <template><br>1.get pmn mines out   <br>2.climb and box and hang   <br>3.start climbinb all the way up   <br>4. as you pulling yourself up plant a mine it will teleport you to the ground and you will climb into the box remember it takes practice and good timing.  <br>  <br>  To See more codes that are not in this list &quot;visit http://glitchdnas.tk/ &quot; where we have all the new glitches</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*GHETTO GOD GLITCH*|*23.)GHETTO GOD GLITCH*|*23*|GHETTO GOD GLITCH</pattern>
 <template><br>1. set ur rpg/at-4 to quick 2    <br>2. unplug ur cord and start to shoot as much as u can with ur primary    <br>3. when it freezes, plug ur cord back in and start tapping L2    <br>4. when the game catches up, ur rpg/at-4 should come out and to everyone else, it'll look like you just shot 5 to 6 rpg rounds out of ur body in every direction  <br>  <br>  To See more codes that are not in this list &quot;visit http://glitchdnas.tk/ &quot; where we have all the new glitches  <br>   <br>   To See more codes that are not in this list &quot;visit http://glitchdnas.tk/ &quot; where we have all the new glitches</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*GLITCHES*</pattern>
 <template><br>Glitches</br> <br>Type the glitch you want out of all these glitches &quot;must be exact&quot;</br> <br>1.)Bypass DNAS Glitch</br> <br>2.)Short Claymore Slide</br> <br>3.)One Shot Kill With M18</br> <br>4.)All wepons selected</br> <br>5.)lock ladders</br> <br>6.)All Boot Glitches</br> <br>7.)Become a hostage</br> <br>8.)invisible mines and claymores</br> <br>9.)rapid rpg</br> <br>10.)Auto hg</br> <br>11.)Plant MP bomb by yourself</br> <br>12.)Auto m82ala or any gun silent</br> <br>13.)Make game never start</br> <br>14.)Rapid nades</br> <br>15.)Same team glitch</br> <br>16.)Run with rpg</br> <br>17.)Snipe with pistol</br> <br>18.)Get into anything u can climb </br> <br>19.)Talk after getting voted</br> <br>20.)God glitch</br> <br>21.)Shoot nades out of rpg</br> <br>22.)M16 auto</br> <br>23.)Ghetto god glitch </br> <br>24.)God glitch in respawn</br> <br>25.)PS2 ninga jump</br> <br>26.)Chain Reaction Glitches</br> <br>27.)The Hulk Glitch</br> <br>28.)NesQuik Glitch</br><br>29.)Become Invisable</br><br>To See more codes that are not in this list &quot;visit http://glitchdnas.tk/ &quot; where we have all the new glitches!</br></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*GOD GLITCH IN RESPAWN*|*24.)GOD GLITCH IN RESPAWN*|*24*|GOD GLITCH IN RESPAWN</pattern>
 <template><br>**set rocket launcher for quick 2 and primary as quick 1    <br>**equip primary    <br>**disconnect cord and unload as many bullets as you can    <br>**after you freeze, plug back in cord and keep tapping quick 2    <br>**after you switch to your rocket launcher (on other peoples screens) rockets shoot EVERYWHERE out of your body  <br>  <br>  To See more codes that are not in this list &quot;visit http://glitchdnas.tk/ &quot; where we have all the new glitches</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*GOD GLITCH*|*20.)GOD GLITCH*|*20*|GOD GLITCH</pattern>
 <template>1. Pick the m4a1-m203!    <br>2. Do the skin glitch!    <br>3. Green Up    <br>4.The first round of the game commit suicide    <br>5.Then in the last slot pick the rpg!    <br>6.Now that you did it to do it you first fire you rpg and then fire your primary weapon and on everybody elses screen your shooting rpgs!    <br>7. If you do that and reload you'll get everybody to shoot blanks but to you your shooting rpgs.    <br>8. If you shoot a enemy or a friend you don't like long enough you'll boot them   <br>  <br>  To See more codes that are not in this list &quot;visit http://glitchdnas.tk/ &quot; where we have all the new glitches</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*HIJAK11*</pattern>
 <template>Hijak11 password: gateway</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*INVISIBLE MINES AND CLAYMORES*|*8.)INVISIBLE MINES AND CLAYMORES*|*8*|INVISIBLE MINES AND CLAYMORES</pattern>
 <template>Go up to wall you can climb pull out rpg highlight mines claymores in inventory dont get them out just hightlight them then unplug your cord run and try to climb the wall guy will freeze plug cord in and climb the wall twice you will only be able to see the clays/mines but no1 not can see them!  <br>   <br>   To See more codes that are not in this list &quot;visit http://glitchdnas.tk/ &quot; where we have all the new glitches</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*JAB1*</pattern>
 <template>Jab1 password: red</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*JC0603*</pattern>
 <template>Jc0603 password: 0603</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*LIQUIDFIRE1111*</pattern>
 <template>liquidfire1111 password: 1234</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*LOCK LADDERS*|*5.)LOCK LADDERS *|*5*|LOCK LADDERS</pattern>
 <template><br>1.) have claymores, or pmn mines out</br>  <br>2.) Go to a ladder and climb all the way up to the top</br>  <br>3.) Turn around get back onto the ladder</br>  <br>4.) Ladder slide down</br>  <br>5.) hit action button to climb back up and plant pmn mine or claymore at the same time</br>  Now the ladder should be broken!  <br>   <br>   To See more codes that are not in this list &quot;visit http://glitchdnas.tk/ &quot; where we have all the new glitches</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*LOST-HOPE*</pattern>
 <template>Lost-Hope password: XCV</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*M16 AUTO*|*22.)M16 AUTO*|*22*|M16 AUTO</pattern>
 <template><br>1st) have your m16 and get to a dead body with an automatic rifle.   <br>2nd) now swithc to your handgun.   <br>3rd)now pick up the dead body's hand gun.   <br>4th) pick up the automatic rifle from the dead body.   <br>5th) go into prone position with your hand gun still out.   <br>6th)now take out a grenade and throw it infront of you while you are laying down so that it kills you.   <br>7th) now you wait till round ends and next round your m16 will be automatic.  <br>   <br>   To See more codes that are not in this list &quot;visit http://glitchdnas.tk/ &quot; where we have all the new glitches</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*MAKE GAME NEVER START*|*13.)MAKE GAME NEVER START*|*13*|MAKE GAME NEVER START</pattern>
 <template>When your in the game and the game is about to begin highlight the armory section then mash all the buttons on your controller square, circle x, triangle and your screen should turn black and the game will never start. You will have to restart you ps2 after this is done!</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*NESQUIK GLITCH*|*28.)NESQUIK GLITCH*|*28*|NESQUIK GLITCH</pattern>
 <template><br>FOR THE INVIS M203'S YOU SEE THEM BUT PEOPLE SEE YOU SHOOTING A BULLET BUT YOU CANT KILL THEM <br>1.GET M203 WAIT FOR THE ROUND TO END IN ANY WAY <br>2.GUST AS THE MUSIC STOPS WAIT 2 SEC PULL CORD WAIT 2 SEC PUT BACK IN. <br>------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- <br>6-RPG'S: <br>1.DO SKINS GET M203 AND THE RPG <br>2.SET RPG AS QUIK 2 <br>3.HAVE YOUR M203'S OUT <br>4.WAIT FOUR ROUND TO HIT 0:00 ONCE CLOCK HITS 0:00 WAIT 1 SEC THEN PULL CORD FOR 2 SEC THEN PLUG BACK IN <br>5.THEN IT SHOULD WORK (MAY NOT WORK FIRST TIME) AND ONLY OTHER PEOPLE SEE YOU SHOOTING RPG BUT WHEN YOU SHOOT THEM WITH THE M2O3 THAT YOU START WITH IT WILL SAY YOU KILLED THEM WITH RPG ROUND. <br>------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- <br>NEW GOD: <br>1.DO THE SKINS <br>2.GET RPG AND M203 <br>3.HAVE YOUR M203'S OUT <br>4.WAIT FOUR ROUND TO HIT 0:00 ONCE CLOCK HITS 0:00 WAIT 1 SEC THEN PULL CORD FOR 2 SEC THEN PLUG BACK IN <br>5.AND THEN DO DAVID BLANE WITH M203'S OUT IN STEAD OF A NORMAL GUN HAVE FUN IF YOU HAVE ANY TROUBEL THEN GUST AIM ME <br> <br> <br>BY THE WAY IM TAKEING CREDIT FOR THIS GLITCH SO CALL IT NESQUIK GLITCH OR A.K.A NESS GLITCH LOL TY</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*NEWS ON SHIBA'S ~CODESPY~*|* ~CODESPY~*|*CODESPY*|*SHIBA*|NEWS ON SHIBA'S ~CODESPY</pattern>
 <template>Want news on shiba's new cheating device called CodeSpy? Just visit his site http://s2hacking.tk/</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*NEWYORK~KID*</pattern>
 <template>NewYork~Kid password: 1234</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*ONE SHOT KILL WITH M18*|*3.)ONE SHOT KILL WITH M18*|*3*|ONE SHOT KILL WITH M18</pattern>
 <template><br>1. Take a m11 or m18 from armory</br>  <br>2. THen take out smokes </br>  <br>3. pick up a Deagle from the gorund </br>  <br>4. Dont move and tell someone to kill you. </br>  <br>5. Then next round it hsould be one shot kill</br></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*PASSWORDS*|*PASSWORD*</pattern>
 <template>Want a password!   <br>Make sure to type the name exact!  <br>  <br><RGLA>SnakeMan  <br>PIMPEN  <br>Buckdog  <br>(utk)Himself   <br>liquidfire1111  <br><cxiiis>Deadly  <br>Agent 009  <br>ASSASSIN 00  <br>Hijak11  <br>Snark  <br>Black-Fox  <br>PeoplesChamp~  <br>Diggi  <br>Cookie Crisp  <br>~G~H~O~S~T~  <br>Jc0603  <br>Jab1  <br>Wingz  <br>Bdog  <br>Lost-Hope  <br>ACE!  <br>White Mike 5  <br>NewYork~Kid  <br>Colt 44    <br> want more? visit http://glitchdnas.tk/</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*PEOPLESCHAMP~*</pattern>
 <template>PeoplesChamp~ password: ME</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*PIMPEN*</pattern>
 <template>PIMPEN password: =</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*PLANT MP BOMB BY YOURSELF*|*11.)PLANT MP BOMB BY YOURSELF *|*11*|PLANT MP BOMB BY YOURSELF</pattern>
 <template><br>Tt is the same thing as with two people except with one person u still plant with the shhot button and stuff like that this is how u do it       <br>when u are about to plany bomb have claymore on quick 1 or 2 when its about to plant (the guy stands up to take it out) u take out ur claymores</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*PS2 NINGA JUMP*|*25.)PS2 NINGA JUMP*|*25*|PS2 NINGA JUMP</pattern>
 <template><br>1.be in crouch   <br>2.shot gun where u wont to go   <br>3.move d-pad left and right really fast   <br>4.hit squar ans tringle reall fat but not at the same time   <br>5.do step 3 and 4 at the same time</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*PS2 NINJA JUMP*|*25.)PS2 NINJA JUMP*|*25*|PS2 NINJA JUMP</pattern>
 <template><br>1.be in crouch   <br>2.shot gun where u wont to go   <br>3.move d-pad left and right really fast   <br>4.hit squar ans tringle reall fat but not at the same time   <br>5.do step 3 and 4 at the same time</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*RAPID NADES*|*14.)RAPID NADES*|*14*|RAPID NADES</pattern>
 <template><br>1. Have a rocket as quick 1 and nades on quick <br>2. take out rocket spin right and keep taping left right left right on the d pad then press quick 2 and the same time pressing left and right you should have a rocket out but really your nades other ppl see u standing now spin around and throw your nades the plus to this glitch is that your sliding when your done</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*RAPID RPG*|*9.)RAPID RPG*|*9*|RAPID RPG</pattern>
 <template><br>1. set rocket launcher for quick 2 and primary as quick 1    <br>2. equip primary    <br>3. disconnect cord and unload as many bullets as you can    <br>4. after you cant move, plug back in cord and keep tapping quick 2    <br>5. when u switch to your rocket launcher on other peoples screens, rocket shoot EVERYWHERE out of your body</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*RUN WITH RPG*|*16.)RUN WITH RPG*|*16*|RUN WITH RPG</pattern>
 <template><br>Get an RPG....And C4    <br>Go up to a C4 door that has a wall you can climb right by it    <br>Plant C4 then turn and climb before You plant it    <br>It should be your active weapon now (Appearing on the bottom left)    <br>Go up to a turrent and get on it and just sit there...    <br>For a while like 1 minute maybe 2 and when it fires on its own    <br>Get off and switch to Rocket launcher    <br>Then Walk and your rocket launcher should still be your active weapon    U can run and stuff...</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*SAME TEAM GLITCH*|*15.)SAME TEAM GLITCH*|*15*|SAME TEAM GLITCH</pattern>
 <template><br>For 2 ppl have the host red on the team u want to be on then have a person on the opposite team green have the host count to 3 on three the host greens up and the other person greens down the host will start loading on his screen but on the other persons screen he'll still be in the lobby now if ur the person in the lobby u wait until u can switch teams then hit (X) 2x fast u should switch and green right after u do that itll force       <br>For 3-4 ppl have the extra person or people on the team with the host green but the host still has to be red and just do the same as the 2 person one but with a person not involved in nething count to 3</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*SHOOT NADES OUT OF RPG*|*21.)SHOOT NADES OUT OF RPG*|*21*|SHOOT NADES OUT OF RPG</pattern>
 <template>go near a ledge, with ur rg on ur quick 2. then climb and press l2 at the same time. now turn around at look at the ground from which u just climbed up. now go to ur menu and get ur nades. u should fall off the ledge, and it should show ur nades as ur weapon but ur rocket launcher will be out. now u can shoot them out of ur rocket. &quot;note they dont really go that far, it mainly looks cool&quot;</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*SHORT CLAYMORE SLIDE*|2.)SHORT CLAYMORE SLIDE|2|SHORT CLAYMORE SLIDE|2</pattern>
 <template><br>1. Take out yer nades and put clays on quick</br> <br>2. unplug e cord throw a grenade(i suggest a smoke 4 newbs) then tap L2 and plant a clay.. you should be frozen now. if you are plug e cord back in and run around. make sure to have someone with you so you can tell if you did it because it doesnt last long... when you do it, you are stuck in a claymore plant position.</br></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*SNARK*</pattern>
 <template>Snark password: smurf</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*SNIPE WITH PISTOL*|*17.)SNIPE WITH PISTOL*|*17*|SNIPE WITH PISTOL</pattern>
 <template>Take a gun with a scope; ie: Stg 77 IW 80 M4A1 etc.  and a desert eagle for a 1 hit kill  .  take out yer primary, push O then R2 right after(or the button for the vote screen and armory) push triangle. you should now be in the armory, if you are keep pushing up(on D-pad) until you are in your scope, then keep pushing up until pistol is highlighted and push X. you can now snipe with yer pistol.   <br>PS you can use snipers but not the high powered rifles like the m82, m87 and the m40a1</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*TALK AFTER GETTING VOTED*|*19.)TALK AFTER GETTING VOTED*|*19*|TALK AFTER GETTING VOTED</pattern>
 <template>When your getting voted off of a room grab the mic and when ur screen freezes eject ur cd then your screen should turn black and you can hear the people on your team and it automatically gives you the mic when it becomes free so you can talk shit.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*THE HULK GLITCH*|*27.)THE HULK GLITCH*|*27*|THE HULK GLITCH</pattern>
 <template><br>1) Select an RPG or AT-4   <br>2) Go to a place where you can climb   <br>3) Bring out your RPG or AT-4   <br>4) Go into armory and highlight your primary   <br>5) Pull out your ethernet cord   <br>6) Select your primary then climb   <br>7) Plug cord back in   <br>-Once your a the top move forward a little bit, then jump back and you must land on the higher ground from where you climbed up onto.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*WEBSITE*</pattern>
 <template>Visit http://glitchdnas.tk/ for more glitches!</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*WHITE MIKE 5*</pattern>
 <template>White Mike 5 password: balls</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*WINGZ*</pattern>
 <template>Wingz  password: myth123</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YOU HOME</pattern>
 <template>Yep</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*~G~H~O~S~T~*</pattern>
 <template>~G~H~O~S~T~ password: qwertyuiop</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>ASS</pattern>
 <template>Fucl< you</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>GI</pattern>
 <template>say something intelligent</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>OR</pattern>
 <template>or... what</template>
</category>
</alice>
