<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>*ALABAMA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Jasper, Alabama, it is illegal for a husband to beat his wife with a stick larger in diameter than his thumb.
<li>It is illegal to play Dominos on Sunday in Alabama.
<li>It is illegal to wear a fake moustache that causes laughter in church in Alabama.
<li>In Alabama, putting salt on a railroad track may be punishable by death.
<li>In Alabama, bear wrestling matches are prohibited.
<li>In Alabama, it is illegal to maim oneself to escape duty.
<li>In Alabama, you may not drive barefooted.
<li>In Alabama, it is considered an offense to open an umbrella on a street, for fear of spooking horses.
<li>In Alabama, it is illegal to sell peanuts in Lee County after sundown on Wednesday.
<li>In Alabama, boogers may not be flicked into the wind.
<li>In Alabama, it is legal to drive the wrong way down a one-way street if you have a lantern attached to the front of your automobile.
<li>In Alabama, you must have windshield wipers on your car.
<li>In Alabama, you may not have an ice cream cone in your back pocket at any time.
<li>In Alabama, masks may not be worn in public.
<li>In Alabama, women are able to retain all property they owned prior to marriage in the case of divorce.  However, this provision does not apply to men.
<li>In Alabama, it is illegal for a driver to be blindfolded while operating a vehicle.
<li>In Alabama, incestuous marriages are legal.
<li>You may not wear blue jeans down Noble Street in Anniston, Alabama.
<li>In Auburn, Alabama, no person may spit on the floor of a church.
<li>In Auburn, Alabama, it is illegal to bike, rollerskate, skateboard, or inline skate in a commercially zoned area.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*ALASKA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Fairbanks, Alaska, it is illegal to feed alcoholic beverages to a moose.
<li>While it is legal to shoot bears, waking sleeping bears for the purpose of taking a photograph is prohibited in Alaska.
<li>A law in Fairbanks, Alaska, does not allow moose to have sex on city streets.
<li>Moose may not be viewed from an airplane in Alaska.
<li>In Alaska, it is considered an offense to push a live moose out of a moving airplane.
<li>In Alaska, no one may tie their pet dog to the roof of a car.
<li>In Anchorage, Alaska, it is illegal to string a wire across any road.
<li>In Anchorage, Alaska persons may not live in a trailer as it is being hauled across the city.
<li>A person may only carry a concealed slingshot in Haines, Alaska if that person has received the appropriate license.
<li>In Haines, Alaska, it is against the law to break any law in title 9 of the code (public peace, morals, and welfare).
<li>In Haines, Alaska, employers of bars may not let their bartenders serve while they are drunk themselves.
<li>In Juneau, Alaska, owners of flamingos may not let their pets into barber shops.
<li>In Juneau, Alaska, buildings that preserve scenic vistas are awarded bonus points by the government.
<li>In Nome, Alaska, one may not roam the city with a bow and arrows.
<li>In Soldotna, Alaska, persons may not allow &quot;attractive nuisances&quot; to exist.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*ALBERTA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Businesses in Alberta must provide rails for tying up horses.
<li>Wooden logs may not be painted in Alberta.
<li>It is illegal to set fire to the wooden leg of a wooden legged man in Alberta.
<li>You may never use dice to play craps in Alberta.
<li>In Alberta if you are released from prison, it is required that you are given a handgun with bullets and a horse, so you can ride out of town.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*ARIZONA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Tucson, Arizona, it is illegal for women to wear pants.
<li>In Globe, Arizona, it is illegal to play cards in the street with a Native American.
<li>In Glendale, Arizona, it is illegal to drive a car in reverse.
<li>In Nogales, Arizona, it is illegal to wear suspenders.
<li>In Arizona, hunting camels is prohibited.
<li>In Arizona, any misdemeanor committed while wearing a red mask is considered a felony.
<li>In Arizona, there is a possible 25 years in prison for cutting down a cactus.
<li>In Arizona, donkeys cannot sleep in bathtubs.
<li>In Arizona, a class 2 misdemeanor occurs if one places a mark upon a flag which is &quot;likely to provoke physical retaliation&quot;.
<li>In Arizona, it is illegal to manufacture imitation cocaine.
<li>In Arizona, when being attacked by a criminal or burglar, you may only protect yourself with the same weapon that the other person possesses.
<li>In Arizona, it is unlawful to refuse a person a glass of water.
<li>In Arizona, you may not have more than two dildos in a house.
<li>In Hayden, Arizona, if you bother the cottontails or bullfrogs, you will be fined.
<li>In Maricopa County, Arizona, no more than six girls may live in any house.
<li>In Mesa, Arizona, it is illegal to smoke cigarettes within 15 feet of a public place unless you have a Class 12 liquor license.
<li>In Mohave County, Arizona, a decree declares that anyone caught stealing soap must wash himself with it until it is all used up.
<li>In Prescott, Arizona, no one is permitted to ride their horse up the stairs of the county court house.
<li>In Tempe, Arizona, one must be 18 years old to buy spray paint.
<li>In Tombstone, Arizona, it is illegal for men and women over the age of 18 to have less than one missing tooth visible when smiling.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*ARKANSAS*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>A man can legally beat his wife, but not more than once a month in Arkansas.
<li>In Fayetteville, Arkansas, it is illegal to kill &quot;any living creature.&quot;
<li>In Arkansas, schoolteachers who bob their hair may forfeit their pay raises.
<li>Flirtation between men and women on the streets of Little Rock, Arkansas, may result in a 30-day jail term.
<li>The Arkansas River can rise no higher than to the Main Street bridge in Little Rock, Arkansas.
<li>In Arkansas, oral sex is considered to be sodomy.
<li>In Arkansas, alligators may not be kept in bathtubs.
<li>In Little Rock, Arkansas, honking one's car horn at a sandwich shop after 9 p.m. is against the law.
<li>In Little Rock, Arkansas, no one may &quot;suddenly start or stop&quot; their car at a McDonald's.
<li>In Little Rock, Arkansas, dogs may not bark after 6 p.m.
<li>In Little Rock, Arkansas, it is unlawful to walk one's cow down Main Street after 1 p.m. on Sunday.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*AUSTRALIA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Australia, a life sentence is 25 years.
<li>In Australia, children may not purchase cigarettes but they may smoke them.
<li>In Australia, you may never leave your car keys in an unattended vehicle.
<li>In Australia, it is illegal to roam the streets wearing black clothes, felt shoes and black shoe polish on your face as these items are the tools of a cat burglar.
<li>In Australia, it is illegal to walk on the right hand side of a footpath.
<li>Under Australian Communications authority (ACA) regulations, a modem can't pick up on the first ring.
<li>In Australia, taxi cabs are required to carry a bale of hay in the trunk.
<li>In Australia, bars are required to stable, water and feed the horses of their patrons.
<li>In Australia, the legal age for straight sex is 16, unless the person is in the care/custody of the older person, in which case it is 18.
<li>In Australia, only licensed electricians may change a light bulb.
<li>In Australia, it is illegal to wear hot pink pants after midday Sunday.
<li>In Australia, you must have a neck to knee swimsuit in order to swim at Brighton Beach.
<li>In Australia, until the Port Arthur Killings it was legal to own an AK-47 but not legal to be gay.
<li>In Australia, lawmakers are proposing a new law that will not allow anyone to come closer than 100 meters from a dead whale's carcass.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*BELGIUM*</pattern>
 <template>In Belgium, a driver who needs to turn through oncoming traffic has the right of way unless he slows down or stops.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*BRITISH COLUMBIA*</pattern>
 <template>It is illegal to kill a sasquatch in British Columbia.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*CALIFORNIA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In California, it is a misdemeanor to shoot at any kind of game from a moving vehicle, unless the target is a whale.
<li>In Pacific Grove, California, &quot;molesting&quot; butterflies can result in a 500 dollar fine.
<li>In Pasadena, California, it is illegal for a secretary to be alone in a room with her boss.
<li>It is illegal to set a mousetrap without a hunting license in California.
<li>In Long Beach, California, it is illegal to curse on a mini-golf course.
<li>In San Francisco, California, it is illegal to wipe one's car with used underwear.
<li>It is illegal to cry on the witness stand in Los Angeles, California, courts.
<li>In Ventura County, California, cats and dogs are not allowed to have sex without a permit.
<li>In Los Angeles, California, a man is legally entitled to beat his wife with a leather belt or strap, but the belt can't be wider than 2 inches, unless he has his wife's consent to beat her with a wider strap. Consent should be given prior to the event, as is carefully stipulated.
<li>In California, sunshine is guaranteed to the masses.
<li>In California, animals are banned from mating publicly within 1,500 feet of a tavern, school, or place of worship.
<li>Bathhouses are against the law in California.
<li>Women may not drive in a house coat in California.
<li>No vehicle without a driver may exceed 60 mph in California.
<li>In Alhambra, California, you cannot leave your car on the street overnight without the proper permit.
<li>In Arcadia, California, peacocks have the right of way to cross any street, including driveways.
<li>In Baldwin Park, California, nobody is allowed to ride a bicycle in a swimming pool.
<li>In Belvedere, California, City Council order reads: &quot;No dog shall be in a public place without its master on a leash.&quot;
<li>In Blythe, California, you are not permitted to wear cowboy boots unless you already own at least two cows.
<li>In Burlingame, California, it is illegal to spit, except on baseball diamonds.
<li>In Cathedral City, California, it is prohibited to sleep in a parked vehicle.
<li>In Cathedra City, California, persons may not ride their bycicles through the &quot;Fount of Life&quot;.
<li>In Cathedral City, California, one may not bring their dog to school.
<li>In Cerritos, California, all dog &quot;waste&quot; must be removed from any yard within seven days.
<li>In Chico, California, one must obtain a permit ffrom the city to throw hay in a cesspool.
<li>In Chico, California, it is illegal to own a green or smelly animal hide.
<li>In Chico, Claifornia, bowling on the sidewalk is illegal.
<li>Driving a herd of cattle down a street in Chico, California, is against the law.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*CAMBODIA*</pattern>
 <template>In Cambodia, water guns may not be used in New Year's celebrations.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*CANADA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Comic books which depict any illegal acts are banned in Canada.
<li>Businesses must provide rails for tying up horses in Canada.
<li>Wooden logs may not be painted in Canada.
<li>In Canada, you may never use dice to play craps.
<li>In Canada, if you are released from prison, it is required that you are given a handgun with bullets and a horse, so you can ride out of town.
<li>When raining, a person may not water his/her lawn in Canada.
<li>In Canada, it is illegal to turn right on a red light at any time.
<li>Margarine producers can't make their margarine yellow in Canada.
<li>All business signs in the province of Quebec must be in French.
<li>In Canada, 30 percent; of a radio station's content must be &quot;Canadian Content&quot;.
<li>The color of house and garage doors is regulated by city bylaws (a purple door gets you a fine) in Canada.
<li>In Canada, the city is classified as a no-pee zone.
<li>You can't work on your car in the street in Canada.
<li>In Canada, it's illegal to climb trees.
<li>In Canada, you may not pay for a fifty-cent item with only pennies.
<li>Citizens may not publicly remove bandages in Canada.
<li>In Canada, it is illegal for clear or non-dark sodas to contain caffeine.
<li>All business signs in the province of Quebec must be in French. If the business operator wishes to have English on the sign, the French must be at least twice as large as the English is. There are no laws governing the usage of other languages on signs. -Bill 101 (Passed in 1976)
<li>No language other than French is permitted to be shown out doors in Quebec.
<li>It is illegal to turn right on a red light at any time in Quebec.
<li>In Montréal, Quebec, you may not swear in French.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*CHINA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In China, persons may only bear one child or risk paying a substantial fine.
<li>In China, to go to college you must be intelligent.
<li>In China, drivers of power-driven vehicles who stop at pedestrian crossings are lizable to a fine of up to five yuan, or a warning.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*COLORADO*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Durango, Colorado, it is illegal to go out in public dressed in clothing &quot;unbecoming&quot; one's sex.
<li>In Logan County, Colorado, it is illegal for a man to kiss a woman while she is asleep.
<li>In Pueblo, Colorado, it is illegal to let a dandelion grow within city limits.
<li>In Colorado, one may not mutilate a rock in a state park.
<li>In Colorado, car dealers may not show cars on a Sunday.lIn Colorado, it is illegal for liquor stores to sell food, or grocery stores to sell any alcohol except beer that is at most 3 percent.
<li>No liquor may be sold on Sundays or election days in Colorado.
<li>It is illegal to ride a horse in Colorado while under the influence.
<li>Tags may be ripped off of pillows and mattresses in Colorado.
<li>Throwing missiles at cars is illegal in Alamosa, Colorado.
<li>In Alamosa, Colorado, keeping a house where unmarried persons are allowed to have sex is prohibited.
<li>To own a dog over three months of age in Alamosa, Colorado, one must obtain a license.
<li>Persons may not urinate in public in Alamosa, Colorado.
<li>In Arvada, Colorado, establishments which sell alcohol must have enough lighting to read text inside them.
<li>In Aspen, Colorado, catapults may not be fired at buildings.
<li>In Boulder, Colorado, it is legal to challenge a police officer, but only until he or she asks you to stop.
<li>In Boulder, Colorado, it is illegal to permit one's llama to graze on city property.
<li>Boulders may not be rolled on city property in Boulder, Colorado.
<li>Couches may not be placed on outside porches in Boulder, Colorado.
<li>In Colorado Springs, it is permissable to wear a holstered six-gun within city limits, except on Sunday, election days, or holidays.
<li>In Cripple Creek, Colorado, it is illegal to bring your horse or pack mule above the ground floor of any building.
<li>In Denver, Colorado, the dog catcher must notify dogs of impounding by posting, for 3 consecutive days, a notice on a tree in the city park and along a public road running through said park.
<li>In Denver, Colorado, it is unlawful to lend your vacuum cleaner to your next door neighbor.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*CONNECTICUT*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Hartford, Connecticut, it is illegal to educate a dog.
<li>It is illegal to dispose of used razor blades in Connecticut.
<li>In New Britain, Connecticut, the speed limit for fire trucks is 25 m.p.h., even when going to a fire.
<li>In Hartford, Connecticut, it is illegal for a man to kiss his wife on Sunday.
<li>In Connecticut, town records may not be kept where liquor is sold.
<li>You can be stopped by the police for biking over 65 mph in Connecticut.
<li>In Connecticut, in order for a pickle to officially be considered a pickle, it must bounce.
<li>You cannot buy any alcohol after 9 p.m., or after noon on Sunday in Connecticut.
<li>It is illegal to discharge a firearm from a public highway in Connecticut.
<li>In Devon, Connecticut, it is unlawful to walk backwards after sunset.
<li>In Guilford, Connecticut, only white Christmas lights are allowed for display.
<li>In Hartforfd, Connecticut, you are not allowed to cross a street while walking on your hands.
<li>In Rocky Hill, Connecticut, an arcade may not have more than a total of 4 amusement devices, such as ping-pong tables, pinball machines, or shuffleboard tables.
<li>In Southington, Connecticut, silly string is banned.
<li>In Waterbury, Connecticut, it is illegal for any beautician to hum, whistle, or sing while working on a customer.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*DELAWARE*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Lewes, Delaware, it is illegal to wear pants that are &quot;form-fitting&quot; around the waist.
<li>Getting married on a dare is grounds for an annulment in Delaware.
<li>In Delaware, it is illegal to fly over any body of water, unless one is carrying sufficient supplies of food and drink.
<li>In Delaware, R-rated movies may not be shown at drive-in theaters.
<li>In Rehoboth Beach, Delaware, no person shall change clothes in his or her vehicle.
<li>On Halloween in Rehoboth Beach, Delaware, children may only trick-or-treat from 6 p.m.-8 p.m., and if Halloween falls on a Sunday, they must trick-or-treat on October 30 during this same time interval.
<li>One may not whisper in church in Rehoboth Beach, Delaware.
<li>No person shall pretend to sleep on a bench or on the boardwalk in Rehoboth Beach, Delaware.
<li>Changing into or out of a bathing suit in a public restroom in Rehoboth Beach, Delaware, is prohibited.
<li>In Rehboth Beach, Delaware, 6 year-old girls may not run around without being fully clothed.
<li>In Rehoboth Beach, Delaware, alcohol may not be served in nightclubs if dancing is occurring on the premises at the same time.
<li>In South Bethany, Delaware, all persons must carry a bag with them at all times when they walk their dog in case said dog defecates, or risk a 100 dollar fine.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*DENMARK*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Denmark, before starting your car you are required to check lights, brakes, steering and honk your horn.
<li>In Denmark, if your vehicle stalls and you leave it on the side of the road, you must mark the vehicle with a red, reflecting triangle.
<li>In Denmark, if a horse drawn carriage is trying to pass a car and the horse becomes uneasy, the owner of the car is required to pull over and if necessary cover the car.
<li>In Denmark, attempt to escape from prison is not illegal, however, if one is caught he is required to serve out the remainder of his term.
<li>In Denmark, no one may start a car while someone is underneath the vehicle.
<li>In Denmark, headlights must be on whenever the vehicle is being operated in order to distinguish it from parked cars.
<li>In Denmark, when driving, you must have someone in front of your car with a flag to warn horse drawn carriages that a motorcar is coming.
<li>In Denmark, any carport added to a building increases the value of the building by 15.
<li>In Denmark, there is a penalty of 20kr for not reporting when a person has died.
<li>In Denmark, persons may not wear a mask.
<li>In Denmark, a fee is levied on each purchaser of any plastic bottle which is returned upon return of the bottle.
<li>In Denmark, one may not be charged for food at an inn unless that person, by his or her own opinion, is &quot;full&quot;.
<li>In Denmark, restaurants may not charge for water unless it is accompanied by another item such as ice or a lemon slice.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*DUMB LAWS*|*LAW*|* LAWS *|* CRAZY LAWS *|* STUPID LAW*</pattern>
 <template>I know a ton of US laws by state (just say the name of the state whose moronic laws you'd like me to recite), and I also know some idiotic international laws for the following places:<p>Thailand,Turkey, Philippines, Switzerland, Sweden, South Korea, Singapore, United Kingdom, Norway, Cambodiia, Netherlands, Morocco, Mexico, Japan, Italy, Australia, Greece, Belgium, Canada, China, Denmark, France, Germany, Ireland, Israel, South Africa, Swaziland, Zimbabwe, and Finland.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*FINLAND*</pattern>
 <template>In Finland, taxi drivers must pay royalties if they play music in their cars for paying customers.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*FLORIDA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Miami, Florida, it is illegal for a man to wear any kind of strapless gown.
<li>In Sarasota, Florida, it is illegal to sing while wearing a bathing suit.
<li>In Florida, it is illegal for single, divorced, or widowed women to parachute on Sunday afternoons.
<li>In Florida, the state constitution allows for freedom of speech, a trial by jury, and pregnant pigs not to be confined in cages.
<li>One may not commit any &quot;unnatural acts&quot; with another person in Florida.
<li>In Florida, unmarried couples may not commit &quot;lewd acts&quot; and live together at the same residence.
<li>Corrupting the public morals in Florida is defined as a nuisance, and is declared a misdemeanor offense.
<li>Doors of all public buildings in Florida must open outwards.
<li>It is illegal to sell your children in Florida.
<li>Women may be fined for falling asleep under a hair dryer, as can the salon owner in Florida.
<li>If an elephant is left tied to a parking meter in Florida, the parking fee has to be paid just as it would for a vehicle.
<li>Having sexual relations with a porcupine is illegal in Florida.
<li>It is illegal to skateboard without a license in Florida.
<li>When having sex in Florida, only the missionary position is legal.
<li>You may not fart in a public place after 6 p.m. in Florida.
<li>It is considered an offense to shower naked in Florida.
<li>You are not allowed to break more than 3 dishes per day, or chip the edges of more than 4 cups and/or saucers in Florida.
<li>Oral sex is illegal in Florida.
<li>You may not kiss your wife's breasts in Florida.
<li>Penalty for horse theft in Florida is death by hanging.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*FRANCE*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In France, between the hours of 8 a.m. and 8 p.m., 70 percent of music on the radio must be by French artists.
<li>In France, it is illegal to kiss on railways in France.
<li>In France, no pig may be addressed as Napoleon by its owner.
<li>In France, it is illegal to take photos of police officers or police vehicles, even if they are just in the background.
<li>In France, it is forbidden without a cemetery plot to die on the territory of the commune.
<li>In France, an ashtray is considered to be a deadly weapon.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*GEORGIA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>All males in the state of Georgia between the ages of 16 and 50 are required to work on public roads.
<li>In Columbus, Georgia, it is illegal to sit on one's porch in an indecent position.
<li>In Quitman, Georgia, it is illegal for a chicken to cross a road.
<li>It is illegal to change the clothes on a storefront mannequin unless the shades are down in Georgia.
<li>It is a misdemeanor in Georgia for any citizen to attend church worship on Sunday unless he is equipped with a rifle and it is loaded.
<li>Jonesboro, Georgia: Forbidden to say &quot;Oh, boy&quot;.
<li>In Georgia, if an organization not registered as non-profit fails to register their raffle with the local sheriff, that group risks paying up to 10,000 dollars in fines and spending 5 years in jail.
<li>While Georgia operates its own lottery, it protects its citizens by making it illegal to promote a private lottery.
<li>The term &quot;sadomasochistic abuse&quot; is defined so broadly in Georgia that it could possibly be applied to a person handcuffing another in a clown suit.
<li>All sex toys are banned in Georgia.
<li>It is illegal to use profanity in front of a dead body which lies in a funeral home or in a coroner's office in Georgia.
<li>In Georgia, members of the state assembly cannot be ticketed for speeding while the state assembly is in session.
<li>In Georgia, donkeys may not be kept in bathtubs.
<li>Signs are required to be written in English in Georgia.
<li>In Georgia, no one may carry an ice cream cone in their back pocket if it is Sunday.
<li>In Acworth, Georgia, all citizens must own a rake.
<li>In Athens-Clarke County, Georgia, adult book stores may not sell alcohol.
<li>In Athens-Clarke County, Georgia, if you want to read your favorite book in public to your friends, do it before 2:45 a.m.
<li>
<li>In Athens-Clarke County, Georgia, massage businesses may not sell alcohol on the side.
<li>In Athens-Clarke County, Georgia, selling two beers at once for the same price is not allowed.
<li>In Georgia, though being forced to close your business is bad enough, Athens-Clarke County forces one to obtain a license before holding a going-out-of-business sale.
<li>In Athens-Clarke County, Georgia, goldfish may not be given away to entice someone to enter a game of bingo.
<li>In Athens-Clarke County, Georgia, owners of mules may not allow their animal to roam around unsupervised.
<li>In Athens-Clarke County, Georgia, persons under the age of 16 may not play pinball after 11 p.m.
<li>In Athens-Clarke County, Georgia, it is illegal for one to make a disturbing sound at a fair.
<li>In Athens-Clarke County, Georgia, it is illegal for one to whistle very loud after 11 p.m. on Mondays.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*GERMANY*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Germany, every office must have a view of the sky, however small.
<li>In Germany, a pillow can be considered a &quot;passive&quot; weapon.
<li>In Germany, it is illegal to wear a mask.
<li>In Germany, it is illegal for one's car to run out of gas on the Autobahn.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*GREECE*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Greece, all electronic games are banned.
<li>In Greece, one could not wear a hat in the Olympic Stadium in ancient times as it would obstruct someone's view.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*HAWAII*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>It is illegal to appear in public wearing only swimming trunks in Hawaii.
<li>It is illegal to own a mongoose without a permit in Hawaii.
<li>It's against the law for a person to insert pennies in the ear in Hawaii.
<li>In Hawaii, billboards are outlawed.
<li>In Hawaii, all residents may be fined as a result of not owning a boat.
<li>
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*IDAHO*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Pocatello, Idaho, &quot;the carrying of concealed weapons is forbidden, unless same are exhibited to public view.&quot;
<li>Also in Pocatello, Idaho, &quot;It is prohibited for pedestrians and motorists to display frowns, grimaces, scowls, threatening and glowering looks, gloomy and depressed facial appearances, generally all of which reflect unfavorably upon the city's reputation.&quot;
<li>In Idaho, boxes of candy given as romantic gifts must weigh more than 50 pounds!
<li>It's safe to make love while parked in Coeur d'Alene, Idaho. Police officers aren't allowed to walk up and knock on the window.
<li>Any suspicious officer who thinks that sex is taking place must drive up from behind, honk his horn three times and wait approximately two minutes before getting out of his car to investigate.
<li>In Idaho, you may not fish on a camel's back.
<li>Riding a merry-go-round on Sundays in Idaho is considered a crime.
<li>In Boise, Idaho, residents may not fish from a giraffe's back.
<li>In Eagle, Idaho, dirt may not be swept from one's house into the street.
<li>In Eagle, Idaho, bicycles are not allowed in the tennis courts.
<li>In Eagle, Idaho, persons may not camp out on sidewalks in the city.
<li>In Pocatello, Idaho, a person may not be seen in public without a smile on their face.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*ILLINOIS*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Chicago, Illinois, people who are diseased, maimed, mutilated, or deformed to the point of being &quot;an unsightly or disgusting object&quot; are banned from going out in public.
<li>In Chicago, Illisnoise, it is illegal to fish in one's pajamas.
<li>In Chicago, Illinois, it is illegal to take a French poodle to the opera.
<li>According to Illinois state law, it is illegal to speak English. The officially recognized language is &quot;American.&quot;
<li>In Guernee, Illinois, it is illegal for women weighing more than 200 pounds to ride horses in shorts.
<li>In Joliet, Illinois, it is illegal to mispronounce the name Joliet.
<li>A state law in Illinois mandates that all bachelors should be called master, not mister, when addressed by their female counterparts.
<li>In Oblong, Illinois, it's punishable by law to make love while hunting or fishing on your wedding day.
<li>You may be arrested for vagrancy in Illinois if you do not have at least one dollar bill on your person.
<li>You must contact the police before entering the city in an automobile in Illinois.
<li>In Carbondale, Illinois, no one may stand on the sidewalk on the 500th block.
<li>In Champaign, Illinois, one may not pee in his neighbor's mouth.
<li>In Chicago, Illinois, all businesses entering into contracts with the city must sift through their records and report any business they had dealing with slaves during the era of slavery.
<li>Law forbids eating in a place that is on fire in Chicago, Illinois.
<li>It is illegal to give a dog whiskey in Chicago, Illinois.
<li>In Chicago, Illinois, it is forbidden to fish while sitting on a giraffe's neck.
<li>Kites may not be flown within the city limits of Chicago, Illinois.
<li>In the Pullman area, it is illegal to drink beer out of a bucket while sitting on the curb.
<li>It is legal to protest naked in front of city hall as long as you are under 17 years of age and have legal permits in Illinois.
<li>In Cicero, Illinois, humming on public streets is prohibited on Sundays.
<li>In Crete, Illinois, it is considered an offense to attempt to have sex with one's dog.
<li>Cars may not be driven through the town in Crete, Illinois.
<li>In Crystal Lake, Illinois, if one wishes to plant new sod in his or her yard in the summer months, that person may not use the city's water to water it.
<li>In Des Plaines, Illinois, wheelbarrows iwth &quot;for sale&quot; signs may not be chained to trees.
<li>In Evanston, Illinois, bowling is forbidden.
<li>In Evanston, Illinois, it is unlawful to change clothes in an automobile with the curtains drawn, except in case of fire.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*INDIANA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Monkeys are forbidden to smoke cigarettes in South Bend, Indiana.
<li>In Gary, Indiana, it is illegal to attend the theater within four hours of eating garlic.
<li>The Stepford Wives is banned in Warsaw, Indiana.
<li>In Indiana, waitresses may not carry drinks into a restaurant or bar.
<li>In Indiana, hotel sheets must be exactly 99 inches long and 81 inches wide.
<li>In Indiana, if any person has a puppet show, wire dancing or tumbling act and receives money for it, they will be fined 3 dollars under the Act to Prevent Certain Immoral Practices.
<li>A 3 dollar fine per pack will be imposed on anyone playing cards in Indiana under the Act for the Prevention of Gaming.
<li>In Indiana, nyone 14 or older who profanely curses, damns or swears by the name of God, Jesus Christ or the Holy Ghost, shall be fined 1-3 dollars for each offense, with a maximum fine of 10 dollars per day in Indiana.
<li>The value of Pi is 3 in Indiana.
<li>In Indiana, it is illegal for a man to be sexually aroused in public.
<li>In Indiana, one may not sniff glue.
<li>In Indiana, a person must get a referral from a licensed physician if he or she wishes to see a hypnotist unless the desired procedure is to quit smoking or lose weight.
<li>In Indiana, baths may not be taken between the months of October and March.
<li>In Indiana, it is illegal to sell cars on Sunday.
<li>In Indiana, oral sex is illegal.
<li>In Indiana, a man over the age of 18 may be arrested for statutory rape if the passenger in his car is not wearing her socks and shoes, and is under the age of 17.
<li>In Indiana, it is against the law to pass a horse on the street.
<li>In Indiana, it is illegal for a liquor store to sell cold soft drinks.
<li>In Indiana, liquor stores may not sell milk.
<li>In Indiana, grocery stores may not sell any type of cold liquor.
<li>In Indiana, you can get ouf of paying for a dependent's medical care by praying for him/her.
<li>In Indiana, one may not back into a parking spot because it prevents police officers from seeing the license plate.
<li>In Indiana, smoking in the state legislature building is banned, except when the legislature is in session.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*IOWA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>State law in Iowa forbids any establishment from charging admission to see a one-armed piano player.
<li>In Fort Madison, Iowa, firemen are required to practice for 15 minutes before attending a fire.
<li>In Ames, Iowa, warn your hubby that after lovemaking, he isn't allowed to take more than three gulps of beer while lying in bed with you/holding you in his arms.
<li>In Iowa, it is a violation of the law to sell or distribute drugs or narcotics without having first obtained the appropriate Iowa drug tax stamp.
<li>In Iowa, a man with a moustache may never kiss a woman in public.
<li>In Iowa, one-armed piano players must perform for free.
<li>In Iowa, kisses may last no more than five minutes.
<li>In Iowa, tanning bed facilites must warn of the risk of getting a sunburn.
<li>In Iowa, a board was created to regulate, among other things, hearing aids.
<li>In Iowa, ministers must obtain a permit to carry their liquor across state lines.
<li>In Iowa, doctors who treat a person with gonorrhea must report this to the local board of health and include the disease's &quot;probable origin&quot;.
<li>In Iowa, all boxes used to pick hops must be exactly 36 inches long.
<li>In Bettendorf, Iowa, liquor stores may not place advertisements for beer outside the store.
<li>In Cedar Rapids, Iowa, it is illegal to read persons' palms in the city limits.
<li>In Dubuque, Iowa, any hotel in the city limits must have a water bucket and a hitching post in front of the building.
<li>In Indianola, Iowa, the ice cream man and his truck are banned.
<li>In Marshalltown, Iowa, horses are forbidden to eat fire hydrants.
<li>In Mount Vernon, Iowa, one must obtain written permission from the City Council before throwing bricks into a highway.
<li>In Mount Vernon, Iowa, no person may pick a flower from a city park.
<li>In Mount Vernon, Iowa, all softball diamond lights must be turned off by 10:30 p.m.
<li>In Ottumwa, Iowa, a man may not wink at any woman he does not know within the city limits.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*IRELAND*</pattern>
 <template>In Ireland, any person who shall pretend or exercise to use any type of witchcraft, sorcery, enchantment, or pretend knowledge in any occult or or craft or science shall for any such offense suffer imprisonment at the time of one whole year and also shall be obliged to obscursion for his/her good behavior.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*ISRAEL*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Israel, bicycles may not be ridden without a license.
<li>In Israel, raising a pig on Israeli soil will result in the murder of said pig.
<li>In Israel, if you have been maintaining an illegal radio station for five or more years, the station becomes legal.In Israel, it is against the law to feed animals in public places.In Israel, it is considered an offense to operate a mobile spay/neuter clinic; it is considered peddling.In Israel, it is forbidden to bring bears to the beach.In Israel, no loud voices or big lights are allowed during weekends.In Israel, the raising of Rotweiller dogs is prohibited.In Israel, picking one's nose on the Sabbath is illegal.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*ITALY*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Italy, it is illegal to practice the profession of charlantry.
<li>In Italy, a man may be arrested for wearing a skirt.
<li>In Italy, striking someone with a fist is considered a felony.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*JAPAN*</pattern>
 <template>In Japan, there is no age of consent.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*KANSAS*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>It is illegal for restaurants to sell cherry pie a la mode on Sundays in Kansas.
<li>In Wichita, Kansas, a man's mistreatment of his mother-in-law may not be used as grounds for divorce.
<li>In Wichita, Kansas, it is illegal to carry a concealed bean snapper.
<li>In Lang, Kansas, it is illegal to ride a mule down Main Street in August, unless the animal is wearing a straw hat.
<li>In Natoma, Kansas, it is illegal to throw a knife at anyone wearing a striped shirt.
<li>Rabbits may not be shot from motorboats in Kansas.
<li>In Kansas, pedestrians crossing the highways at night must wear tail lights.
<li>No one may catch fish with his bare hands in Kansas.
<li>The state game rule in Kansas prohibits the use of mules to hunt ducks.
<li>If two trains meet on the same track in Kansas, neither shall proceed until the other has passed.
<li>In Derby, Kansas, it is illegal to urinate on the side of a building.
<li>In Derby, Kansas, hitting a vending machine that stole your money is illegal.
<li>Persons may not screech their tires while driving in Derby, Kansas.
<li>Riding an animal down any road is against the law in Derby, Kansas.
<li>In Dodge City, Kansas, it is illegal to spit on a sidewalk.
<li>In Lawrence, Kansas, all cars entering the city limits must first sound their horn to warn the horses of their arrival.
<li>In lawrence, Kansas, no one may wear a bee in their hat.
<li>In Overland Park, Kansas, one may not picket a funeral.
<li>In Russell, Kansas, musical car horns are banned.
<li>In Salina, Kansas, it is against the law to leave your car running unattended.
<li>In Topeka, Kansas, it is illegal to drive one's car through a parade.
<li>In Topeka, Kansas, there are laws to force citizens to keep their yards in decent shape.
<li>In Topeka, Kansas, no one may sing the alphabet on the streets at night.
<li>In Topeka, Kansas, spitting on sidewalks is expressly forbidden.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*KENTUCKY*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>State law in Kentucky stipulates that a person is considered sober until he or she &quot;cannot hold onto the ground.&quot;
<li>It is illegal to remarry the same man four times in Kentucky.
<li>An excerpt from brilliant Kentucky state legislation: &quot;No female shall appear in a bathing suit on any highway within this state unless she be escorted by at least two officers or unless she be armed with a club.&quot; The following important amendment however is to be considered here: &quot;The provisions of this statute shall not apply to females weighing less than 90 pounds nor exceeding 200 pounds, nor shall it apply to male horses.&quot;
<li>In Kentucky, throwing eggs at a public speaker could result in up to one year in prison.
<li>One may not dye a duckling blue in Kentucky and offer it for sale unless more than six are for sale at once.
<li>It is illegal to fish with a bow and arrow in Kentucky.
<li>In Fort Thomas, Kentucky, dogs may not molest cars.
<li>One may not receive anal sex in Owensboro, Kentucky.
<li>In Owensboro, Kentucky, a woman may not buy a hat without her husband's permission.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*LOUISIANA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In New Orleans, fire trucks are required by law to stop at all red lights.
<li>It is considered &quot;simple assault&quot; to bite someone in New Orleans; it is &quot;aggravated assault&quot; if the biter has false teeth.
<li>In Louisiana, it is against the law to gargle in public.
<li>In Louisiana, &quot;fake&quot; wrestling matches are prohibited.
<li>In Louisiana, spectators at a boxing match may not mock one of the contestants.
<li>In Louisiana, one could possibly land in jail for 20 years upon urinating in the city's water supply.
<li>In Louisiana, a law was passed with the specific intent of stating the punishment for stealing crawfish.
<li>Persons could land in jail for up to ten years for stealing an alligator in Louisiana.
<li>In Louisiana, it is a $500 fine to instruct a pizza delivery man to deliver a pizza to your friend without them knowing.
<li>In Louisiana, running an abortion advertisement can land you in jail for a year.
<li>In Louisiana, it is illegal to rob a bank and then shoot at the bank teller with a water pistol.
<li>In Louisiana, it is illegal to shoot lasers at police officers.
<li>In Louisiana, one may not date another to go onto railroad tracks owned by another.
<li>In Louisiana, rituals that involve the ingestion of blood, urine, or fecal matter are not allowed.
<li>In Louisiana, one could land in jail for up to a year for making a false promise.
<li>In Louisiana, every time a person is seriously burned, he must report the injury to the fire marshal.
<li>In Louisiana, prisoners who hurt themselves could serve an additional two years in jail.
<li>In Jefferson Parish, Lousiana, minors may not go into businesses with coin operated foosball machines unless accompanied by an adult.
<li>In Jefferson Parish, Lousiana, no one may pour a drink out on the ground at any drive-in movie.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*MAINE*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Portland, Maine, it is illegal for men to tickle women under the chin with feather dusters.
<li>The most money one can legally win gambling in Maine is $3.
<li>In Rumford, Maine, it is illegal for a tenant to bite his/her landlord.
<li>In Waterville, Maine, it is illegal to blow one's nose in public.
<li>In Maine, shotguns are required to be taken to church in the event of a Native American attack.
<li>In Maine, you may not step out of a plane in flight.
<li>In Maine, after January 14th you will be charged a fine for having your Christmas decorations still up.
<li>In Augusta, Maine, to stroll down the street playing a violin is against the law.
<li>It is illegal to gamble at the airport in Biddeford, Maine.
<li>In Biddeford, Maine, no person may rollerskate on a sidewalk.
<li>In Ellsworth, Maine, if any part of the sign ordinances of the city are more stringent than federal laws, even though they may be in conflict with them, they will prevail.
<li>In Freeport, Maine, mercury thermometers may not be sold in the city.
<li>In Freeport, Maine, it is illegal to expectorate from any second story window.
<li>In South Berwick, Maine, it is illegal to park in front of Dunkin Donuts.
<li>In Watersboro, Maine, dog leashes may not be over eight feet in length.
<li>In Wells, Maine, deer may not be fed.
<li>Advertisements may not be placed in cemeteries in Wells, Maine.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*MARYLAND*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Baltimore, Maryland, it is illegal to wash or scrub sinks, no matter how dirty they get.
<li>In Maine, every person who has bowled since 1833 may be fined 2 dollars for each offense.
<li>In Halethorpe, Maine, it is illegal to kiss for more than one second.
<li>It's illegal to mistreat oysters in Maine.
<li>It's illegal to play Randy Newman's &quot;Short People&quot; on the radio in Maine.
<li>Oral sex cannot be given or received anywhere in Maryland.
<li>Thistles may not grow in one's yard in Maryland.
<li>In Baltimore, Maryland, it is illegal to throw bales of hay from a second story window within the city limits.
<li>It's illegal to take a lion to the movies in Baltimore, Maryland.
<li>In Baltimore, Maryland, it is a park rule violation to be in a public park with a sleeveless shirt.
<li>No person who is a tramp or a vagrant shall loiter in any park at any time in Baltimore, Maryland.
<li>It is a violation of city code in Baltimore, Maryland, to sell chicks or ducklings to a minor within 1 week of the Easter holiday.
<li>Though you may spit on a city roadway in Baltimore City, spitting on city sidewalks is prohibited.
<li>You may not curse inside the city limits of Baltimore City, Maryland.
<li>In Cumberland, Maryland, it is illegal to use profane language on a playground.
<li>Knocking stones into a public park in Cumberland, Maryland, is prohibited.
<li>In Rockville, Maryland, persons may not swear while on the highway.
<li>In Rockville, Maryland, it is illegal to remove a public building by writing on it.
<li>Citizens may not swim in the public fountains within the city limits of Rockville, Maryland.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*MASSACHUSETTS*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Salem, Massachusetts, even married couples are forbidden from sleeping in the nude in rented rooms.
<li>It is illegal to wear a goatee without a license in Massachusetts.
<li>North Andover prohibits its citizens from carrying &quot;space guns.&quot;
<li>State legislation forbids dueling with water pistols.
<li>In Boston, it is illegal to take a bath unless one has been ordered by a physician to do so.
<li>In 1659, the state of Massachusetts outlawed Christmas.
<li>In Massachusetts, mourners at a wake may not eat more than three sandwiches.
<li>Taxi drivers are prohibited from making love in the front seat of their taxi during their shifts in Massachusetts.
<li>In Massachusetts, all men must carry a rifle to church on Sunday.
<li>No gorilla is allowed in the back seat of any car in Massachusetts.
<li>Alcoholic drink specials are illegal in Massachusetts.
<li>In Massachusetts, it is forbidden to put tomatoes in clam chowder.
<li>Cooling one's feet by hanging them out the window is forbidden in Massachusetts.
<li>Law declares that peanuts may not be eaten in court in Massachusetts.
<li>Snoring is illegal in Massachusetts unless all bedroom windows are closed and securely locked.
<li>It is illegal to give beer to hospital patients in Massachusetts.
<li>In Massachusetts, candy may not contain more than 1 percent of alcohol.
<li>Shooting ranges may not set up targets that resemble human beings in Massachusetts.
<li>In Massachusetts, mourners may eat no more than three sandwiches at a wake.
<li>Hunting on Sundays is prohibited in Massachusetts.
<li>In Massachusetts, a woman cannot be on top during sexual activities.
<li>Tattooing and body piercing is illegal in Massachusetts.
<li>Children may smoke in Massachusetts, but they may not purchase cigarettes.
<li>Quakers and witches are banned from Massachusetts.
<li>Bullets may not be used as currency in Massachusetts.
<li>Massachusetts liquor stores can only open on Sundays if they are in Berkshire, Essex, Franklin, Middlesex or Worcester Counties and are within 10 miles of the Vermont or New Hampshire borders.
<li>Public boxing matches are outlawed in Massachusetts.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*MEXICO*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Mexico, clergymen may not wear their religious garb in public.
<li>In Mexico, boneshakers, safety bicycles, and any other similar machines are banned from the center of town.
<li>In Mexico, bicycle riders may not lift either foot from the peddles, as it might result in a loss of control.
<li>In Mexico, during Holy Week, no horses or wheeled transport is allowed in the city.
<li>In Mexico, no fireworks may be thrown by hand during Holy Week.
<li>In Mexico, all males must wear trousers, and such groups of employees as hack drivers and newspaper delivery boys must adopt uniforms.
<li>In Mexico, women who work for the government of the city of Guadalajara may not wear miniskirts or any other &quot;provocative&quot; garment during office hours.
<li>In Mexico, it is illegal to shout offensive words in any public place.
<li>In Mexico, any kind of nude artistic display is illegal.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*MICHIGAN*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Clawson, Michigan, it is legal for a farmer to &quot;sleep with his pigs, cows, horses, goats, and chickens.&quot;
<li>A state law in Michigan stipulates that a woman's hair legally belongs to her husband.
<li>In Detroit, it is illegal to make love in a car unless it is parked on your property.
<li>In Detroit, it is illegal to &quot;ogle&quot; a woman from a moving car.
<li>In Port Huron, Michigan, the speed limit for ambulances is 20 m.p.h.
<li>Under state law in Michigan, dentists are officially classified as &quot;mechanics.&quot;
<li>In Michigan, a woman isn't allowed to cut her own hair without her husband's permission.
<li>Persons may not be drunk on trains in Michigan.
<li>It is illegal to kill a dog using a decompression chamber in Michigan.
<li>Adultery is illegal in Michigan, but can only be punished upon a complaint by the affected wife or husband.
<li>No man may seduce and corrupt an unmarried girl, or else he risks 5 years in prison in Michigan.
<li>In Michigan, the last Sunday in June of every year was named &quot;Log Cabin Day&quot;.
<li>Cars may not be sold on Sunday in Michigan.
<li>There is a three cent bounty for each starling and ten cent bounty for each crow killed in any village, township, or city in the state of Michigan.
<li>It is legal for a robber to file a lawsuit if he or she was hurt in your house in Michigan.
<li>You may not swear in front of women and children in Michigan.
<li>Any person over the age of 12 in Michigan may have a license for a handgun as long as s/he has not been convicted of a felony.
<li>Putt-putt golf courses must be closed by 1 a.m. in Detroit, Michigan.
<li>Security guards at Joe Louis Arena will confiscate any item they feel might be thrown onto the ice in Detroit, Michigan.
<li>In Detroit, Michigan, willfully destroying your old radio is prohibited.
<li>It is illegal for a man to scowl at his wife on Sunday in Detroit, Michigan.
<li>In Detroit, Michigan, it is illegal to let your pig run free unless it has a ring in its nose.
<li>In Grand Haven, Michigan, no person shall throw an abandoned hoop skirt into any street or on any sidewalk, under penalty of a 5 dollar fine for each offense.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*MINNESOTA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Minnesota, women may face up to 30 days in jail if they impersonate Santa Claus.
<li>In Minneapolis, Minnesota, double-parkers can be put on a chain gang.
<li>Every man in Brainerd, Minnesota,  is required by law to grow a beard.
<li>It's illegal to tease skunks in Minnesota.
<li>In Alexandria, Minnesota, no man is allowed to make love to his wife with the smell of garlic, onions, or sardines on his breath. If his wife so requests, law mandates that he must brush his teeth.
<li>In Blue Earth, Minnesota, law declares that no child under the age of 12 may talk over the telephone unless accompanied by a parent.
<li>In Minnesota, the land of 10,000 lakes declares mosquitos a public nuisance.
<li>In Minnesota, it is illegal to stand around any building without a good reason to be there.
<li>A person may not cross state lines with a duck atop his head in Minnesota.
<li>It is illegal to sleep naked in Minnesota.
<li>All men driving motorcycles in Minnesota must wear shirts.
<li>In Minnesota, a citizen may not enter Wisconsin with a chicken on their head.
<li>Oral sex is prohibited in Minnesota.
<li>All bathtubs must have feet in Minnesota.
<li>In Cottage Grove, Minnesota, airplanes may not be landed in city parks.
<li>In Cottage Grove, Minnesota, residents of even numbered addresses may not water their plants on odd numbered days excluding the 31 day where it applies.
<li>In Hibbing, Minnesota, it shall be the duty of any policeman or any other officer to enforce the provisions of this section, and if any cat is found running at large, or which is found in any street, alley or public place, it shall be the duty of any policeman or other officer of the city to kill such cat.
<li>In Minneapolis, Minnesota, red cars may not drive down Lake Street.
<li>Driving a truck with dirty tires in Minnetonka, Minnesota, is considered a public nuisance.
<li>Placing tacks on a sidewalk in Minnetonka, Minnesota, is considered a public nuisance.
<li>Any person who persuades another to enter a massage therapist business after 11 p.m. in Minnetonka, Minnesota, is guilty of a misdemeanor.
<li>In St. Cloud, Minnesota, hamburgers may not be eaten on Sundays.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*MISSISSIPPI*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Mississippi, it is still legal to kill one's &quot;servant.&quot;
<li>In Truro, Mississippi, a would-be groom must &quot;prove himself manly&quot; prior to marriage by hunting and killing either six blackbirds or three crows.
<li>It is illegal to teach others what polygamy is in Mississippi.
<li>In Mississippi, a man may not seduce a woman by lying, and claiming he will marry her.
<li>In Mississippi, adultery or fornication (living togeather while not married or having sex with someone that is not your spouse) results in a fine of 500 dollars and/or 6 months in prison.
<li>If one is a parent of two illegitimate children in Mississippi, that person will go to jail for at least one month.
<li>In Mississippi, no one may bribe any athlete to rig a game, match, tournament, etc.
<li>In Mississippi, one may be fined up to 100 dollars for using profane language in public areas.
<li>In Mississippi, cattle rustling is punishable by hanging.
<li>Horses are not to be housed within 50 feet of any road in Mississippi.
<li>Vagrancy in Mississippi is punishable by either 30 days in prison or a 250 dollar fine.
<li>Unnatural intercourse, if both parties voluntarily participate, results in a maximum sentence of 10 years at 10,000 dollar in Mississippi.
<li>It is illegal for a man to be sexually aroused in public in Mississippi.
<li>In Ridgeland, Mississippi, it is unlawful for anyone to have sex in public.
<li>In Ridgeland, Mississippi, exterior burglar bars which are viewable from the street are not allowed.
<li>In Tylertown, Mississippi, it is unlawful to shave in the center of Main Street.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*MISSOURI*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Saco, Missouri, women are forbidden from wearing hats that &quot;might frighten timid persons, children or animals.&quot;
<li>In St. Louis, Missouri, it is illegal for an on-duty firefighter to rescue a woman wearing a nightgown; in order to be rescued, a woman must be fully dressed.
<li>While children may purchase shotguns in Kansas City, Missouri, they are not allowed to buy toy cap guns.
<li>Missouri considers drunkenness an &quot;inalienable right.&quot;
<li>In Merryville, Missouri, women are prohibited from wearing corsets because &quot;The privilege of admiring the curvaceous, unencumbered body of a young woman should not be denied to the normal, red-blooded American male.&quot;
<li>In St. Louis, Missouri, it is illegal to sit on the curb of any city street and drink beer from a bucket.
<li>It is illegal to have oral sex in Missouri.
<li>Single men between the ages of 21 and 50 must pay an annual tax of one dollar in Missouri (enacted 1820).
<li>It is not illegal to speed in Missouri.
<li>In Buckner, Missouri, yard waste may be burned any day except Sunday.
<li>In Columbia, Missouri, you cannot have an antenna exposed outside of your house, yet you can have a 25 foot satellite dish.
<li>In Columbia, Missouri, though clotheslines are banned, clothes may be draped over a fence.
<li>One may not drink in a bar between 2 a.m. and 6 a.m. in Columbia, Missouri.
<li>In Kansas City, Missouri, installation of bathtubs with four legs resembling animal claws is prohibited.
<li>In Marceline, Missouri, minors can buy rolling paper and tobacco but not lighters.
<li>In Marquette, Missouri, it is illegal for more than four unrelated persons to occupy the same dwelling (The Brothel Law).
<li>In Mole, Missouri, frightening a baby is in violation of the law.
<li>In Natchez, Missouri, it shall be unlawful to provide beer or other intoxicants to elephants.
<li>In Purdy, Missouri, dancing is strictly prohibited.
<li>In St. Louis, Missouri, a milkman may not run while on duty.
<li>In University City, Missouri, four women may not rent an apartment together.
<li>In University City, Missouri, no person may own a PVC pipe.
<li>In University City, no person may have a yard sale in their front yard.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*MONTANA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>It is a felony for a wife to open her husband's mail in Montana.
<li>In Montana, it is a misdemeanor to show movies that depict acts of felonious crime.
<li>In Whitehall, Montana, it is illegal to operate a vehicle with ice picks attached to the wheels.
<li>Bozeman, Montana, has a law that bans all sexual activity between members of the opposite sex in the front yard of a home after sundown -- if they're nude.
<li>A law in Helena, Montana, mandates that a woman can't dance on a table in a saloon or bar unless she has on at least three pounds, two ounces of clothing.
<li>In Montana, prostitution is considered a &quot;crime against the family&quot;.
<li>In Montana, one may not pretend to abuse an animal in the presence of a minor.
<li>In Montana, it is illegal to have a sheep in the cab of your truck without a chaperone.
<li>In Montana, it is a misdemeanor to show movies that depict acts of felonious crime.
<li>In Montana, it is illegal for married women to go fishing alone on Sundays, and illegal for unmarried women to fish alone at all.
<li>In Montana, it is illegal for a man and a woman to have sex in any other position than missionary style.
<li>In Montana, 7+ indians are considered a raiding/war party and it is legal to shoot them.In Billings, Montana, no person shall raise pet rats.
<li>In Billings, Montana, persons in possession of a pea shooter risk it being confiscated by police.
<li>In Billings, Montana, it is illegal to bring a bomb or rocket at city council proceedings.
<li>In Billings, Montana, bands who play in clubs where alcohol is served may not leave the stage while performing.
<li>In Billings, Montana, it is illegal to use speed dial in the city phone system.
<li>In Excelsior Springs, Montana, hard objects may not be thrown by hand.
<li>
<li>In Excelsior Springs, Montana, worrying squirrels will not be tolerated.
<li>In Excelsior Springs, Montana, balls may not be thrown within the city limits.
<li>In Helena, Montana, it is illegal to annoy passersby on sidewalks with a revolving water sprinkler.
<li>In Helena, Montana, the game of &quot;folf&quot; may not be played at night.
<li>In Helena, Montana, no items may be thrown across a street.
<li>In Kalispell, Montana, all pool tables must be able to be viewed from the street outside a billiard hall where they are located.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*MOROCCO*</pattern>
 <template>In Morocco, anyone in company with someone who possesses narcotics, even if they are unaware that their companion has them, can be tried for the same crime.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*NEBRASKA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>It is illegal for a mother to give her daughter a perm without a state license in Nebraska.
<li>In Waterloo, Nebraska, barbers are forbidden from eating onions between 7 a.m. and 7 p.m.
<li>In Omaha, Nebraska, barbers are forbidden to shave their customers' chests.
<li>If a child burps during a church service in Omaha, his or her parents may be arrested.
<li>It is illegal for bar owners to sell beer unless they are simultaneously brewing a kettle of soup in Nebraska.
<li>The owner of every hotel in Hastings, Nebraska, is required to provide each guest with a clean and pressed nightshirt.
<li>In Nebraska, no couple, even if they are married, may sleep together in the nude. Nor may they have sex unless they are wearing a clean, white cotton nightshirt.
<li>In Nebraska, persons with gonorrhea may not marry.
<li>In Nebraska, it is illegal to fly a plane while drunk.
<li>In Nebraska, it is illegal to go whale fishing.
<li>In Lehigh, Nebraska, doughnut holes may not be sold.
<li>In Omaha, Nebraska, sneezing or burping is illegal during a church service.
<li>In Omaha, Nebraska, a man is not allowed to run around with a shaved chest.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*NETHERLANDS*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In the Netherlands, it is illegal to smoke pot, buy it, or have less than 5 grams with you.
<li>In the Netherlands, prostitution is legal but the prostitutes must pay taxes like any other business.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*NEVADA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Nyala, Nevada, a man is forbidden from buying drinks for more than three people other than himself at any one period during the day.
<li>It is illegal to drive a camel on the highway in Nevada.
<li>In Eureka, Nevada, men who wear moustaches are forbidden from kissing women.
<li>Everyone walking on the streets of Elko, Nevada, is required to wear a mask.
<li>In Nevada, sex without a condom is illegal.
<li>It's still legal to hang someone for shooting your dog on your property in Nevada.
<li>In Clark County, Nevada, an ordinance makes bringing a concealable firearm into the county illegal unless it is registered with the Las Vegas Metropolitan Police Department.
<li>In Reno, Nevada, it is illegal to lie down on the sidewalk.
<li>In Reno, Nevada, benches may not be placed in the middle of any street.
<li>In Reno, Nevada, sex toys are outlawed.
<li>
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*NEW BRUNSWICK*</pattern>
 <template>A law in New Brunswick says that driving on the roads is not allowed.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*NEW HAMPSHIRE*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>It is illegal to sell the clothes one is wearing to pay off a gambling debt in New Hampshire.
<li>It is illegal to check into a hotel under an assumed name in New Hampsire.
<li>You may not tap your feet, nod your head, or in any way keep time to the music in a tavern, restaurant, or cafe in New Hampshire.
<li>In New Hampshire, any cattle that crosses state roads must be fitted with a device to gather its feces.
<li>In New Hampshire, It is illegal to pick seaweed up off of the beach.
<li>You may not run machinery on Sundays in New Hampshire.
<li>On Sundays in New Hampshire, citizens may not relieve themselves while looking up.
<li>In Claremont, New Hampshire, it is illegal to do any of the following in cemeteries: get drunk, picnic, enter at night, and enter by oneself if one is younger than 10.
<li>In White Mountain National, New Hampshire, if a person is caught raking the beaches, picking up litter, hauling away trash, building a bench for the park, or performing other similar duties without a permit, s/he may be fined 150 dollars for &quot;maintaining the national forest without a permit&quot;.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*NEW JERSEY*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>It is against the law to &quot;frown&quot; at a police officer in New Jersey.
<li>In Newark, New Jersey, it is illegal to sell ice cream after 6 p.m., unless the customer has a note from his doctor.
<li>It is illegal to slurp soup in New Jersey.
<li>In Trenton, New Jersey, it is illegal to throw a bad pickle in the street.
<li>If any couple making out inside a vehicle accidentally sounds the horn during their lustful act, they may be taken to jail according to a Liberty Corner, New Jersey law.
<li>In New Jersey, drivers must warn those they pass on highways before doing so.
<li>In New Jersey, spray paint may not be sold without a posted sign warning juveniles of the penalty for creating graffiti.
<li>In New Jersey, handcuffs may not be sold to minors.
<li>In New Jersey, it is illegal to wear a bullet proof vest while committing a murder.
<li>In New Jersey, one must yield a phone line to a person if it is an emergency.
<li>In New Jersey, all motorists must honk before passing another car, bicyclist, skater, and even a skateboarder.
<li>In New Jersey, you cannot pump your own gas.
<li>In New Jersey, it is against the law for a man to knit during the fishing season.
<li>In New Jersey, the month of May is designated &quot;Kindness Awareness Month&quot;.
<li>In New Jersey, if you've been convicted of driving while intoxicated, you may never again apply for personalized license plates.
<li>In New Jersey, the third Thursday of October is designated as &quot;New Jersey Credit Union Day&quot; and citizens of the state should observe the day with &quot;appropriate activities and programs&quot;.
<li>In New Jersey, car dealerships are forbidden to open on Sunday.
<li>In New Jersey, automobiles are not to pass horse drawn carriages on the street.
<li>In New Jersey, it is illegal to delay or detain a homing pigeon.
<li>In Bernards Township, New Jersey, it is illegal to frown as the town is a &quot;Frown-Free Town Zone&quot;.
<li>In Blairstown, New Jersey, shooting ranges are outlawed.
<li>In Blairstown, New Jersey, no street-side trees may be planted that &quot;obscure the air&quot;.
<li>In Blairstown, New Jersey, it is illegal to throw ashes on the sidewalk.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*NEW MEXICO*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Raton, New Mexico, it is illegal for a woman to ride horseback down a public street with a kimono on.
<li>The Merriam-Webster Collegiate Dictionary is banned in Carlsbad, New Mexico.
<li>State officials in New Mexico ordered 400 words of &quot;sexually explicit material&quot; to be cut from Romeo and Juliet
<li>During lunch breaks in Carlsbad, New Mexico, no couple should engage in a sexual act while parked in their vehicle, unless their car has curtains.
<li>Idiots may not vote in New Mexico.
<li>In Carrizozo, New Mexico, it's forbidden for a female to appear unshaven in public.
<li>In Deming, New Mexico, persons may not spit on the steps of the opera house.
<li>Hunting is prohibited in Mountain View Cemetery in Deming, New Mexico.
<li>In Las Cruces, New Mexico, you may not carry a lunchbox down Main Street.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*NEW YORK*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In New York City, it is illegal for a woman to be on the street wearing &quot;body hugging clothing.&quot;
<li>In New York City, it is illegal for a man to turn around and look &quot;at a woman in that way,&quot; and violators are forced to wear horse blinders.
<li>In Staten Island, it is illegal for a father to call his son a &quot;faggot&quot; or &quot;queer&quot; in an effort to curb &quot;girlie behavior.&quot;
<li>In New York City, &quot;It is disorderly conduct for one man to greet another on the street by placing the end of his thumb against the tip of his nose, at the same time extending and wiggling the fingers of his hand.&quot;
<li>In New York, women may go topless in public, providing it is not being used as a business.
<li>In New York, you may not smoke within 100 feet of the entrance to a public building.
<li>In New York, a fine of 25 dollars can be levied for flirting.
<li>In New York, it is against the law to throw a ball at someone's head for fun.
<li>In New York, the penalty for jumping off a building is death.
<li>In New York, you cannot dissolve a marriage for irreconcilable differences, unless both parties agree to it.
<li>In New York, a person may not walk around on Sundays with an ice cream cone in his/her pocket.
<li>In New York, while riding on an elevator, one must talk to no one, and fold his hands while looking toward the door.
<li>In New York, slippers are not to be worn after 10 p.m.
<li>In Carmel, New York, a man can't go outside while wearing a jacket and pants that do not match.
<li>In Carmel, New York, ice cream may not be eaten while standing on the sidewalk.
<li>In Carmel, New York, women may not wear high heels while in the city limits.
<li>In Greene, New York, it is illegal to eat peanuts and walk backwards on the sidewalks during a concert.
<li>In Ocean City, New York, a law from the early 1900s prohibits men from going topless on the Boardwalk.
<li>In Ocean City, New York, eating while swimming in the ocean is prohibited.
<li>In Ocean City, New York, people maynot slurp their soup.
<li>In Ocean City, New York, pinball machines are not to be played on Sunday.
<li>In Ocean City, New York, raw hamburger may not be sold.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*NORTH CAROLINA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Charlotte, North Carolina, women must have their bodies covered by at least 16 yards of cloth at all times.
<li>In Ashville, Carolina, it is illegal to sneeze on city streets.
<li>Ironically, Hornytown, North Carolina, has banned all massage parlors.
<li>State law in North Carolina mandates that all couples staying in rooms for one night must be kept in a room with double beds, kept a minimum of two feet apart, and making love on the floor between the beds is strictly forbidden.
<li>It is illegal to have sex in a churchyard in North Carolina.
<li>In North Carolina, the mere possession of a lottery ticket is illegal and may result in a 2,000 dollar fine.
<li>In North Carolina, no one may be a professional fortune teller, and if one wishes to pursue the practice as an amateur, it must be practiced in a school or church.
<li>In North Carolina, it's against the law to sing off key.
<li>In North Carolina, elephants may not be used to plow cotton fields.
<li>In North Carolina, while having sex, you must stay in the missionary position and have the shades pulled.
<li>In North Carolina, if a man and a woman who aren't married go to a hotel/motel and register themselves as married then, according to state law, they are <i>legally married</i>.
<li>In North Carolina, oral sex is considered a crime against nature.
<li>In North Carolina, a marriage can be declared void if either of the two persons is physically impotent.
<li>In North Carolina, persons in possession of illegal substances must pay taxes on them.
<li>In North Carolina, a 3 dollar tax must be paid on all white goods sold.
<li>In North Carolina, organizations may not hold their meetings while the members present are in costume.
<li>In North Carolina, bingo games may not last over 5 hours unless they are held at a fair.
<li>In North Carolina, serving alcohol at bingo games is not allowed.
<li>In Barber, North Carolina, fights between cats and dogs are prohibited.
<li>In Chapel Hill, North Carolina, it is a misdemeanor to urinate or defecate publicly.
<li>In Dunn, North Carolina, it is illegal to drive cars through city cemeteries for pleasure.
<li>No one may visit their departed loved ones late at night in Dunn, North Carolina.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*NORTH DAKOTA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Fargo, North Dakota, one may be jailed for wearing a hat while dancing, or even for wearing a hat to a function where dancing is taking place.
<li>It is illegal to lie down and fall asleep with your shoes on in North Dakota.
<li>It is illegal to serve beer and pretzels at the same time in any bar, club, or restaurant in North Dakota.
<li>In North Dakota, it is illegal to shoot an Indian on horseback, provided you are in a covered wagon.
<li>In Devil's Lake, North Dakota, New Year's celebrations are somewhat bland as fireworks may not be set off after 11 p.m.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*NORWAY*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Norway, if your vehicle stalls and you leave it on the side of the road, you must mark the vehicle with a red, reflecting triangle.
<li>In Norway, a fee is levied on each purchaser of any plastic bottle which is returned upon return of the bottle.
<li>In Norway, licenses must be bought in order to own television sets, and even VCRs.
<li>In Norway, you may not spay your female dog or cat.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*NOVA SCOTIA*</pattern>
 <template>When raining, a person may not water his/her lawn in Nova Scotia.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*OHIO*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Cleveland, Ohio, women are forbidden from wearing patent leather shoes, lest men see reflections of their underwear.
<li>In Columbus, Ohio, it is illegal for stores to sell Cornflakes on Sunday.
<li>In Oxford, Ohio, it is illegal for a women to disrobe in front of a man's picture.
<li>In Youngstown, Ohio, it is illegal to run out of gas.
<li>Catch 22 is banned in Strongville, Ohio.
<li>In Ohio, if you ignore an orator on Decoration Day to such an textent as to publicly play croquet or pitch horseshoes within one mile of the speaker's stand, you can be fined 25 dollars.
<li>In Ohio, it is illegal to fish for whales on Sunday.
<li>In Ohio, it is illegal to get a fish drunk.
<li>The Ohio driver's manual states that you must honk the horn whenever you pass another car.
<li>In Ohio, participating or conducting a duel is prohibited.
<li>In Ohio, breast feeding is not allowed in public.
<li>In Ohio, it is illegal for more than 5 women to live in a house.
<li>In Ohio, it is illegal to mistreat anything of great importance.
<li>In Ohio, no one may be arrested on Sunday or on the Fourth of July.
<li>In Akron, Ohio, it is illegal to display colored chickens for sale.
<li>In Akron, Ohio, no person shall solicit sex from another of the same gender if it offends the second person.
<li>Skateboarding in the city limits of Akron, Ohio, is prohibited after dark.
<li>Posting signs at swimming pools is illegal in Akron, Ohio.
<li>In Bay Village, Ohio, it is illegal to walk a cow down Lake Road.
<li>In Bexley, Ohio, ordinance # 223, of 09/09/19 prohibits the installation and usage of slot machines in outhouses.
<li>In Canton, Ohio, electric fences are banned.
<li>If one loses their pet tiger in Canton, Ohio, they must notifty the authorities within one hour.
<li>Power Wheels cars may not be driven down the street in Canton, Ohio.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*OKLAHOMA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>People who make &quot;ugly faces&quot; at dogs may be fined and/or jailed in Oklahoma.
<li>In Schulter, Oklahoma, it is illegal for a woman to gamble in the nude, in lingerie, or while wearing a towel.
<li>Clinton, Oklahoma, has a law against masturbating while watching two people having sex in a car.
<li>One may not promote a &quot;horse tripping event&quot; in Oklahoma.
<li>In Oklahoma, it is illegal for the owner of a bar to allow anyone inside to pretend to have sex with a buffalo.
<li>In Oklahoma, females are forbidden from doing their own hair without being licensed by the state.
<li>In Oklahoma, dogs must have a permit signed by the mayor in order to congregate in groups of 3+ on private property.
<li>Oklahoma will not tolerate anyone taking a bite out of another's hamburger.
<li>In Oklahoma, it's against the law to read a comic book while operating a motor vehicle.
<li>In Oklahoma, whaling is illegal.
<li>In Oklahoma, it is illegal to have the hind legs of farm animals in your boots.
<li>In Oklahoma, residents are taxed for the furniture in their homes, and any other personal belongings.
<li>In Oklahoma, cars must be tethered outside of public buildings.
<li>In Oklahoma, oral sex is a misdemeanor and is punishable by one year in jail and a 2,500 dollar fine.
<li>In Oklahoma, anyone arrested for soliciting a hooker must have their name and picture shown on television.
<li>In Oklahoma, it's statutory rape for a man over 18 to have sex with a female under the age of 18, provided she's a virgin.
<li>In Oklahoma, tattoos are banned.  <B>(Repealed, effective 11/1/2006.  Tattoos are now legal in Oklahoma!)</b>
<li>In Oklahoma, no one may spit on a sidewalk.
<li>In Oklahoma, it is illegal to wear your boots to bed.
<li>In Oklahoma, it is illegal to have sex before you are married.vfish may not be contained in fishbowls while on a public bus.
<li>In Oklahoma, tissues are not to be found in the back of one's car.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*ONTARIO*</pattern>
 <template>The speed limit is 80 kph for cars, but bicyclists have the right of way in Ontario.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*OREGON*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Oregon, one may not bathe without wearing &quot;suitable clothing,&quot; i.e., that which covers one's body from neck to knee.
<li>The town of Hood River, Oregon, prohibits the act of juggling without a license.
<li>Salem, Oregon, has barred women's wrestling.
<li>In Marion, Oregon, ministers are forbidden from eating garlic or onions before delivering a sermon.
<li>In Willowdale, Oregon, no man may curse while having sex with his wife.
<li>Drivers must yield to pedestrians who are standing on the sidewalk in Oregon.
<li>In Oregon, one may not test their physical endurance while driving a car on a highway.
<li>In Oregon, it is illegal to place a container filled with human feces on the side of any highway.
<li>In Oregon, babies may not be carried on the running boards of a car.
<li>In Oregon, drivers may not pump their own gas.
<li>In Oregon, a door on a car may not be left open longer than is necessary.
<li>In Oregon, an adult may not show a minor any piece of classical artwork which depicts sexual excitement.
<li>In Oregon, dishes must drip dry.
<li>In Oregon, the &quot;Peer Review Statute&quot; prohibits you from finding out details of any written or oral discussion about your medicla treatment.
<li>In Oregon, it is illegal to whisper dirty things in your lover's ear during sex.
<li>In Oregon, ice cream may not be eaten on Sundays.
<li>In Oregon, it is illegal to buy or sell marijuana, but it is legal to smoke it on your own property.
<li>In Oregon, canned corn is not to be used as bait for fishing.
<li>In Beaverton, Oregon, you must buy a $10 permit to be allowed to install a burglar alarm.
<li>It is illegal to show movies or attend a car race on Sundays in Eugene, Oregon.
<li>In Eugene, Oregon it is legal to conduct a horse race or a symphony concert.
<li>In Klamath River, Oregon, it's illegal to walk down a sidewalk and knock a snake's head off with your cane.
<li>In marian, Oregon, you cannot eat a doughnut and walk backwards on a city street.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*PENNSYLVANIA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Pennsylvania, any motorist who sights a team of horses coming toward him must pull well off the road, cover his car with a blanket or canvas that blends with the countryside, and let the horses pass. If the horses appear skittish, the motorist must take his car apart, piece by piece, and hide it under the nearest bushes.
<li>In Morrisville, Pennsylvania, women need a permit to wear cosmetics.
<li>Ministers in Pennsylvania are forbidden from performing marriages when either the bride or groom is drunk.
<li>In Harrisburg, Pennsylvania, it is illegal to have sex with a truck driver inside a toll booth.
<li>It is contrary to Pennsylvania law to discharge a gun, cannon, revolver or other explosive weapon at a wedding.
<li>In Pennsylvania, it is illegal to have over 16 women live in a house together because that constitutes a brothel.
<li>In Pennsylvania, it is illegal to sleep on top of a refrigerator outdoors.
<li>In Pennsylvania, any motorist driving along a country road at night must stop every mile and send up a rocket signal, wait 10 minutes for the road to be cleared of livestock, and continue.
<li>In Pennsylvania, a special cleaning ordinance bans housewives from hiding dirt and dust under a rug in a dwelling.
<li>In Pennsylvania, you may not sing in the bathtub.
<li>In Pennsylvania, fireworks stores may not swell fireworks to Pennsylvania residents.
<li>In Pennsylvania, a person is not eligible to become governor if s/he has participated in a duel.
<li>In Pennsylvania, no more than two packages of beer at any time may be purchased, unless you are buying from an official &quot;beer distributor&quot;.
<li>In Pennsylvania, all liquor stores must be run by the state.
<li>In Pennsylvania, motorized vehicles are not to be sold on Sundays.
<li>In Pennsylvania, you may not catch a fish with your hands.
<li>In Pennsylvania, you may not catch a fish with any body part except the mouth.
<li>In Pennsylvania, dynamite is not to be used to catch fish.
<li>In Pennsylvania, though you do not need a fishing license to fish on your own land, a hunting license is required to hunt on your own land.
<li>In Allentown, Pennsylvania, there is a ban on men becoming aroused in public.
<li>In Bensalem, Pennsylvania, persons convicted of felonies may not operate bingo games.
<li>In Bensalem, Pennsylvania, operators of bingo games may not advertise the prizes offered.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*PHILIPPINES*</pattern>
 <template>In the Philippines, cars whose license plates end with a 1 or 2 are not allowed on the roads on Monday; 3 or 4 on Tuesday; 5 or 6 on Wednesday; 7 or 8 on Thursday; and 9 or 0 on Friday from 7:00 a.m.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*QUEBEC*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>All business signs in the province of Quebec must be in French. If the business operator wishes to have English on the sign, the French must be at least twice as large as the English is. There are no laws governing the usage of other languages on signs. -Bill 101 (Passed 1976)
<li>No language other than French is permitted to be shown out doors in Quebec.
<li>It is illegal to turn right on a red light at any time in Quebec.
<li>In Montréal, Quebec, you may not swear in French.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*RHODE ISLAND*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Providence, Rhode Island, it is illegal to sell toothpaste and a toothbrush to the same customer on a Sunday.
<li>It is illegal to throw pickle juice on a trolley in Rhode Island.
<li>In Newport, Rhode Island, it is illegal to smoke a pipe after sunset.
<li>In Rhode Island, cap guns are illegal.
<li>In Rhode Island, ropes may not be strung across a highway.
<li>In Rhode Island, no one may bite off another's leg.
<li>Rhode Island recently applied to the US Government to make all the coastal waters of Rhode Island a &quot;No Discharge Zone&quot;.
<li>In Rhode Island, impersonating a town sealer, auctioneer, corder of wood, or a fence-viewer is against the law.vriding a horse over any public highway for the purpose of racing, or testing the speed of the horse is illegal.
<li>In Rhode Island, exercising any labor, businesses, or work, or using any game, sport, play, or recreation, or causing any of the above to be done to or by your children, servants, or apprentices on the first day of the week (Sunday) results in a penalty of 5 dollars for the first offense and 10 dollars for the second.
<li>In Rhode Island, professional sports, except ice polo and hockey, must obtain a license to play games on Sunday.
<li>In Rhode Island, any marriage where either of the parties is an idiot or lunatic is null and void.
<li>In Rhode Island, one must make a loud noise before passing a car on the left.
<li>In Providence, Rhode Island, there is not an appeals process for exemption of property tax due to a disability or poverty.
<li>It is illegal to wear transparent clothing in Providence, Rhode Island.
<li>In Scituate, Rhode Island, it is illegal to drive down any street with beer in your car, even if it is unopened.
<li>It is illegal to use water on even-numbered days for the sole purpose of watering plants, lawns, or gardens in West Warwick, Rhode Island.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*SINGAPORE*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Singapore, bungee jumping is illegal.
<li>The sale of gum is prohibited in Singapore.
<li>Oral sex is illegal unless it is used as a form of foreplay in Singapore.
<li>Pornography in Singapore is illegal.
<li>In Singapore, homosexuals are not allowed to live in the country.
<li>As it is considered pornographic, you may not walk around your home nude in Singapore.
<li>Failure to flush a public toilet in Singapore may result in very hefty fines.
<li>In Singapore, it is considered offensive to enter the country with cigarettes.
<li>Cigarettes are illegal at all public places in Singapore.
<li>It is illegal to come within 50 meters of a pedestrian crossing marker on any street in Singapore.
<li>If you are convicted of littering 3 times in Singapore, you will have to clean the streets on Sundays with a bib on saying, &quot;I am a litterer.&quot;
<li>It is illegal to pee in an elevator in Singapore.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*SOUTH AFRICA*|*AFRICA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In South Africa, a license is required to purchase a television set.
<li>In South Africa, in the days of the aparthed, all people of color had to be indoors by 9 p.m. at which time a siren was sounded.
<li>In South Africa, young people wearing bathing suits are prohibited from sitting less than 12 inches apart.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*SOUTH CAROLINA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Every citizen in South Carolina is obliged to carry his gun to church.
<li>In Charleston, South Carolina, all carriagehorses must wear diapers.
<li>In South Carolina, it is illegal to display a confederate flag on a courthouse.
<li>In South Carolina, by law, if a man promises to marry an unmarried woman, the marriage must take place.
<li>In South Carolina, railroad companies may be held liable in some instances for scaring horses.
<li>In South Carolina, a railroad may not remove itself from a town of more than 500 people.
<li>In South Carolina, fortune tellers are required to obtain a special permit from the state.
<li>In South Carolina, dance halls may not operate on Sundays.  An exception to the above law is that light bulbs may be sold.
<li>In South Carolina, no work may be done on Sunday.
<li>In South Carolina, musical instruments may not be sold on Sunday.
<li>In South Carolina, performing a U-turn within 1,000 feet of an intersection is illegal.
<li>In South Carolina, it is considered an offense to get a tattoo.
<li>In South Carolina, horses may not be kept in bathtubs.
<li>In South Carolina, it is illegal to sell any alcoholic beverages on Sunday, unless you own a private club.
<li>In South Carolina, a permit must be obtained to fire a missile,
<li>In South Carolina, it is illegal to give or receive oral sex.
<li>In South Carolina, when approaching a four way or blind intersection in a non-horse driven vehicle, you must stop 100 feet from the intersection and discharge a firearm into the air to warn horse traffic.
<li>In South Carolina, it is perfectly legal to beat your wife on the courthouse steps on Sundays.
<li>In South Carolina, every adult male must bring a rifle to church on Sunday in order to ward off Indian attacks.
<li>In South Carolina, it is a capital offense to inadvertently kill someone while attempting suicide.
<li>In South Carolina, a person must be 18 years old to play a pinball machine.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*SOUTH DAKOTA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>It is illegal to lie down and fall asleep in a cheese factory in South Dakota.
<li>Movies that show police officers being struck, beaten, or treated in an offensive manner are forbidden in South Dakota.
<li>In hotels in Sioux Falls, South Dakota, every room is required to have twin beds. The beds must always be a minimum of two feet apart when a couple rents a room for only one night. And it's illegal to make love on the floor between the beds!
<li>In South Dakota, no horses are allowed into Fountain Inn unless they are wearing pants.
<li>In South Dakota, if there are 5+ Native Americans on your property you may shoot them.
<li>In Spearfish, South Dakota, if 3+ Indians are walking down the street together, they can be considered a war party and fired upon.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*SOUTH KOREA*|*KOREA*</pattern>
 <template>In South Korea, traffic police are required to report all bribes that they receive from motorists.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*SWAZILAND*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Swaziland, any woman who wears pants faces a possible punishment of having the pants ripped off her and torn to pieces by soldiers.
<li>In Swaziland, young girls may not shake hands with men.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*SWEDEN*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>A prince or princess who marries without the consent of the government, that person forfeits the right of succession for his/her children and all other descendants in Sweden.
<li>While prostitution is legal, it is illegal to use the services of a prostitute in Sweden.
<li>You may only own half a meter down in the ground of your land in Sweden.
<li>In Sweden, it is illegal to repaint a house without a painting license and the government's permission.
<li>If you release pigs into an acornwood (or a beechnutwood) mutually owned by you and at least one more, and exceeded your quota of allowed pigs, you will have to pay a fine for each pig to the owners and to restore any damages caused by the extra pigs in Sweden.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*SWITZERLAND*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Switzerland, clothes may not be hung to dry on Sunday.
<li>In Switzerland, you may not wash your car on a Sunday.In Switzerland, it is considered an offense to mow your lawn on a Sunday, because it causes too much noise.In Switzerland, it is illegal to flush the toilet after 10 p.m.
<li>In Switzerland, a man may not relieve himself while standing up after 10 p.m.
<li>In Switzerland, though it is illegal to produce, store, sell and trade absinthe, it is legal to consume it.
<li>In Switzerland, it is required that every car with snow tires has to have a sticker on its dashboard which tells that the driver should not drive faster than 160 km/h with these tires.
<li>In Switzerland, if you forget your car keys inside the car and you leave the car open, you will be punished.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*TENNESSEE*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>It is illegal to use a lasso to catch a fish in Tennessee.
<li>In Dyersburg, Tennessee, it is illegal for a woman to call a man for a date.
<li>In Memphis restaurants, it is illegal to give any pie to fellow diners. It is also illegal to take unfinished pie home. All pie must be eaten on the premises.
<li>In Memphis, it is illegal for a woman to drive by herself; &quot;a man must walk or run in front of the vehicle, waving a red flag in order to warn approaching pedestrians and motorists.&quot;
<li>In Tennessee, you can't shoot any game other than whales from a moving automobile.
<li>In Tennessee, hollow logs may not be sold.
<li>In Tennessee, more than 8 women may not live in the same house because that would constitute a brothel.
<li>In Tennessee, &quot;crimes against nature&quot; are prohibited.
<li>In Tennessee, ministers are to be dedicated to God and therefore are not eligible to hold a seat in either House of the Legislature.
<li>In Tennessee, any person who participates in a duel may not hold any public office in the state.
<li>In Tennessee, giving and receiving oral sex is still prohibited by law.
<li>In Tennessee, stealing a horse is punishable by hanging.
<li>In Tennessee, no Christian parent may require their children to pick up trash from the highway on Easter day.
<li>In Tennessee, driving is not to be done while asleep.
<li>In Tennessee, it is legal to gather and consume roadkill.
<li>In Tennessee, the definition of &quot;dumb animal&quot; includes every living creature.
<li>In Tennessee, interracial marriages are illegal.
<li>In Tennessee, tattooing a minor is a misdemeanor.
<li>In Tennessee, it is illegal to dare a child to purchase a beer.
<li>In Tennessee, it is illegal to place tacks on a highway.
<li>In Tennessee, skunks may not be carried into the state.
<li>In Bell Buckle, Tennessee, one may not throw bottles at a tree.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*TEXAS*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>The entire Encyclopedia Britannica is banned in Texas because it contains a formula for making beer at home.
<li>A recently passed anticrime law in Texas requires criminals to give their victims 24 hours notice, either orally or in writing, and to explain the nature of the crime to be committed.
<li>In El Paso, Texas, churches, hotels, halls of assembly, stores, markets, banking rooms, railroad depots, and saloons are required to provide spittoons &quot;of a kind and number to efficiently contain expectorations into them.&quot;
<li>It is illegal to milk another person's cow in Texas.
<li>In Houston, Texas, it is illegal to sell Limburger cheese on Sunday.
<li>In LeFors, Texas, it is illegal to take more than three swallows of beer while standing.
<li>In San Antonio, Texas, it is illegal for both sexes to flirt or respond to flirtation using the eyes and/or hands.
<li>In Mesquite, Texas, it is illegal for children to have unusual haircuts.
<li>In Kingsville, Texas, there is a law against two pigs having sex on the city's airport property.
<li>It is illegal to raise alligators in your home in Texas.
<li>When two trains meet each other at a railroad crossing in Texas, each shall come to a full stop, and neither shall proceed until the other has gone.
<li>You need a 5 dollar permit to go barefoot in Texas.
<li>In Texas, one must acknowledge a supreme being before being able to hold public office.
<li>In Texas, it is illegal to sell one's eye.
<li>In Texas, a program has been created that attempts to control the weather.
<li>In Texas, up to a felony charge can be levied for promoting the use of, or owning more than 6 dildos.
<li>In Texas, it is illegal for one to shoot a buffalo from the second story of a hotel.
<li>In Texas, homosexual behavior is a misdemeanor offense.
<li>In Abilene, Texas, it is illegal to idle or loiter any place within the corporate limits of the city for the purpose of flirting or mashing.
<li>In Austin, Texas, wire cutters cannot be carried in your pocket.
<li>In Beaumont, Texas, collegiate football is banned at Lamar University.
<li>In Borger, Texas, it is against the law to throw confetti, rubber balls, feather dusters, whips or quirts (riding crops), and explosive firecrackers of any kind.
<li>In Clarendon, Texas, it is illegal to dust any public building with a feather duster.
<li>In Dallas, Texas, it's illegal to possess realistic dildos.
<li>In El Paso, Texas, urinating on the streets is illegal.
<li>Appearing in public places wearing &quot;lewd dress&quot; is prohibited in El Paso, Texas.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*THAILAND*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Thailand, it is illegal to leave your house if you are not wearing underwear.
<li>You must wear a shirt while driving a car in Thailand.
<li>You must pay a fine of 600 dollars in Thailand if you're caught throwing away chewed bubble gum on the sidewalk.
<li>No one may step on any of the nation's currency in Thailand.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*TURKEY*</pattern>
 <template>In Turkey, all married women must get their husbands permission if they wish to have a job, they must live wherever the husband wishes to reside, and they must forfeit all jointly held assets upon divorce from her husband.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*UNITED KINGDOM*|*UK*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In the UK, no cows may be driven down the roadway between 10 a.m. and 7 p.m. unless there is a prior approval from the Commissioner of Police.
<li>In the UK, all land must be left to the eldest son.
<li>In the UK, divorces are outlawed.
<li>In the UK, since 1313, MPs are not allowed to don armor in Parliament.
<li>In the UK, those wishing to purchase a television must also buy a license.
<li>In the UK, with the exception of carrots, most goods may not be sold on Sunday.
<li>In the UK, all English males over the age of 14 are to carry out 2 or so hours of longbow practice a week supervised by the local clergy.
<li>In the UK, London Hackney Carriages (taxis/cabs) must carry a bale of hay and a sack of oats.
<li>In the UK, it is illegal to be drunk on Licensed Premises (in a pub or bar).
<li>In the UK, it is illegal for two adult men to have sex in the same house as a third person.
<li>In the UK, any person found breaking a boiled egg at the sharp end will be sentenced to 24 hours in the village stocks (enacted by Edward VI).
<li>In the UK, Chelsea Pensioners may not be impersonated.
<li>In the UK, a bed may not be hung out of a window.
<li>In the UK, it is illegal to leave baggage unattended.
<li>In the UK, picking up abandoned baggage is an act of terrorism.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*UTAH*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Birds have the right of way on all highways in Utah.
<li>In Utah, a husband is responsible for every criminal act committed by his wife while she is in his presence.
<li>In Monroe, Utah, daylight must be visible between partners on a dance floor.
<li>A Tremonton, Utah law states that no woman is allowed to have sex with a man while riding in an ambulance. In addition to normal charges, the woman's name will be published in the local newspaper. The man does not receive any punishment.
<li>Utah state legislation outlaws all sex with anyone but your spouse.  Thus, adultery, oral and anal sex, and masturbation are considered sodomy and can lead to imprisonment. Sex with an animal - unless performed for profit - however is NOT considered sodomy.
<li>Polygamy - provided only the missionary position has been applied - is only a misdemeanor in Utah.
<li>In Utah, it is against the law to fish from horseback.
<li>In Utah, it is illegal <i>not</i> to drink milk.
<li>In Utah, it is illegal to detonate any nuclear weapon.
<li>In Utah, you're not allowed to sell beverages containing more than 3 (?).
<li>In Utah, it is a felony to persistently tread on the cracks between paving stones on the sidewalk of a state highway.
<li>In Utah, it's legal for restaurants to serve wine with meals, but only if you ask for the wine list.
<li>In Utah, it is considered an offense to hunt whales.
<li>In Utah, alcohol may not be sold during an emergency.
<li>In Utah, boxing matches that allow biting are not allowed.
<li>In Utah, individuals may not possess beer in containers larger than two liters unless they are a retailer.
<li>In Utah, it is illegal to cause a catastrophe.
<li>In Kaysville, Utah, you must have identification to enter a convenience store after dark.
<li>In Logan, Utah, women may not swear.
<li>In Provo, Utah, throwing snowballs will result in a 50 dollar fine.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*VERMONT*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Women must obtain written permission from their husbands to wear false teeth in Vermont.
<li>In Vermont, it is illegal to deny the existence of God.
<li>It is illegal to whistle underwater in Vermont.
<li>At one time, it was illegal to tie a giraffe to a telephone pole in Vermont.
<li>In Barre, Vermont, all residents shall bathe every Saturday night.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*VIRGINIA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Richmond, Virginia, it is illegal to flip a coin in any eating establishment to determine who buys a cup of coffee.
<li>In Norfolk, Virginia, a man may face 60 days in jail for patting a woman's derriere.
<li>There is a state law prohibiting &quot;corrupt practices of bribery by any person other than candidates.&quot;
<li>In Lebanon, Virginia, it is illegal to kick your wife out of bed.
<li>In Norfolk, Virginia, a woman can't go out without wearing a corset. (There was a Civil Service job--for men only--called a corset inspector.)
<li>In Virginia, not only is it illegal to have sex with the lights on, one may not have sex in any position other than missionary.
<li>In Virginia, you may not engage in business on Sundays, with the exception of almost every industry.
<li>In Virginia, if one is not married, it is illegal for him to have sexual relations.
<li>In Virginia, you may not have oral or anal sex.
<li>In Virginia, driving while not wearing shoes is prohibited.
<li>In Virginia, police radar detectors are illegal.
<li>In Virginia, citizens must honk their horn while passing other cars.
<li>In Virginia, children are not to go trick-or-treating on Halloween.
<li>In Virginia, it is illegal to tickle women.
<li>In Virginia, no animal may be hunted for on Sunday with the exception of raccoons, which may be hunted until 2 a.m.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*WASHINGTON*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Seattle, Washington, women who sit on men's laps on buses or trains without placing a pillow between them face an automatic six-month jail term.
<li>In Auburn, Washington, men who deflower virgins, regardless of age or marital status, may face up to five years in jail.
<li>Seattle, Washington residents may not carry concealed weapons longer than six feet.
<li>In Washington, it is illegal to pretend that one's parents are rich.
<li>In the state of Washington there is a law against having sex with a virgin under any circumstances. (Including the wedding night.)
<li>In Washington, it is illegal to attach a vending machine to a utility pole without prior consent from the utility company.
<li>In Washington, no person may walk about in public if he or she has the common cold.
<li>In Washington, destroying a beer cask or bottle of another is illegal.
<li>In Washington, it is illegal to entice girls away from the Maple Lane School for girls.
<li>In Washington, x-rays may not be used to fit shoes.
<li>In Washington, all lollipops are banned.
<li>In Washington, a law to reduce crime states: &quot;It is mandatory for a motorist with criminal intentions to stop at the city limits and telephone the chief of police as he is entering the town.&quot;
<li>In Washington, it is illegal to paint polka dots on the American flag.
<li>In Washington, people may not buy mattresses on Sunday.
<li>In Washington, all motor vehicles must be preceded by a man carrying a red flag (daytime) or a red lantern (nighttime) fifty feet in front of said vehicle.
<li>In Washington, it is illegal to pretend that one's parents are rich.
<li>In Washington, you are not allowed to breastfeed in public.
<li>In Washington, one may not spit on a bus.
<li>In Washington, when two trains come to a crossing, neither shall go until the other has passed.
<li>In Washington, you cannot buy meat of any kind on Sunday.
<li>In Bremerton, Washington, you may not shuck peanuts on the street.
<li>In Everett, Washington, it is illegal to display a hypnotized or allegedly hypnotized person in a store window.
<li>In Lynden, Washington, dancing and drinking may not occur at the same establishment.
<li>In Seattle, Washington, you may not carry a concealed weapon that is over six feet in length.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*WEST VIRGINIA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In Nicholas County, West Virginia, no clergy members may tell jokes or humorous stories from the pulpit during church services.
<li>Doctors and dentists may not place a woman under anesthesia unless a third person is present in West Virginia
<li>It is illegal to snooze on a train in West Virginia.
<li>In West Virginia, unmarried couples who live together and &quot;lewdly associate&quot; with one another may face up to a year in prison.
<li>In West Virginia, when a railroad passes within 1 mile of a community of 100 or more people, they must build a station and stop there regularly to pick up and drop off passengers.
<li>In West Virginia, any person who commits adultery shall be fined at least 20 dollars.
<li>In West Virginia, it is legal for a male to have sex with an animal as long as it does not exceed 40 lbs.
<li>In West Virginia, a tax of 1 cent is levied for every 16 and 9 ounces of Coke sold in a store.
<li>In West Virginia, a person may be placed in jail for up to six months for making fun of someone who does not accept a challenge.
<li>In West Virginia, a person may not hold public office if he or she has ever participated in a duel.
<li>In West Virginia, according to the state constitution, it is unlawful for anyone to own a red or a black flag.
<li>In West Virginia, if you wear a hat inside a theater, you may be fined.
<li>In West Virginia, roadkill may be taken home for supper.
<li>In West Virginia, whistling underwater is prohibited.
<li>In Alderson, West Virginia, one may not walk a lion, tiger or leopard, even on a leash.
<li>In Huntington, West Virginia, firemen may not whistle or flirt with any woman passing a firehouse.
<li>In Huntington, West Virginia, it is legal to beat your wife so long as it is done in public on Sunday, on the courthouse steps.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*WISCONSIN*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In St. Croix, Wisconsin, women are not allowed to wear anything red in public.
<li>It is illegal to cut a woman's hair in Wisconsin.
<li>It is illegal to kiss on a train in Wisconsin.
<li>In Wisconsin, cheese making requires a cheese maker's license and Limburger cheese making requires a master cheese maker's license.
<li>In Connorsville, Wisconsin, no man shall shoot off a gun while his female partner is having a sexual orgasm.
<li>In Wisconsin, butter substitutes are not allowed to be served in state prisons.
<li>In Wisconsin, whenever two trains meet at an intersection of said tracks, neither shall proceed until the other has.
<li>In Wisconsin, as people used to smuggle it in from Illinois, all yellow butter substitute is banned.
<li>In Wisconsin, condoms were considered an obscene article and had to be hidden behind the pharmacist's counter.
<li>In Wisconsin, at one time margarine was illegal.
<li>In Wisconsin, state law made it illegal to serve apple pie in public restaurants without cheese.
<li>In Wisconsin, the state definition of rape stated that it was a man having sex with a woman he knows not to be his wife.
<li>In Wisconsin, margarine may not be substituted for butter in restaurants unless it is requested by the customer.
<li>In Wisconsin, the government may not prohibit manually flushed urinals.
<li>In Wisconsin, one may not camp in a wagon on any public highway or risk a fine of up to $10.
<li>In Wisconsin, it is a Class A misdemeanor to wave a burning torch around in the air.
<li>In Wisconsin, it is illegal to throw rocks at a railroad car.
<li>In Wisconsin, livestock have the right-of-way on public roads.
<li>In Brookfield, Wisconsin, tattooing is illegal unless it is done for medical purposes.
<li>It is unlawful for one to allow another ot use the first person's telephone in order to make prank phone calls in Brookfield, Wisconsin.
<li>In Hudson, Wisconsin, screens are required on all windows from May 1 to October 1.
<li>In Hudson, Wisconsin, you are not allowed to put litter into someone else's trash receptacle without express permission.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*WYOMING*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>It is illegal to wear a hat that obstructs people's view in a public theater or place of amusement in Wyoming.
<li>In Wyoming, it is illegal for women to stand within five feet of a bar while drinking.
<li>An ordinance in Newcastle, Wyoming, specifically bans couples from having sex while standing inside a store's walk-in meat freezer!
<li>In Wyoming, all new buildings that cost over 100,000 dollars to build must have 1 percent of funds spent on art work for the building.
<li>In Wyoming, if one is drunk in a mine, he or she could land in jail for up to a year.
<li>In Wyoming, junk dealers may not make any business transactions with drunk persons.
<li>In Wyoming, using a firearm to fish is strictly forbidden.
<li>In Wyoming, any person who fails to close a fence is subject to a fine of up to 750 dollars.
<li>In Wyoming, you may not take a picture of a rabbit from January to April without an official permit.
<li>In Wyoming, skiing under the influence of alcohol is prohibited.
<li>In Wyoming, it is illegal to spit on the steps of a school.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*ZIMBABWE*</pattern>
 <template>In Zimbabwe, citizens may not make offensive gestures at a passing state motorcade.</template>
</category>
</alice>
