
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>2 WAY</pattern>
 <template>(Chorus)  (x2)  Romeo, Romeo  it takes two to make a thing go right  Romeo, oh Romeo  it takes two to make it out of sight       I wanna rock right now im lil Romeo and i came to get down im not internationally known but I'm known to rock the microphone  Call me a pretty boy crown me the greatest a new no limit  Ya'll can't fade this you know I'm a   winner sho not a loser P. Miller clothes is what I choose ladies love me   Girls adore me I mean even the ones that never saw me  Like the way that i rhyme at a show the reason why whodie I don't know  Oh yea    (Chorus X2)    Gametime, hair done up, hang time, attention 2 way on the waist line, young P   role on cress and neck below zero I'm the best to come in the game ask Cleo   holla back youngn (ooh ooh)  Pop ya colla call me richie rich I got a dog name   Dollar Custom paint 20's on my ride but I keep it lockdown  Cuz I'm to young to drive I got bankrolls of pesos so my love wont cost a thing like J-Lo  I'm a baller ma I don't play with playdoh  You seen cribs that's now thats how we roll    (Chorus X2)     You got mail give it to the haters yall get fame we get paper Rome be Kobe I   be Shaq come back get double-platiunum back to back  Grown folks watchin girls be jockin ooohhhwwee tank ain't stoppin  Come on off the bench and win it that's just in me drop the top  Nothin less than the bently don't twist the game  We reversed it back, P, rome & silkk, how you love that    (Chorus x2)     Six Flags, I got the doleo platinum tanks that the logo  You know u suppose to   bounce to this I'm 12 years old  With 21 karrots around my wrist o wats up doc   The party don't stop these no limit boys gone drop It like its hot     Where them girls at  Where them boys at  Throw em up get em up put em up</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>CRAWLING</pattern>
 <template>Crawling in my skin  These wounds they will not heal  Fear is how i fall  Confusing what is real    There's something inside me that pulls beneath  The surface  Consuming, confusing  This lack of self-control I fear is never ending  Controlling, I can't seem  To find myself again  My walls are closing in   (Without a sense of confindence, I'm convinced there's just too much pressure to take)  I've felt this way before so insecure    Crawling in my skin  These wounds they will not heal  Fear is how I fall  Confusing what is real    Discompfort endlessly has pulled itself upon me  Distracting, reacting  Against my will I stand beside my own reflection  It's haunting how I can't seem to find myself again  My walls are closing in   (Without a sense of confindence, I'm convinced there's just too much pressure to take)  I've felt this way before  So insecure    Crawling in my skin  These wounds they will not heal  Fear is how I fall  Confusing what is real    Crawling in my skin  These wounds they will not heal  Fear is how I fall  Confusing, confusing what is real    *[In background]  (There's something inside me that pulls beneath the surface consuming, confusing  This lack of self control I fear is never ending, controlling)</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>GO JIMMY JIMMY</pattern>
 <template>Jimmy  Jimmy who?  Neutron, Neutron, Neutron    Here we go  Verse one      I flip the switches  In the atomosphere  In my drop top market  Doin' my ten  I'm a little shootin'  Star in the makin'  Droppin' Neutron bombs  On the ???  Cuz I'm headin' for the top  No mistakin'  And my destiny's mine  For the takin'  ?????  Like a black hole  Wanna act up  I'm a big shot  Make a big move  Comin' up  Take control of my life  Like a spaceship  But I still keep it  Real with my parents  Don't lip, won't trip  While I'm on Earth  When I'm in the  Milky Way  Just trust, givin' up  Ain't an option  Where I'm goin'  Ain't no man ever been  Light speed, light years  I'm ahead of them      Go Jimmy Jimmy  That's the voice I hear inside  Everybody let's bounce  Straight up come along for the ride  Go Jimmy Jimmy  To the rescue  Through the big blue sky  Be back before I leave  It's Jimmy Neutron time      No time for jittering  It's my turn  At bat like Robin  Since I'm in  The big leagues  No stoppin'  Like a comet  On a mission  I'm movin'  Cuz I'm doin' my thing  Lookin' for the big bang  Do you wanna hang?  Make a decision  How are you livin'?  Don't be a quitter  I'm gonna fly  Forget about physics  Gravity mean nuthin' to me  Work can't stop me  Is it just me?  Hold me back  Yeah right, let's see  Whatever I say  ??? you'll see  So let's ride out, slide out  Time ain't nuthin'  When ya got big dreams  It's your world, universe  Woooweee  Split them atoms  Blow the scene      Go Jimmy Jimmy  That's the voice I hear inside  Everybody let's bounce  Straight up come along for the ride  Go Jimmy Jimmy  To the rescue  Through the big blue sky  Be back before I leave  It's Jimmy Neutron time      Do your thing  Do your thing  Do your thing  Do your thing  Do your thing  Do your thing      You know I got to make you dance      Go Jimmy Jimmy  That's the voice I hear inside  Everybody let's bounce  Straight up come along for the ride  Go Jimmy Jimmy  To the rescue  Through the big blue sky  Be back before I leave  It's Jimmy Neutron time      Go Jimmy Jimmy  That's the voice I hear inside  Everybody let's bounce  Straight up come along for the ride  Go Jimmy Jimmy  To the rescue  Through the big blue sky  Be back before I leave  It's Jimmy Neutron time</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>IKO IKO</pattern>
 <template>My grandma and your grandma  Were sittin' by the fire.  My grandma said to your grandma  &quot;I'm gonna set your flag on fire&quot;     Hey now! Hey now!  Iko, Iko, unday  Jockamo feeno ai nan?  Jockamo fee nan?     Look at my king all dressed in red Iko, Iko, unday.  I betcha five dollars he'll kill you dead  Jockamo fee nan?    Hey now! Hey now!  Iko, Iko, unday  Jockamo feeno ai nan?  Jockamo fee nan?     My flag boy and your flag boy  Were sittin' by the fire.  My flag boy told your flag boy  &quot;I'm gonna set your flag on fire&quot;    Hey now! Hey now!  Iko, Iko, unday  Jockamo feeno ai nan?  Jockamo fee nan?     Hey now! Hey now!  Iko, Iko, unday  Jockamo feeno ai nan?  Jockamo fee nan?    See that guy all dressed in green ?  Iko Iko unday   He's not a man He's a lovin' machine.  Jockamo fee nan?    Hey now! Hey now!  Iko, Iko, unday  Jockamo feeno ai nan?  Jockamo fee nan?     Hey now! Hey now!  Iko, Iko, unday  Jockamo feeno ai nan?  Jockamo fee nan?    Hey now! Hey now!  Iko, Iko, unday  Jockamo feeno ai nan?  Jockamo fee nan?    Hey now! Hey now!  Iko, Iko, unday  Jockamo feeno ai nan?  Jockamo fee nan?</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>KIDS IN AMERICA</pattern>
 <template>Looking out a dirty old window  Down below the cars in the City go rushing by  I sit here alone And I wonder why    Friday night and everyone's moving  I can feel the heat,But it's soothing  Heading down (repeat)  I search for the beat in this dirty town    Down town the young ones are going  Down town the young ones are growing    We're the kids in America   We're the kids in America  Everybody live for the music-go-round    Bright lights the music gets faster  Look boy, don't check on your watch  Not another glance (another glance)  I'm not leaving now, honey not a chance    Hot-shot, give me no problems  Much later baby you'll be saying never mind  You know life is cruel, life is never kind    Kind hearts don't make a new story  Kind hearts don't grab any glory    We're the kids in America   We're the kids in America  Everybody live for the music-go-round    dah dah dah dah dah dah  dah dah dah dah dah dah  dah dah dah dah dah dah  dah dah dah  dah dah dah  dah dah dah dah dah dah dah    Come closer, honey that's better  Got to get a brand new experience  Feeling nice (repeat)  Oh don't try to stop baby    New York to California  There's a new wave coming we warn ya    We're the kids in America   We're the kids in America  Everybody live for the music-go-round    dah dah dah dah dah dah  dah dah dah dah dah dah  dah dah dah dah dah dah  dah dah dah  dah dah dah  dah dah dah dah dah dah dah    We're the kids  We're the kids  We're the kids in America    We're the kids  We're the kids  k-k-k-kids in America    We're the kids  We're the kids  We're the kids in America    We're the kids  We're the kids  We're the kids in America    We're the kids  We're the kids  We're the kids in America.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>LEAVE IT UP TO ME</pattern>
 <template>It's the kids, baby  It's the kids, baby  It's the kids, come on  It's the kids, baby  It's the kids, baby  And ya know we're gonna groove  It's the kids, baby  It's the kids, baby  It's the kids, come on  It's the kids, baby    Leave it up, leave it up to me      Listen to the kids  Grown up, sewn up  Even when they mess up  Actin' like it's all sewn up  Mom and dad think we  Need to have a talk  Think the kids rule the world  Boys and girls      You can't blame us for notta  You taught us, to follow orders  Cuz I'm the baby, dun gotta  Monkey see (ah ah)  Monkey do no more  The fun stops here  What's the score  We might start a play fight  Just to imitate you  Donchya feel silly now  Shame on you  Don't start to cry now  I don't blame you  Afterall your just a grown-up  Whachya gonna do      It's the kids. Even I  Gotta heat it up, heat it up  What's the deal. Doncha know I  Gotta give it up, give it up  Make way, put it on  Gotta hook it up, hook it up  How's that  Leave it up, leave it up to me      It's the kids  What would ya do if I  Speed it up, speed it up  Set it off  Gonna live it up, live it up  Make way, put it on  Gonna hook it up, hook it up  How's that  Leave it up, leave it up to me      When the grown-ups go awol  Who ya gonna call  Here come the young ones  The baby crime busters  Big people, listen up  Relax now we're equal  And if the money's right  Then we might make a sequal  Do I hear a &quot;please&quot;?  I love it when you beg me  I need a bribe now  Just to move my legs, see  And I might fit you in  If you make way      (Lemme talk to my people we can save the day)      It's the kids. Even I  Gotta heat it up, heat it up  What's the deal. Doncha know I  Gotta give it up, give it up  Make way, put it on  Gotta hook it up, hook it up  How's that  Leave it up, leave it up to me      It's the kids  What would ya do if I  Speed it up, speed it up  Set it off  Gonna live it up, live it up  Make way, put it on  Gonna hook it up, hook it up  How's that  Leave it up, leave it up to me      (Now whatchya gonna do)      Mom and dad, they be  Gettin' on my nerves  Workin' em, workin' em  Is that what I deserve  But after many days  Hey, I want them back  Tell me who's gonna bake  My cake and all that  Who's gonna suffer from  My practical jokes  And answer when I'm moving  Hey, it's gotta be my folks  And who's gonna get me up  Ready for the flight  And who's gonna tell me  &quot;Everything's alright&quot;      But wait a minute  That sounds so soft  That won't impress a  Hot chicka that I cross  Don't play me out cuz  I'll switch ya off  You've been told old for too long  Singin' the same song  If you're old enough to vote  Then it's time to sit down  It's all about the little hommies  Takin' the crown  So if you're too young to vote  Here's your chance to have a say  Come on everybody  Help me save the day      It's the kids. Even I  Gotta heat it up, heat it up  What's the deal. Doncha know I  Gotta give it up, give it up  Make way, put it on  Gotta hook it up, hook it up  How's that  Leave it up, leave it up to me      It's the kids  What would ya do if I  Speed it up, speed it up  Set it off  Gonna live it up, live it up  Make way, put it on  Gonna hook it up, hook it up  How's that  Leave it up, leave it up to me      It's the kids. Even I  Gotta heat it up, heat it up  What's the deal. Doncha know I  Gotta give it up, give it up  Make way, put it on  Gotta hook it up, hook it up  How's that  Leave it up, leave it up to me      It's the kids  What would ya do if I  Speed it up, speed it up  Set it off  Gonna live it up, live it up  Make way, put it on  Gonna hook it up, hook it up  How's that      Leave it up, leave it up to me</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>NOT TOO YOUNG NOT TOO OLD</pattern>
 <template>I'm not too young   And I'm not too old    Listen up, everybody  This ain't Aaron's party  Talk to me more than that  Come and show me body  Girl whatcha gonna do,  come and talk  To me in the backseat  Baby backstreetWe could surf the board  Surf the net, yeah  Better yet  We could make a little bet  If we get together,  Yo it's gonna be the bomb  Hit me all, baby  Aaron Carter dot com  See when it comes to girls  I'm not too young  Baby face back up on the scene  But when I get in trouble,  Hey I'm not too old  I pull my cap way down  And I'm seven years old  That's how we roll    Throw your hands up now  Let the music take control  This is how we roll  I'm not too young  And I'm not too old  Here we go    Throw your hands up now  Let the music take control   This is how we roll  I'm not too young and I'm not too old    It's the A to the A to the R O N  I'm all grown up now  Run and tell your friend  It's all sewn up now  Where do I begin?  Don't even play a hater  Tryin' to say I look ten  I'll tell you again  I all up in da video  Catch me in the studio  That's my life, bro  It's in my blood, hey!  It ain't my fault  You wanna step to me,  We can take it to the asphalt  Shoot some hoops  Can you slam dunk the funk  Battle on the rollerblades  You callin me a punk?  Bring on the skateboards  Or the BMX  Show me watcha got  Is that all? Please, next!  I'll wipe the floor with you  Where's your concentration?  Don't even talk about the Sony Playstation  I'll make it happen if its games that you want  Aaron Carter gotcha open  This is how we roll     Throw your hands up now  Let the music take control  This is how we roll   I'm not too young  And I'm not too old  Here we go    Throw your hands up now  Let the music take control  This is how we roll  I'm not too young   And I'm not too old    He's goin' out with the older boys  Cover up your ears  'Cause we're makin' that noise  He's goin' out with the younger girls  Cover up your eyes   'Cause we rock the world!    See when it comes to takin all the girls for cruisin'  All I need is pillows, hello!  I'm not too young  (Doo doo doo doo)  My cellular phone  (Doo doo doo doo)  Switch it off, yo  Hit me on the pager  A real teenager  With a fake beard  Battin' in the majors  That's how we roll  And when it suits me   I'm anywhere between 12 and 18 years old    Here we go    Throw your hands up now  Let the music take control  This is how we roll  I'm not too young  And I'm not too old    Here we go    Throw your hands up now  Let the music take control  This is how we roll  I'm not too young   And I'm not too old</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>POKERAP GS</pattern>
 <template>P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  Pokemon!  P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  Pokemon!    Sunflora, Igglybuff, Piloswine, Slugma,  Crobat, Politoed, Noctowl, Houndour,  Heracross, Natu, Tyrogue, Ariados,  Lugia, Steelix, Phanpy, Ampharos    P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  Pokemon!  P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  Pokemon!    Sudowoodo, Corsola, Teddiusa,  Sneasel, Forretress, Mantine, Pichu,  Larvitar, HootHoot, Miltank, Totodile,  Gligar, Lanturn, Skarmony, Spinarak,  Tyranitar    Chikorita, Dunsparce, Aipom, Pupitar,  Porygon2, Cyndaquil, Elekid, Raikou,  Wobbuffet, Typhlosion, Granbull,  Pokemon!  Stantler, Espeon, Ledyba, Togepi    I turn to you, whenever I need you  You've got the power to protect us all  One thing is true  Your kind of magic's  At the tip of my fingers  Whenever I call    Gotta catch em,  Gotta catch em,  Gotta catch em all!  POKEMON!    P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  Pokemon!  P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  Pokemon!    Quilfish, Ho-oh, Azumarill, Croconaw,  Snubbull, Ursaring, Yanma, Smoochum.  Slowking, Blissey, Scizor, Donphan,  Houndoom, Octillery, Wooper, Mareep,  Hitmontop, Marill, Umbreon, Bayleaf    P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  Pokemon!    Sunkern, Ledian, Girafarig, Murkrow,  Remoraid, Jumpluff, Quilava, Smeargie,  Swinub, Magcargo  Furret, Bellossom, Flaaffy, Entei,  Meganium, Magby    Xatu, Misdreavus, Togetic, Shuckle,  Quagsire, Pineco, ChinChou, Feraligatr,  Hoppip, Kingdra, Unown, Cleffa,  Suicine, Delibird, Sentret, Skiploom    Gotta catch em,  Gotta catch em,  Gotta catch em all!  POKEMON!    Gotta catch em,  Gotta catch em,  Gotta catch em all!  (Sing it!)    P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  Pokemon!  P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  Pokemon!    P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  Pokemon!  P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  Pokemon!    P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  Pokemon!  P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  Pokemon!    P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  Pokemon!  P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  P-O-K-E-M-O-N!  Pokemon!</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>POLKAMON</pattern>
 <template>Krabby, Snubbull, Venonat,   Mankey, Chansey and Zubat  Slowking, Ditto, Butterfree,   Lugia and Caterpie  Oddish, Poliwag, Goldeen,  Elekid and Nidoqueen  Victreebel and Magneton - Everybody Polkamon!    Aerodactyl, Seel, Machoke,  Marill, Moltres, then Slowpoke,  Articuno, Ditto, Muk,  Flareon and ol' Psyduck  Cloyster, Kingler, Shellder, Gloom,  Snorlax and of course Vileplume  Zapdos and Charmeleon - Everybody Polkamon!    It's time to polka  For Ponyta and Pidgey too  Come on put on your lederhosen  And try not to stamp on little Pikachu  You'd better grab yourself a partner  Like Tentacruel or Bulbasaur (Bulbasaur!)  Hold on a minute,  there's still at least a 127 more    Including Ledyba and Omastar  Jynx, Bellossom and Magmar  Geodude and Arcanine  Jiggypuff and Mr. Mime  Don't forget about Sandslash,   Exeggcute and Rapidash  Lickitung and Porygon - Everybody Polkamon!    Everybody Polkamon!    Everybody Polkamon!</template>
</category>
</alice>
