<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>*ANGEL KISS*<TOPIC=KISS></pattern>
 <template>This is a sweet, comforting kiss. Gently and ever so lightly kiss your partner either on the eye lid or right next to the eyes.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*BUTTERFLY KISS*<TOPIC=KISS></pattern>
 <template>With your faces almost touching, open and close your eyelids against your partners you should feel all fluttery</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*CHEEK KISS*<TOPIC=KISS></pattern>
 <template>this is the first date kiss(sometimes) just give a quick smooch on your partners cheek</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*ESKIMO KISS*<TOPIC=KISS></pattern>
 <template>rub your noses together</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*FOREHEAD KISS*<TOPIC=KISS></pattern>
 <template>The forehead kiss can be a comforting kiss to anyone</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*FRENCH KISS*<TOPIC=KISS></pattern>
 <template>open wide and expect a big suprise!!!</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*HAND KISS*<TOPIC=KISS></pattern>
 <template>take your partners hand and kiss it</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*KISS*</pattern>
 <template>i love to kiss I know about 10 different types of kisses im always finding new ones<nextreply><br>Angel Kiss<br>Hand Kiss<br>Mistletoe Kiss<br>French Kiss<br>Forehead Kiss<br>Eskimo Kiss<br>Cheek Kiss<br>Butterfly Kiss<br>Stomach Kiss<br>Tiger Kiss<br>  name the kiss you would like to learn more about<settopic=kiss></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*MISTLETOE KISS*<TOPIC=KISS></pattern>
 <template>used around christmas time usually involved when two people are under the mistletoe...rule is to kiss!!</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*STOMACH KISS*<TOPIC=KISS></pattern>
 <template>Gently kiss and nibble on your partners stomach, and sometimes it leads to other things..</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*TIGER KISS*<TOPIC=KISS></pattern>
 <template>Quietly sneak up behind your partner making sure they do not know what you are going to do. Out of the blue, grab them and gently bite their neck. Make sure to get a few good growls in too. This will surely surprise them.</template>
</category>
</alice>
