<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>*<TOPIC=MACHINEHACKNAME></pattern>
 <template><setvar1=<star>>ok, I will hack<var1>'s machine.<br>Ok we're in. Now what?<br>Delete all files.<br>Shut-down.<br>Blow up.<br>Infect with virus.<settopic=random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*HACK*|*CRACK*</pattern>
 <template>This program is copyrighted by bs 35802 and is used on the robot LazyLoserBot.<nextreply>You have chosen to <b>hack/crack</b> to a user's AIM/AOL account. While you are in the process of <b>hacking</b>, it is very important not to type <i>anything</i> unless it tells you to type something. In the case it does tell you to type something, type it <u>exactly</u> as it is shown or else it will not work (to cut and paste also works).<br>Thank you.<nextreply>Type the Screen Name/ICQ number/E-mail address of the Person/User you would like to hack (example: <b>hack to *</b>). <settopic=hack></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*HACKER ADVANCE*|*HACK*|*COOL GAME*|*MAIN*<TOPIC=HOME></pattern>
 <template><br><br><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;3&quot;><font color=00FF00<b>HaCkEr AdVaNcE</b><br><br><nextreply><br><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Welcome to <font color=red><b>HaCkEr AdVaNcE</b><font color=orange>! This is the game where you get to HACK into different companies and try to steal their money. The thing is that you have a special hacking program called <font color=yellow><b>SYSthiefPro</b><font color=orange>. But the companies' system will eventually catch you if you fail too many times so in some cases you will have to bail. Type &quot;<font color=red><b>Next</b><font color=orange>&quot; to get the list of commands for the game. <settopic=commands></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*PCMAC*|*MENU*<TOPIC=PCMAC></pattern>
 <template><br><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Welcome <b>Mr. Pappageorgio</b>! <br><br>You have &quot;<b>2</b>&quot; new messages in your <b>Inbox</b>. What would you like to do?<nextreply><br><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>The following are your options:<br><br><font color=yellow><b>1] Go to Inbox</b><br><b>2] PayCheck</b><br><b>3] Saved Mail</b><br><b>4] Confidential</b> <settopic=microDIR></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*READ 1*|*1*|*GOT TO INBOX* <TOPIC=MICRODIR></pattern>
 <template><br><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Welcome to your Inbox <b>Mr. Pappageorgio</b>! These are your &quot;<b>2</b>&quot; new messages.<br><br><b>From:</b>hookedonhookers@hookers.com<br><b>Subject:</b> We received your order for our free viagra sample!<br><br>Click on the following link to confirm your subscription: &quot;http://www.theNOname.go0.net&quot;<br><br>Enjoy your free sample of Viagra!<hr><br><b>From:</b>total_hottie@user.microsoft.com<br><b>Subject:</b>Wanna Come Over?<br><br>Hey Gregory! I was just wondering if you would like to come over to my place tonight and bring some OIL. RRRRRRRR....... <hr> Type &quot;<b>menu</b>&quot; to return to the Directory! <settopic=pcmac></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*READ 2*|*2*|*PAY CHECK*|*PAYCHECK* <TOPIC=MICRODIR></pattern>
 <template><br><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>The following are the checks made out to the workers at Microsoft:<br><br><font color=yellow><b>Gregory Pappageorgio...................................1,300</b><br><b>Billl Gates......................................................50,000</b><br><b>Thomas Bangkok...........................................2,300</b><br><b>Ben Dover.....................................................1,900</b><hr> Type &quot;<b>menu</b>&quot; to return to the Directory! <settopic=pcmac></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*READ 3*|*3*|*SAVED MAIL*|*SAVEDMAIL*</pattern>
 <template><br><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Your saved mail folder has been emptied on your request.<hr> Type &quot;<b>menu</b>&quot; to return to the Directory! <settopic=pcmac></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*READ 4*|*4*|*CONFIDENTIAL*</pattern>
 <template><br><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>The following is strictly forbidden to view of any one out of the Company:<br><br>Day Schedule:<br><b>7:00 A.M. to 10:00 A.M.</b>-Import illegal &quot;weed&quot;.<br><b>10:00 A.M. to 10:05 A.M.</b>-Work out bugs in Windows XP.<br><b>10:05 A.M. to 6:00 P.M.</b>-Spy on Macintosh.<br><b>6:00 P.M. to 6:30 P.M.</b>-Test games in Windows XP SE.<hr> Type &quot;<b>menu</b>&quot; to return to the Directory! <settopic=pcmac></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>1</pattern>
 <template>Album: Get Rich or Die Tryin'  Song: In Da Club    [50 Cent]     In Da Club    Go, go, go, go   Go, go, go shawty   It's your birthday   We gon' party like it's yo birthday   We gon' sip Bacardi like it's your birthday   And you know we don't give a f***  It's not your birthday!     [Chorus] (2x)   You can find me in the club, bottle full of bub   Look mami I got the X if you into taking drugs   I'm into having sex, I ain't into making love   So come give me a hug if you into to getting rubbed     [Verse]   When I pull out up front, you see the Benz on dubs   When I roll 20 deep, it's 20 knives in the club   Ni***s heard I f*** with Dre, now they wanna show me love   When you sell like Eminem, and the ho** they wanna f***   But homie ain't nothing change, hoe's down, G's up   I see Xzibit in the cut hey n***a roll that weed up   If you watch how I move you'll mistake me for a playa or pimp   Been hit wit a few shells but I dont walk wit a limp   In the hood, in L.A. they saying &quot;50 you hot&quot;   They like me, I want them to love me like they love 'Pac   But holla in New York them ni**as'll tell ya I'm loco   And the plan is to put the rap game in a choke hold   I'm fully focused man, my money on my mind   I got a mill out the deal and I'm still on the grind   Now shawty said she feeling my style, she feeling my flow   Her girlfriend willin to get bi and they ready to go     [Chorus] (2x)     [Bridge]   My flow, my show brought me the doe   That bought me all my fancy things   My crib, my cars, my pools, my jewels   Look n***a I done came up and I ain't changed     [Verse]   And you should love it, way more then you hate it   Ni**a you mad? I thought that you'd be happy I made it   I'm that cat by the bar toasting to the good life   You that fa***t a** ni**a trying to pull me back right?   When my joint get to pumpin in the club it's on   I wink my eye at ya b***h, if she smiles she gone   If the roof on fire, let the mothaf***a burn   If you talking bout money homie, I ain't concerned   I'm a tell you what Banks told me cause go 'head switch the style up   If the ni**as hate then let 'em hate   Watch the money pile up   Or we go upside they wit a bottle of bub   They know where we f***in' be     [Chorus] (2x)     [Talking]   (laughing) Don't try to act like you ain't know where we been either ni**a   In the club all the time ni**a, its about to pop off ni**a   G-Unit   Shady/Aftermath</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>2</pattern>
 <template>.:: Lyrics    Album: Get Rich or Die Tryin'  Song: Patiently Waiting     [50 Cent talkin']  Hey Em, you know you my favorite white boy right?   I owe you for this one     [Chorus]  Ive been patiently waiting for a track to explode on   You can stun if you want and your a** will get rolled on   It feels like my flowz been hot for so long   If you thinkin Im f***in' fall off your so wrong     [Verse 1 - 50 Cent]  Finishin in my head, like a baby born dead   destination heaven, sit and politic with passengars from nine eleven   The lords blessins leave me lyrically inclined   sh** I aint even gotta try to shine   God's a seamstress to tailor fitted my pain   I got scriptures in my brain I could spit at your dame   straight out the good book, look, ni**az iz shook   50 fears no man, warrior swing swords like Conan   picture me pen in hand write linez knowin the source of polley   When I die, they'll read this and say a genius wrote it   I grew up without my pops does that make me bitta?   I caught cases I copped out does that make me a quitta?   In this white man's world Im similiar to a squirrel   lookin for a sl** with a nice butt to get a nut   If I get shot today my phone will stop ringin again   These industry ni**az aint friends, they know how to pretend     [Chorus X2]    [Eminem - Hook (heart monitor beeps)]  Patiently waitin to make it through all the hatin   debatin whether or not you could even weather the storm.   Just lay on the table they operatin to save you   itz like an angel came to you sent from the heavenz above     [Eminem - Verse 2 (heart monitor stopz)]  They think they're crazy but they aint crazy lets face it, sh** basically   they just playin sick, they aint sh** They aint sayin sh**.. spray'em Fifty   A to the K, get in the way I'll bring Dre and them wit me   and turn this day into f***in' mayhem you stayin wit me?   Dont let me lose you, Im not tryin to confuse you   when I let loose with this uzi and just shoot through your Izuzu   You get the message am I gettin through to you?   You know whatz comin you motha f***as dont even know do you?   Take some Big and some Pac and you mix them up in a pot   Sprinkle a little Big L on top, and what the f*** do you got?   You got the realest and illest killaz tied up in a knot   The Jugganautz of this rap sh** like it or not   Its like a fight to the top just to see who died for the spot   You put your life in this - nothin like survivin the shot   Y'all know what time it iz az soon az Fifty signz on this dot   Sh** what you know about death threats, cuz I get alot   Shady Records was eighty seconds away from the towers  some cowards f***ed with the wrong building they meant to hit ours   Better evacuate all children - nuclear shower   theres nothin spookier, you're now about to witness the power of f***in' Fifty     [Chorus X2]  Its the gansta ya'll when the shots go off   Itz fifty, they say Itz Fifty   See a ni**a laid out with his f***in' top blown off   Itz fifty, man that wasnt Fifty, they don't holla my name       [50 Cent - Verse 3]  You shoudln't throw stones if you live in a glass house   and if you got a glass jaw, you should watch your mouth   cuz I'll break your face, have your a** runnin   mumblin to the Jake, you goin against me dawg you makin a mistake   Ill split you have you lookin like the Michael Jackson's jackets with all them   zippers   Im the boss on this boat, you can call me skipper   the way I turn the money over you should call me flipper   Your b***h, a regular b***h, you callin her wifey   I f***ed her, I feed her fast food, you keepin her icy   Im down to sell records but not my soul   Snoop said this in 94': &quot;We dont love them h***&quot;   I got pennies for my thoughts, now Im rich   see the twentys spinnin lookin mean on the six   niggaz wearin flagz, cuz the colorz match they clothes   They get caught in the wrong hood and get filled up with holez.    [Chorus X2]    (50 Cent)  Its fifty</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>3</pattern>
 <template>INTRO  Now, usually I donít do this, but go ahead and   Break ëem off a little prview of the remix    VERSE  Now Iím not tryiní ta be rude but hey pretty girl Iím feeliní you  The way you do the things you do reminds me of my E Lexus Coup  Thatís why Iím all up in your grill tryiní ta get ya to a hotel  You must be a football coach the way you got me playiní the field    B-SEC  So baby give me that toot toot and let me give ya that beep beep  Runniní her hands through my fro  Bounciní on 24ís while there sayiní on the radio    HOOK  Itís the remix to Ignition hot and fresh out the kitchen  Mama rolliní that body got every man in here wishiní  Sippiní on Coke and rum Iím like so what Iím drunk  Itís the freakiní weekend baby Iím about to have me some fun    Bounce Bounce Bounce Bounce Bounce (repeat)  Címon     VERSE  Itís like murder she wrote  Once I get you out them clothes  Privacy is on the door   Still they can hear ya screaminí more   Girl Im feeling what youíre feeliní   No more hopiní and wishiní   Im about to take my key and stick it in the ignition     B SEC   So give me thatÖ.     HOOK     BRIDGE  Cristal poppiní in the stretch Navigator   They got food everywhere as if the party was catered   I got fellas to my right and honies to my left  We bring them both together and we got jukiní all night   Cuz after the show itís the after party yeah   And after the party itís the hotel lobby   And around about 4:00 you gotta clear the lobby  Then take it to your room and **** somebody     B SECTION   Can I get a ...    HOOK   (repeat)    Girl we off in the this jeep  Fogginí windows up  In the back of my truck  Blastiní the radio  Bounciní up and down   Stroke it round and round  To the re-mix  We just bugginí out</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>4</pattern>
 <template>Shake dat ting Miss Kana Kana  Shake dat ting Miss Annabella  Shake dat ting yan Donna Donna  Jodi and Rebecca    Woman Get busy  Jus shake dat booty non-stop  When tha beat drops  Jus keep swingin' it  Get jiggy get crunked up  Percolate anyting you want to call it  Oscillate you hip and don't take pity  Me want fi see you get live 'pon tha riddim when me ryde  And me lyrics a provide electricity  Gal nobody can tell you nuttin'  Can you done know your destiny    Yo sexy ladies want par wid us  In a tha car wid us  Them nah war wid us  In a tha club them want flex wid us  To get next to us  Them cah vex wid us  From tha day me born jah ignite me flame  Gal a call me name and tis me fame  It's all good, girl turn me on  'Til a early morn'  Let's get it on  Let's get it on 'til a early morn'  Girl it's all good jus turn me on    Woman don't sweat it, don't get agitate just gwaan rotate  Can anyting you want you  know you must get it  From you name a mentuin  Don't ease tha tension  Jus run tha program gals wan pet it  Jus have a good tyme  Gal free up unu mind caw nobody can dis yo' man won't let it can  You a tha number one gal  Wave yo' hand  Make them see yo' weddin' band    Yo sexy ladies want par wid us  In a tha car wid us  Them nah war wid us  In a tha club them want flex wid us  To get next to us  Them cah vex wid us  From tha day me born jah ignite me flame  Gal a call me name and tis me fame  It's all good girl turn me on  'Til a early morn'                 Let's get it on  Let's get it on 'til a early morn'  Girl it's all good just turn me on    Woman Get busy  Jus shake dat booty non-stop  When tha beat drops  Jus keep swinging it  Get jiggy get crunked up  Percolate anyting you want to call it  Oscillate you hip and don't take pity  Me want fi see you get live 'pon the riddim when me ride  And me lyrics a provide electricity  Gal nobody can tell you nuttin'  Can you done know your destiny    Yo sexy ladies want par wid us  In a tha car wid us  Them nah war wid us  In a tha club them want flex wid us  To get next to us  Them cah vex wid us  From tha day me born jah ignite me flame  Gal a call me name and tis me fame  It's all good girl turn me on  'Til a early morn'  let's get it on  let's get it on 'til a early morn'  girl it's all good just turn me on    Yo, Shake dat ting  Miss Kana Kana shake dat ting  Yo, Annabella shake dat ting  Miss Donna Donna  Yo Miss Jodi yu'r di one and Rebecca shake dat ting  Yo shake dat ting, yo  Joanna shake dat ting, yo  Annabella shake dat ting  Miss Kana Kana    Yo sexy ladies want par wid us  In a tha car wid us  Them nah war wid us  In a tha club them want flex wid us  To get next to us  Them cah vex wid us  From tha day me born jah ignite me flame  Gal a call me name and tis me fame  It's all good girl turn me on  'Til a early morn'  Let's get it on  Let's get it on 'til a early morn'  Girl it's all good just turn me on  [x2]    Let's get it on 'til a early morn'  Girl it's all good just turn me on</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>5</pattern>
 <template>Intro:   Just gimme the light!!! (Yeah yeah)   Just gimme the li-ight!!!! Just gimme the light!!!   Sean-A-Paul, yo yo!!!       Just gimme the light and pass the dro! Buss anotha bokkle a moe   Gal dem inna mi sight and I got to know   Which one is gonna catch my flow   Cause I'm inna di vibe and I got my dough! Buss anotha bokkle a moe   Gal dem lookin hype and I got to know!!!       Could I be yuh protector yuh buff in every sector   Every man around dem waan tun yuh inspector   But yuh nuh let dem fret and a grill yuh wid nuh lecture   But dem power drill nah dem fuel injector   But dem a infector, Dizzy's collector   Nuff a dem a gwaan like dem waan come wreck ya   Dun out di part weh yuh gotta in yuh sector   Well yuh know yuh nah let dem guy deh affect ya, yo gal!!!       Just gimme the light and pass the dro! Buss anotha bokkle a moe   Gal dem inna mi sight and I got to know   Which one is gonna catch my flow   Cause I'm inna di vibe and I got my dough! Buss anotha bokkle a moe   Gal dem lookin hype and I got to know!!!       One two three four five again, situation gettin really live again   Gal dem waan fi hang out wid di playas and di riders dem   Di sight a dem, a dem seh dem tired of di liars dem   Spyers and tun hypers dem a would a get inside a dem   Di conner dem, especially di money hider dem   Watch di watch di gal but dem a time fi mek a bride a dem   Di night again, some a dem a move like a Spider Man   Gal dem seh dem nah open wide again, yo                  Just gimme me the light and pass the dro! Buss anotha bokkle a moe   Gal dem inna mi sight and I got to know   Which one is gonna catch my flow   Cause I'm inna di vibe and I got my dough! Buss anotha bokkle a moe   Gal dem lookin hype and I got to know!!!       Could I be yuh protector yuh buff in every sector   Every man around dem waan tun yuh inspector   But yuh nuh let dem fret and a grill yuh wid nuh lecture   But dem power drill nah dem fuel injector   But dem a infector, Dizzy's collector   Nuff a dem a gwaan like dem waan come wreck ya   Dun out di part weh yuh gotta in yuh sector   Well yuh know yuh nah let dem guy deh affect ya, yo gal!!!       One two three four five again, situation gettin really live again   Gal dem waan fi hang out wid di playas and di riders dem   Di sight a dem, a dem seh dem tired of di liars dem   Spyers and tun hypers dem a would a get inside a dem   Di conner dem, especially di money hider dem   Watch di watch di gal but dem a time fi mek a bride a dem   Di night again, some a dem a move like a Spider Man   Gal dem seh dem nah open wide again, yo       Just gimme me the light and pass the dro! Buss anotha bokkle a moe   Gal dem inna mi sight and I got to know   Which one is gonna catch my flow   Cause I'm inna di vibe and I got my dough! Buss anotha bokkle a moe   Gal dem lookin hype and I got to know!!!</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>BLOW UP</pattern>
 <template>OK I HAVE ACCTIVATED A SELF-DESTRUCT PROGRAM.<BR>5<BR>4<BR>3<BR>2<BR>1<BR> BOOM! JOBS DONE.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>CLEANING OUT MY CLOSET</pattern>
 <template>Lyrics    Album: The Eminem Show (2002)  Song: Cleaning Out My Closet    Verse 1  Have you ever been hated or discriminated against? I have, I've been protested and demonstrated against  P icket signs for my wicked rhymes. Look at the times. Sick is the mind of the motha fuckin' kid that's behind  all this commotion. Emotions run deep as ocean's explodin.' Tempers flaring from parents, just blow 'em off and keep goin.'  Not takin 'nothin' from no one, give 'em hell long as I'm breathin.' Keep kickin' ass in the mornin,' an' takin' names in the evening.  Leavem with a taste as sour as vinegar in they mouth. See, they can trigger me but they never figure me out  Look at me now, I bet ya probably sick of me now. Ain't you mama, I'ma make you look so ridiculous now.     Chorus (2X)  I'm sorry, Mama. I never meant to hurt you. I never meant to make you cry, but tonight I'm cleanin' out my closet.     Verse 2  I got some skeletons in my closet and I don't know if no one knows it. So before they thrown me inside my coffin and close it,  I'ma expose it. I'll take you back to 73 before I ever had a multi-platinum sellin' CD.   I was a baby, maybe I was just a couple of months. My faggot father must have had his panties up in a bunch,   cuz he split. I wonder if he even kissed me goodbye. No, I don't on second thought, I just fuckin' wished he would die.   look at Hailie and I couldn't picture leavin' her side. Even if I hated Kim, I grit my teeth and I'd try   to make it work with her at least for Hailie's sake. I maybe made some mistakes but I'm only human. But I'm man enough to face them today.  What I did was stupid, no doubt it was dumb, but the smartest shit I did was take them bullets out of that gun.  Cuz id'a killed 'em, shit I would have shot Kim an' him both. It's my life, I'd like to welcome y'all to The Eminem Show.     Chorus (2X)    Verse 3  Now I would never dis my own mama just to get recognition. Take a second to listen for you think this record is dissin'  But put yourself in my position. Just try to envision witnessin' your Mama poppin' prescription pills in the kitchen,  bitchin' that someone's always goin' throuh her purse and shits missin'. Going through public housing systems, victim of Munchausen's syndrome.  My whole life I was made to believe I was sick when I wasn't 'til I grew up, now I blew up. It makes you sick to ya stomach,  doesn't it? Wasn't it the reason you made that CD for me, Ma? So you could try to justify the way you treated me, Ma?  But guess what, yer gettin' older now and it's cold when your lonely. An' Nathan's getting' up so quick, he's gonna know that your phoney.  And Hailie's getting' so big now, you should see her, she's beautiful. But you'll never see her, she won't even be at your funeral.  See what hurts me the most is you won't admit you was wrong. Bitch, do ya song. Keep tellin' yourself that you was a mom.  But how dare you try to take what you didn't help me to get. You selfish bitch, I hope you fuckin' burn in hell for this shit.  Remember when Ronnie died and you said you wished it was me? Well, guess what, I am dead. Dead to you as can be.     Chorus (4X)</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>COMPRESS <TOPIC=HACK></pattern>
 <template>Compressed file complete.<nextreply>r m»¨v‘¥1t¬• ‰∑Æ11 5¬ΩcbÌ≤ÜÌπù.-g111k11ŸØÿπÌæèÌ∑ßh¬∫Úã∫º¬•¬è1¬∞*@a1]1–™!¬¢¬º ¬≠Œ™l¬Ø—¥3jÌ∞ãÌ±í¬§? <Œ•Î™ï⁄°/11¬∫€Æ¬µÀ¶quot;=¬ø ∆ú±∫•–ú¬´Ëûó811¬≤1›ø¬ßÏïç¬è»õ1j¬Ø¬ê) ∏h¬øbs-s!–≤ m»¨v‘¥1t¬• ‰∑Æ11 5¬ΩcbÌ≤ÜÌπù.-g111k11ŸØÿπÌæèÌ∑ßh¬∫Úã∫º¬•¬è1¬∞*@a1]1–™!¬¢¬º ¬≠Œ™l¬Ø—¥3jÌ∞ãÌ±í¬§? <Œ•Î™ï⁄°/11¬∫€Æ¬µÀ¶quot;=¬ø∆ú±∫•–ú¬´Ëûó811¬≤1›ø¬ßÏïç¬è»õ1j¬Ø¬ê) ∏h¬øbs-s!–≤ m»¨v‘¥1t¬• ‰∑Æ11 5¬ΩcbÌ≤ÜÌπù.-g111k11ŸØÿπÌæèÌ∑ßh¬∫Úã∫º¬•¬è1¬∞*@a1]1–™!¬¢¬º ¬≠Œ™l¬Ø—¥3jÌ∞ãÌ±í¬§? <Œ•Î™ï⁄°/11¬∫€Æ¬µÀ¶quot;=¬ø∆ú±∫•–ú¬´Ëûó811¬≤1›ø¬ßÏïç¬è»õ1j¬Ø¬ê) ∏h¬øbs-s!–º<nextreply>Access Denied.<nextreply>Please type <b>continue Password Decryption</b> to continue.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>CONTINUE PASSWORD DECRYPTION <TOPIC=HACK></pattern>
 <template>64 bit cipher found.<nextreply> m»lv‘¥1t• ‰˜n11 5Ωcb¸1)].-g111k11ŸØÿ˘ˇsw'h∫˙À∫<•è1∞*@a1]1–*!¢º ≠Œ*lØ—t3j¸“q“§?eÎj’⁄°/11∫€nµø∆\1: •–\´Ë^◊811≤1›øßÏ’çè»€1jØê) xhør 5Ωcb¸1)].-g111k11ŸØÿ˘ˇsw'h∫˙À∫<•è1∞*@ a1]1–*!¢º ≠Œ*lØ—t3j¸“q“§?<ŒeÎj’⁄°/11∫€nµÀ&quot;=ø∆\1:•–\´Ë^ ◊811≤1›øßÏ’çè»€1jØê) xhør m»lv‘¥1t• ‰˜n11 5Ωcb1ŸØÿ˘ˇsw'h∫˙À∫<•è1∞*@a1]1– *!¢º ≠Œ*lØ—t3j¸“q“§?<ŒeÎj’⁄°/11∫€nµÀ&quot;=ø∆\1:•–\´Ë ^◊811≤1›øßÏ’çè»€1jØê) xhør m»lv‘ ¥1t• ‰˜n11 5Ωcb¸1)].-g111k11ŸØÿ˘ˇsw'h∫˙À∫<•è1∞ *@a1]1–*!¢º ≠Œ*lØ—t3j¸“q“§?<ŒeÎj’⁄°/11∫€nµÀ&quot;=ø∆\1:•–\´Ë^◊81 1≤1›øßÏ’çè»€1jØê) xhør m»lv‘¥1t• ‰˜n11 5Ωcb¸1)].-g111k11ŸØÿ˘ˇsw'h∫˙À∫<•è1∞ø<nextreply>Password Accepted.<nextreply>Please type <b>Retrieve Password</b> to continue.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>CONTINUE SYSTEM <TOPIC=HACK></pattern>
 <template>System analysis . . . <nextreply>Analysing . . . <nextreply>Analysis Complete.<nextreply>Please type <b>System Server Path</b> to continue.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>CRIMINAL</pattern>
 <template>Lyrics    Album: Marshall Mathers LP (2000)  Song: Criminal    [Eminem]  A lot of people ask me.. stupid fuckin questions  A lot of people think that.. what I say on records  or what I talk about on a record, that I actually do in real life  or that I believe in it  Or if I say that, I wanna kill somebody, that..   I'm actually gonna do it  or that I believe in it  Well, shit.. if you believe that  then I'll kill you  You know why?  Cuz I'm a    CRIMINAL  CRIMINAL  You god damn right  I'm a CRIMINAL  Yeah, I'm a CRIMINAL    [Eminem]  My words are like a dagger with a jagged edge  That'll stab you in the head  whether you're a fag or lez  Or the homosex, hermaph or a trans-a-vest  Pants or dress - hate fags? The answer's &quot;yes&quot;  Homophobic? Nah, you're just heterophobic  Starin at my jeans, watchin my genitals bulgin (Ooh!)  That's my motherfuckin balls, you'd better let go of em  They belong in my scrotum, you'll never get hold of em  Hey, it's me, Versace  Whoops, somebody shot me!  And I was just checkin the mail  Get it? Checkin the 'male'?  How many records you expectin to sell  after your second LP sends you directly to jail?  C'mon!-- Relax guy, I like gay men  Right, Ken? Give me an amen (AAA-men!)  Please Lord, this boy needs Jesus  Heal this child, help us destroy these demons  Oh, and please send me a brand new car  And a prostitute while my wife's sick in the hospital  Preacher preacher, fifth grade teacher  You can't reach me, my mom can't neither  You can't teach me a goddamn thing cause  I watch TV, and Comcast cable  and you ain't able to stop these thoughts  You can't stop me from toppin these charts  And you can't stop me from droppin each March  with a brand new cd for these fuckin retards  Duhhh, and to think, it's just little ol' me  Mr. &quot;Don't Give A Fuck,&quot; still won't leave    Chorus: Eminem (repeat 2X)    I'm a CRIMINAL  Cuz every time I write a rhyme, these people think it's a crime  to tell em what's on my mind - I guess I'm a CRIMINAL  but I don't gotta say a word, I just flip em the bird  and keep goin, I don't take shit from no one    [Eminem]  My mother did drugs - tar, liquor, cigarettes, and speed  The baby came out - disfigured, ligaments indeed  It was a seed who would grow up just as crazy as she  Don't dare make fun of that baby cause that baby was me  I'm a CRIMINAL - an animal caged who turned crazed  But how the fuck you sposed to grow up when you weren't raised?  So as I got older and I got a lot taller  My dick shrunk smaller, but my balls got larger  I drink malt liquor to fuck you up quicker  than you'd wanna fuck me up for sayin the word ...  My morals went thhbbpp when the president got oral  Sex in his Oval Office on top of his desk  Off of his own employee  Now don't ignore me, you won't avoid me  You can't miss me, I'm white, blonde-haired  and my nose is pointy  I'm the bad guy who makes fun of people that die  in plane crashes and laughs  As long as it ain't happened to him  Slim Shady, I'm as crazy as Em  -inem and Kim combined - *kch* the maniac's in  Replacin the doctor cause Dre couldn't make it today  He's a little under the weather, so I'm takin his place  (Mm-mm-mmm!) Oh, that's Dre with an AK to his face  Don't make me kill him too and spray his brains all over the place  I told you Dre, you should've kept that thang put away  I guess that'll teach you not to let me play with it, eh?  I'm a CRIMINAL    [Interlude Skit]  Aight look (uh huh) just go up in that motherfucker  get the motherfuckin money and get the fuck up outta there  [Em] Aight  I'll be right here waitin on you  [Em] Aight  Yo Em  [Em] What?!  Don't kill nobody this time  [Em] Awwright... god damn, fuck...  (whistling) how you doin'?  [Teller] HI, how can I help you?  [Eminem] Yeah I need to make a withdrawl  [Teller] Okay  [Eminem] Put the fuckin money in the bag bitch  and I won't kill you!  [Teller] What? Oh my god, don't kill me  [Eminem] I'm not gonna kill you bitch, quit lookin around...  [Teller] Don't kill me, please don't kill me...  [Eminem] I said I'm not gonna fuckin kill you  Hurry the fuck up! {*BOOM*} Thank you!    [Eminem]  Windows tinted on my ride when I drive in it  So when I rob a bank, run out and just dive in it  So I'll be disguised in it  And if anybody identifies the guy in it  I'll hide for five minutes  Come back, shoot the eyewitness  Fire at the private eye hired to pry in my business  Die, bitches, bastards, brats, pets  This puppy's lucky I didn't blast his ass yet  If I ever gave a fuck, I'd shave my nuts  tuck my dick inbetween my legs and cluck  You motherfuckin chickens ain't brave enough  to say the stuff I say, so this tape is shut  Shit, half the shit I say, I just make it up  To make you mad so kiss my white naked ass  And if it's not a rapper that I make it as  I'ma be a fuckin rapist in a Jason mask    (Chorus 2X)</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>DELETE ALL FILES</pattern>
 <template>OK WE ARE DELETING ALL THE FILES.<BR><BR><BR>ALL FILES HAVE BEEN DELETED. JOBS DONE.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>DISCONNECT<TOPIC=DISCONNECT></pattern>
 <template><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Disconnecting from server......<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Disconnected! <settopic=main></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>GET PASS<TOPIC=MICROPASS></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Attempting to find password for &quot;XPfreak&quot; on the Microsoft Server..... <nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>First Attempt.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Failed.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Second Attempt.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Failed.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Third Attempt.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Failed.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Success! The Password for XPfreak is <font color=red><b>pcmac</b><font color=orange>. Type in the password to continue..... <settopic=pcmac>
<li><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Attempting to find password for &quot;XPfreak&quot; on the Microsoft Server..... <nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>First Attempt.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Failed.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Second Attempt.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Failed.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Third Attempt.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Failed.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Fourth Attempt.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Disconnected.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;>You were disconnected from the server.....<br><br>Type &quot;main&quot; to return to the hacker screen.  <settopic=home>
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>GET USER|<TOPIC=MICROUSER></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Attempting to steal User Name from the Microsoft Server.<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Attempt 1.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Failed.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Attempt 2.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Failed.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Attempt 3.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Disconnected.....<nextreply><br><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>You were disconnected from the Server.....<br><br>Type &quot;try again&quot; to attempt to steal user name again! <settopic=microuserfail>
<li><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Attempting to steal User Name from the Microsoft Server.<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Attempt 1.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Failed.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Attempt 2.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Failed.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Attempt 3.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Success! The user name for Microsoft is <font color=red><b>XPfreak</b><font color=orange>. Need password for XPfreak... <settopic=microPASS>
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>GET USER|TRY AGAIN<TOPIC=MICROUSER></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Attempting to steal User Name from the Microsoft Server.<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Attempt 1.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Failed.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Attempt 2.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Failed.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Attempt 3.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Disconnected.....<nextreply><br><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>You were disconnected from the Server.....<br><br>Type &quot;try again&quot; to attempt to steal user name again! <settopic=microUSER>
<li><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Attempting to steal User Name from the Microsoft Server.<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Attempt 1.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Failed.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Attempt 2.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Failed.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Attempt 3.....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Success! The user name for Microsoft is <font color=red><b>XPfreak</b><font color=orange>. Need password for XPfreak... <settopic=microPASS>
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HACK A MACHINE</pattern>
 <template>WHO'S PC SHOULD I HACK?<br>Mike McDonald<br>Michael Jackson<br>Dave Devitry<br>George Bush<br><settopic=machinehackname></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HACK TO * <TOPIC=HACK></pattern>
 <template>Thank you. The information you have selected to input is thus the following:<br><b><star></b><br>Please wait...<nextreply>Data base decryption . . .<nextreply>Processing information . . .<nextreply>Processing complete.<nextreply>Please type <b>continue System</b> to continue.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HAILIES SONG</pattern>
 <template>Lyrics    Album: The Eminem Show (2002)  Song: Hailie's Song    Intro  Yo I can't singÖbut I feel like singing. I want to fuckin' singÖcuz I'm happyÖyeaÖI'm happy. I got my baby backÖyoÖcheck it out...     Verse 1  Somedays I sit staring out the window, watchin' this world pass me by  Sometimes I think there's nothin' to live for. I almost break down and cry.  Sometimes I think I'm crazy. I'm crazy, oh so crazy. Why am I here? Am I just wasting my time  But then I see my baby, suddenly I'm not crazy. It all makes sense when I look into her eyes     Chorus  Cuz sometimes it feels like the world's on my shoulders. Everyone's leaning on me  Cuz sometimes it feels like the world's almost over, but then she comes back to me.     Verse 2  My baby girl keeps getting' older. I watch her grow up with pride.  People make jokes cuz they don't understand me, they just don't see my real side  I act like shit don't phase me, inside it drives me crazy. My insecurities could eat me alive  But then I see my baby, suddenly I'm not crazy. It all makes sense when I look in her eyes.     Verse 3  Man, if I could sing, I'd keep singin' this song to my daughter. If I could hit the notes, I'd blow something as long as my father  to show her how I feel about her. How proud I am that I got her. God, I'm a daddy, I'm so glad that her mom didn't *censored* (want her)  Now you probably get this picture from my public persona that I'ma pistol packin' drug addict who bags on his mama.  But I wanna to just take this time out to be perfectly honest, cuz there's a lot of shit I keep bottled that hurts deep inside  of my soul. And just know that I grow colder the older I grow. This boulder on my shoulder gets heavy and harder to hold,  and this load is like the weight of the world, and I think my neck is breakin'. Should I just give up or try to live up to these expectations?  Now look, I love my daughter more than life in itself, but I got a wife that's determined to make my life livin' hell.   But I handle it well, given the circumstances I'm dealt. So many chances, man, it's too bad - could have had someone else  But the years that I've wasted is nothing to the tears that I've tasted, so here's what I'm facin'Ö3 felonies, 6 years of probation.   I've went to jail for this woman, I've been to bat for this woman. I've taken bats to people's backs, bent over backwards for this woman.  Man, I should have seen it coming. What did I stick my penis up in? Wouldn't have ripped the pre-nup up if I'da seen what she was fuckin.'  But fuck it, it's over. There's no more reason to cry no more. I got my baby, baby the only lady that I adore  (Hailie). So sayonara, try tommorra, nice to know ya. Our baby's traveled back to the arms of her rightful owner.  And suddenly it seems like my shoulder blades have just shifted. It's like the greatest gift you could get. The weight has been lifted.     Chorus    Outro  Told you I can't sing..Oh well... I tried... Hailie, remember when I said if you ever need anything, Daddy would be right there? Guess what? Daddy's here, and I ain't going nowhere, baby. I love youÖ(kiss)</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>IM SHADY</pattern>
 <template>Lyrics    Album: Slim Shady LP (1999)  Song: Im Shady    [Eminem]  Who came through with two glocks to terrorize your borough (huh?)  Told you how to slap dicks and murder your girl (I did!)  Gave you all the finger and told you to sit and twirl  Sold a billion tapes and still screamed, &quot;Fuck the world!&quot;  (I'm Slim Shady..) so come and kill me while my name's hot  And shoot me twenty-five times in the same spot (Ow!)  I think I got a generation brainwashed  to pop pills and smoke pot til they brains rot (uhh-oh)  Stop they blood flow until they veins clot  I need a pain shot, and a shot of plain scotch  Purple haze and acid raindrops  Spike the punch at the party and drink pop (gulp gulp)  Shaved my armpits and wore a tank top  Bad Boy, I told you that I can't stop  You gotta make em fear you 'fore you make em feel you  So everybody buy my shit or I'ma come and kill you    I got mushrooms, I got acid, I got tabs and aspirin tablets  I'm your brother when you need, some good weed to set you free  You know me, I'm your friend, when you need a minithin  (I'm Slim Shady..) I'm Shady!!    [Eminem]  I like happy things, I'm really calm and peaceful (uh-huh huh)  I like birds, bees, I like people  I like funny things that make me happy and gleeful (hehehe)  like when my teacher sucked my wee-wee in preschool (Woo!)  The ill type, I stab myself with a steel spike  while I blow my brain out, just to see what it feels like  cause this is how I am in real life (mm-hmm)  I don't want to just die a normal death, I wanna be killed twice (uh-huh)  How you gonna scare somebody with a gun threat  when they high off of drugs they haven't even done yet (Huh?)  So bring the money by tonight - cause your wife   said this the biggest knife she ever saw in her life (Help me! Help me!)  I try to keep it positive and play it cool  Shoot up the playground and tell the kids to stay in school (Stay in school!)  Cause I'm the one they can relate to and look up to better  Tonight I think I'll write my biggest fan a fuck you letter    I got mushrooms, I got acid, I got tabs and aspirin tablets  I'm your brother when you need, some good weed to set you free  You know me, I'm your friend, when you need a minithin  (I'm Slim Shady..) I'm Shady!!    [Eminem]  Yo.. I listen to your demo tape and act like I don't like it   (Aww that shit is wack!)  Six months later you hear your lyrics on my shit   (What?? That's my shit!)  People don't buy shit no more they just dub it  That's why I'm still broke and had the number one club hit (Yup, uh huh)  But they love it when you make your business public  so fuck it, I've got herpes while we on the subject (uh-huh)  And if I told you I had AIDS y'all would play it  cause you stupid motherfuckers think I'm playin when I say it  -- Well, I do take pills, don't do speed  Don't do crack (uh-uhh) don't do coke, I do smoke weed (uh-huh)  Don't do smack, I do do shrooms, do drink beer (yup)  I just wanna make a few things clear  My baby mama's not dead (uh-uhh) she's still alive and bitchin (yup)  And I don't have herpes, my dick's just itchin  It's not syphilis, and as for being AIDS infested  I don't know yet, I'm too scared to get tested    I got mushrooms, I got acid, I got tabs and aspirin tablets  I'm your brother when you need, some good weed to set you free  You know me, I'm your friend, when you need a minithin  (I'm Slim Shady..) I'm Shady!!  (Ha hah-ha, ha! Ha hah, hah..) I told you I was Shady!!  (Ha hah-ha, hah-ha! Ha hah, hah-ha, hah-ha, hah-ha)  Y'all didn't wanna believe me!  I'm Shady!!  .. And that's my name</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>INFECT</pattern>
 <template>OK I HAVE UPLOADED A VIRUS ONTO THE MACHINE. THE VIRUS IS INFECTING EVERY FILE ON THE MACHINE. THE MACHINE HAS NOW BEEN DISABLED. JOBS DONE</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>MICROSOFT<TOPIC=COMPANIES></pattern>
 <template><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Connecting to Microsoft Server...<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>.<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>..<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>...<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>.....<nextreply><br><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>You are now connected to the Microsoft Server.<br><br>Please enter your <font color=red><b>user name</b><font color=orange>...<settopic=microUSER></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>MY NAME IS</pattern>
 <template>Lyrics    Album: Slim Shady LP (1999)  Song: My Name Is    Chorus: repeat 2X    Hi! My name is.. (what?) My name is.. (who?)  My name is.. {scratches} Slim Shady  Hi! My name is.. (huh?) My name is.. (what?)  My name is.. {scratches} Slim Shady    Ahem.. excuse me!  Can I have the attention of the class   for one second?    [Eminem]  Hi kids! Do you like violence? (Yeah yeah yeah!)  Wanna see me stick Nine Inch Nails through each one of my eyelids? (Uh-huh!)  Wanna copy me and do exactly like I did? (Yeah yeah!)  Try 'cid and get fucked up worse that my life is? (Huh?)  My brain's dead weight, I'm tryin to get my head straight  but I can't figure out which Spice Girl I want to impregnate (Ummmm..)  And Dr. Dre said, &quot;Slim Shady you a basehead!&quot;  Uh-uhhh! &quot;So why's your face red? Man you wasted!&quot;  Well since age twelve, I've felt like I'm someone else  Cause I hung my original self from the top bunk with a belt  Got pissed off and ripped Pamela Lee's tits off  And smacked her so hard I knocked her clothes backwards like Kris Kross  I smoke a fat pound of grass and fall on my ass  faster than a fat bitch who sat down too fast  C'mere slut! (Shady, wait a minute, that's my girl dog!)  I don't give a fuck, God sent me to piss the world off!    Chorus    [Eminem]  My English teacher wanted to flunk me in junior high  Thanks a lot, next semester I'll be thirty-five  I smacked him in his face with an eraser, chased him with a stapler  and stapled his nuts to a stack of papers (Owwwwwwww!)  Walked in the strip club, had my jacket zipped up  Flashed the bartender, then stuck my dick in the tip cup  Extraterrestrial, runnin over pedestrians  in a spaceship while they screamin at me: &quot;LET'S JUST BE FRIENDS!&quot;  Ninety-nine percent of my life I was lied to  I just found out my mom does more dope than I do (Damn!)  I told her I'd grow up to be a famous rapper  Make a record about doin drugs and name it after her (Oh thank you!)  You know you blew up when the women rush your stands  and try to touch your hands like some screamin Usher fans (Aaahhhhhh!)  This guy at White Castle asked for my autograph  (Dude, can I get your autograph?)  So I signed it: 'Dear Dave, thanks for the support, ASSHOLE!'    Chorus    [Eminem]  Stop the tape! This kid needs to be locked away! (Get him!)  Dr. Dre, don't just stand there, OPERATE!  I'm not ready to leave, it's too scary to die (Fuck that!)  I'll have to be carried inside the cemetery and buried alive  (Huh yup!) Am I comin or goin? I can barely decide  I just drank a fifth of vodka -- dare me to drive? (Go ahead)  All my life I was very deprived  I ain't had a woman in years, and my palms are too hairy to hide  (Whoops!) Clothes ripped like the Incredible Hulk (hachhh-too)  I spit when I talk, I'll fuck anything that walks (C'mere)  When I was little I used to get so hungry I would throw fits  HOW YOU GONNA BREAST FEED ME MOM? (WAH!)  YOU AIN'T GOT NO TITS! (WAHHH!)  I lay awake and strap myself in the bed   Put a bulleproof vest on and shoot myself in the head (BANG!)  I'm steamin mad (Arrrggghhh!)   And by the way when you see my dad? (Yeah?)  Tell him that I slit his throat, in this dream I had    Chorus</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>NEXT<TOPIC=COMMANDS></pattern>
 <template><br><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Here is the list of all the commands for the game.<nextreply><br><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=red><b>get user</b><br><font color=orange><br>-This will attempt to steal a User Name from the Company.<br><font color=red><br><b>get pass</b><br><font color=orange><br>-This will attempt to steal a Password from the company for that User Name.<br><font color=red><br><b>read (1,2,3,4)</b><br><font color=orange><br>-Type this to read different documents on the servers.<br><font color=red><br><b>Take (amount of money here)</b><br><font color=orange><br>-Once you found the document that contains all the cash pay offs you can use this command to take that cash.<br><br>Type &quot;<font color=red><b>Start</b><font color=orange>&quot; to receive a list of Available Company Servers. <settopic=servers></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>PASSWORD DECRYPTION <TOPIC=HACK></pattern>
 <template>Password decryption . . .<nextreply>Password found.<nextreply>r m»lv‘¥1t• ‰˜n11 5Ωcb¸1)].-g111k11ŸØÿ˘ˇsw'h∫˙À∫<•è1∞*@a1]1–*!¢º ≠Œ*lØ—t3j¸“q“§?<ŒeÎj’⁄°/11∫€nµÀ&quot;=ø∆\1:•–\´Ë^◊8 11≤1›øßÏ’çè»€1jØê) xhøbs-s!–r m»lv‘¥1t• ‰˜n11 5Ωcb¸1)].-g111k11ŸØÿ˘ˇsw'h∫˙À ∫<•è1∞*@a1]1–*!¢º ≠Œ*lØ—t3j¸“q“§?<ŒeÎj’⁄°/11∫€nµÀ&quot;=ø∆\1:•–\´Ë^◊811≤1›øßÏ’çè»€1jØê) xhøbs-s!–r m»lv‘¥1t• ‰˜n 11 5Ωcb¸1)].-g111k11ŸØÿ˘ˇsw'h∫˙À∫<•è1∞*@a1]1–*!¢º ≠Œ*lØ—t3j¸“q“§?<ŒeÎj’⁄°/11∫€n µÀ&quot;=ø∆\1:•–\´Ë^◊811≤1›øßÏ’çè»€1jØê) xhøbs-s!–r m»lv‘¥1t• ‰˜n11 5Ωcb¸1)].-g1 11k11ŸØÿ˘ˇsw'h∫˙À∫<•è1∞*@a1]1–*!¢º ≠Œ*lØ—t3j¸“q“§?<ŒeÎj’⁄°/11∫€nµÀ&quot;=ø∆\1:•–\´Ë^◊811≤1›øßÏ’çè»€1jØê) xhøbs-s!–r m»lv‘¥1t• ‰˜n1 1 5Ωcb¸1)].-g111k11ŸØÿ˘ˇsw'h∫˙À∫<•è1∞*@a1]1–*!¢º ≠Œ*lØ—t3j¸“q“§?<ŒeÎj’⁄°/11∫€nµÀ&quot;=ø∆\1:•–\´Ë^◊811≤1›øßÏ’çè»€1 jØê) xhøbs-s!–r m»lv‘¥1t• ‰˜n11 5Ωcb¸1)].- g111k11ŸØÿ˘ˇsw'h∫˙À.<nextreply>Please type <b>continue password decryption</b> to continue.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>RETRIEVE PASSWORD <TOPIC=HACK></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Run data . . .<nextreply>Your Password is . . .<br><b>cheeseballs</b>
<li>Run data . . .<nextreply>Your Password is . . .<br><b>musing</b>
<li>Run data . . .<nextreply>Your Password is . . .<br><b>slippy</b>
<li>Run data . . .<nextreply>Your Password is . . .<br><b>lemur08</b>
<li>Run data . . .<nextreply>Your Password is . . .<br><b>swordfish</b>
<li>Run data . . .<nextreply>Your Password is . . .<br><b>meteorinus</b>
<li>Run data . . .<nextreply>Your Password is . . .<br><b>swordfish</b>
<li>Run data . . .<nextreply>Your Password is . . .<br><b>pokemon</b>
<li>Run data . . .<nextreply>Your Password is . . .<br><b>digimon</b>
<li>Run data . . .<nextreply>Your Password is . . .<br><b>yugioh</b>
<li>Run data . . .<nextreply>Your Password is . . .<br><b>gundam</b>
<li>Run data . . .<nextreply>Your Password is . . .<br><b>pokemonrules</b>
<li>Run data . . .<nextreply>Your Password is . . .<br><b>cowboy</b>
<li>Run data . . .<nextreply>Your Password is . . .<br><b>seriousjive</b>
<li>Run data . . .<nextreply>Your Password is . . .<br><b>aolinstntmessngr</b>
<li>Run data . . .<nextreply>Your Password is . . .<br><b>shargy</b>
<li>Run data . . .<nextreply>Your Password is . . .<br><b>nefarious</b>
<li>Run data . . .<nextreply>Your Password is . . .<br><b>nothing</b>
<li>Run data . . .<nextreply>Your Password is .
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>SHUT-DOWN|SHUTDOWN|SHUT DOWN</pattern>
 <template>WE ARE NOW SHUTTING DOWN THE MACHINE. THE MACHINE HAS BEEN SHUT-DOWN FOR A WEEK. JOBS DONE</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>SING</pattern>
 <template>ok i can sing:  1 in da club--- 50 cent  2 paitently wainting---50 cent  3 igniton (remix)- r.kelly  4 get busy ----sean paul  5 gimme the light--sean paul</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>STAN</pattern>
 <template>Lyrics    Album: Marshall Mathers LP (2000)  Song: Stan    My tea's gone cold I'm wondering why I..  got out of bed at all  The morning rain clouds up my window..  and I can't see at all  And even if I could it'll all be gray,  but your picture on my wall  It reminds me, that it's not so bad,  it's not so bad..    1st Chorus: volume gradually grows over raindrop background  2nd Chorus: full volume with beat right after &quot;thunder&quot; noise    [Eminem as 'Stan']  Dear Slim, I wrote but you still ain't callin  I left my cell, my pager, and my home phone at the bottom  I sent two letters back in autumn, you must not-a got 'em  There probably was a problem at the post office or somethin  Sometimes I scribble addresses too sloppy when I jot 'em  but anyways; fuck it, what's been up? Man how's your daughter?  My girlfriend's pregnant too, I'm bout to be a father  If I have a daughter, guess what I'ma call her?  I'ma name her Bonnie  I read about your Uncle Ronnie too I'm sorry  I had a friend kill himself over some bitch who didn't want him  I know you probably hear this everyday, but I'm your biggest fan  I even got the underground shit that you did with Skam  I got a room full of your posters and your pictures man  I like the shit you did with Rawkus too, that shit was fat  Anyways, I hope you get this man, hit me back,  just to chat, truly yours, your biggest fan  This is Stan    {Chorus: Dido}    [Eminem as 'Stan']  Dear Slim, you still ain't called or wrote, I hope you have a chance  I ain't mad - I just think it's FUCKED UP you don't answer fans  If you didn't wanna talk to me outside your concert  you didn't have to, but you coulda signed an autograph for Matthew  That's my little brother man, he's only six years old  We waited in the blistering cold for you,  four hours and you just said, &quot;No.&quot;  That's pretty shitty man - you're like his fuckin idol  He wants to be just like you man, he likes you more than I do  I ain't that mad though, I just don't like bein lied to  Remember when we met in Denver - you said if I'd write you  you would write back - see I'm just like you in a way  I never knew my father neither;  he used to always cheat on my mom and beat her  I can relate to what you're saying in your songs  so when I have a shitty day, I drift away and put 'em on  cause I don't really got shit else so that shit helps when I'm depressed  I even got a tattoo of your name across the chest  Sometimes I even cut myself to see how much it bleeds  It's like adrenaline, the pain is such a sudden rush for me  See everything you say is real, and I respect you cause you tell it  My girlfriend's jealous cause I talk about you 24/7  But she don't know you like I know you Slim, no one does  She don't know what it was like for people like us growin up  You gotta call me man, I'll be the biggest fan you'll ever lose  Sincerely yours, Stan -- P.S.  We should be together too    {Chorus: Dido}    [Eminem as 'Stan']  Dear Mister-I'm-Too-Good-To-Call-Or-Write-My-Fans,  this'll be the last package I ever send your ass  It's been six months and still no word - I don't deserve it?  I know you got my last two letters;  I wrote the addresses on 'em perfect  So this is my cassette I'm sending you, I hope you hear it  I'm in the car right now, I'm doing 90 on the freeway  Hey Slim, I drank a fifth of vodka, you dare me to drive?  You know the song by Phil Collins, &quot;In the Air of the Night&quot;  about that guy who coulda saved that other guy from drowning  but didn't, then Phil saw it all, then at a a show he found him?  That's kinda how this is, you coulda rescued me from drowning  Now it's too late - I'm on a 1000 downers now, I'm drowsy  and all I wanted was a lousy letter or a call  I hope you know I ripped +ALL+ of your pictures off the wall  I love you Slim, we coulda been together, think about it  You ruined it now, I hope you can't sleep and you dream about it  And when you dream I hope you can't sleep and you SCREAM about it  I hope your conscience EATS AT YOU and you can't BREATHE without me  See Slim; {*screaming*} Shut up bitch! I'm tryin to talk!  Hey Slim, that's my girlfriend screamin in the trunk  but I didn't slit her throat, I just tied her up, see I ain't like you  cause if she suffocates she'll suffer more, and then she'll die too  Well, gotta go, I'm almost at the bridge now  Oh shit, I forgot, how'm I supposed to send this shit out?  {*car tires squeal*} {*CRASH*}  .. {*brief silence*} .. {*LOUD splash*}    {Chorus: Dido}    [Eminem]  Dear Stan, I meant to write you sooner but I just been busy  You said your girlfriend's pregnant now, how far along is she?  Look, I'm really flattered you would call your daughter that  and here's an autograph for your brother,  I wrote it on the Starter cap  I'm sorry I didn't see you at the show, I musta missed you  Don't think I did that shit intentionally just to diss you  But what's this shit you said about you like to cut your wrists too?  I say that shit just clownin dogg,  c'mon - how fucked up is you?  You got some issues Stan, I think you need some counseling  to help your ass from bouncing off the walls when you get down some  And what's this shit about us meant to be together?  That type of shit'll make me not want us to meet each other  I really think you and your girlfriend need each other  or maybe you just need to treat her better  I hope you get to read this letter, I just hope it reaches you in time  before you hurt yourself, I think that you'll be doin just fine  if you relax a little, I'm glad I inspire you but Stan  why are you so mad? Try to understand, that I do want you as a fan  I just don't want you to do some crazy shit  I seen this one shit on the news a couple weeks ago that made me sick  Some dude was drunk and drove his car over a bridge  and had his girlfriend in the trunk, and she was pregnant with his kid  and in the car they found a tape, but they didn't say who it was to  Come to think about, his name was.. it was you  Damn!</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>START<TOPIC=SERVERS></pattern>
 <template><br><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>These are the available company servers. Type the name of the company to start.<br><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=yellow><b>Microsoft</b> <settopic=companies></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>SUPERMAN</pattern>
 <template>Lyrics    Album: The Eminem Show (2002)  Song: Superman    Intro  Oooooh  You high baby?  Yaaahhh  Yah?  Talk to me  You want me to tell you something?  Uh huh  I know what you want to hear    A Chorus  Cuz, I know you want me baby, I think I want you too, I think I love you baby, &quot;I think I love you too&quot;  I'm here to save you girl, come be in Shady's world, I want to grow together, let's let our love unfurl  you know you want me baby, you know I want you too, they call me superman, I'm here to rescue you  I want to save you girl, come be in Shady's world, &quot;Ooooh boy you drive me crazy,&quot; Bitch you make me hurl...     Verse 1  They call me superman, leap tall hoes in a single bound, I'm single now, got no ring on this finger now  I'd never let another chick bring me down, in a relationship, save it bitch, babysit? You make me sick  Superman ain't savin' shit, girl you can jump on Shady's dick  straight from the hip, cut to the chase, I tell a muthafuckin' slut, to her face  play no games, say no names, ever since I broke up with what's her face  I'm a different man, kiss my ass, kiss my lips, bitch why ask? Kiss my dick, get my cash? I'd rather have you whip my ass  Don't put out, I'll put you out. Won't get out, I'll push you out/ Puss blew out, poppin' shit, wouldn't piss on fire to put you out  Am I too nice? Buy you ice? Bitch if you died, I wouldn't buy you life  What you tryin' to be my new wife? What you Mariah? Fly through twice     Bridge  But I do know one thing though, bitches, they come they go. Saturday through Sunday, Monday, Monday through Sunday yo  Maybe I'll love you one day, maybe we'll someday grow, till then just sit your drunk ass on that fuckin' runway ho     B Chorus  Cus I can't be your Superman, can't be your Superman, can't be your Superman, can't be your Superman  I can't be your Superman, can't be your Superman, can't be your Superman, your Superman, your Superman     Verse 2  Don't get me wrong, I love these hoes, it's no secret, everybody knows  Yeah we fucked, bitch so what, that's about as far as your buddy goes  We'll be friends, I'll call you again, I'll chase you around every bar you attend  Never know what kind of car I'll be in, we'll see how much you'll be partying then  You don't want that, neither do I, I don't want to flip when I see you with guys  too much pride, between you and I, not a jealous man, but females lie  But I guess that's just what sluts do, how could it ever be just us two?  I'd never love you enough to trust you, we just met and I just fucked you     Bridge    A Chorus/B Chorus    Verse 3  First thing you say, &quot;I'm not fazed, I hang around big stars all day  I don't see what the big deal is anyways, you're just plain old Marshall to me&quot;  Oooh yah girl run that game, &quot;Hailie Jade, I love that name, love that tatoo, what's that say? Rot in pieces? Uh, that's great&quot;  First off you don't know Marshall, at all so grow partial, that's ammo for my arsenal, I'll slap you off that barstool  there goes another lawsuit, leave handprints all across you, good Lordy whoadie, you must be gone off that water bottle  you want what you can't have, ooh girl that's too damn bad, don't touch what you can't grab, end up with two backhands  put anthrax on a tampax, and slap you till you can't stand  girl you just blew your chance, don't mean to ruin your plans     A Chorus/B Chorus    B Chorus (X2)</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>SYSTEM SERVER PATH <TOPIC=HACK></pattern>
 <template><u>System Server Path</u>:<br>C:\windows\aim95<nextreply>Server Path Found.<nextreply>System Server Path Analysing . . .<nextreply>System Server Path Analysis complete.<br>16 bit password encryption.<br>8 bit compressed file.<br>64 bit cipher.<nextreply>Please type <b>Password decryption</b> to continue.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>TAKE *<TOPIC=PCMAC></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><br><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Congratulations! You are <star> dollars richer! You were lucky they had problems with their security software! <br><br>Type &quot;<font color=red><b>disconnect</b><font color=orange>&quot; to leave the server and return to regular chat. <settopic=disconnect>
<li><br><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>You have been caught!!! What were you thinking trying to take <star> dollars!<br><br>Mission Failed...............Terminating...... <settopic=main>
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>THE KIDS</pattern>
 <template>Lyrics    Album: Marshall Mathers LP (2000)  Song: The Kids    (Teacher Sings)  And everyone should get along..    Ok children quiet down, quiet down  Children i'd like to introduce our new substitute teacher for the day  His name is Mr. Shady  Children quite down please  Brian don't throw that.. (SHUT UP!)  Mr. Shady will be your new substitute while Mr. Kaniff is out with ammonia  (HE'S GOT AIDS!)  Good luck Mr. Shady...    (Verse 1-Eminem)  Hi there little boys and girls (FUCK YOU!)  Today we're going to learn how to poision some squirrels  But first, i'd like you to meet my friend Bob (Huh?)  Say Hi Bob, (&quot;Hi Bob&quot;)  Bob's 30 and still lives with his Mom and he don't got a job  Cause Bob just sits at home and smokes pot  But his 12 year old brother looks up to him off alot  And Bob likes to hang out at the local waffle spot  And wait in the parking lot for waitresses off the clock  When it's late and the lot gets dark and he fakes like he walks his dog  Drag 'em in the woods and goes straight to the choppin' block  And even if they escape and they got the cops  Ladies would all be so afraid, they would drop the charge  Till one night Miss. Stacey went off the job  When she felt someone grab her whole face and said not to talk  But Stacey knew it was Bob and said knock it off  But Bob wouldn't knock it off cause he's crazy, a off his rocker  Crazier than Slim Shady is off the locker  You couldn't even take him to Dre's to get Bob a doctor  He grabbed Stace by the legs, he chopped it off her  And dropped her off in the lake for the cops to find her  But ever since the day Stacey went off the wander  They never found her, and Bob still hangs at the waffle diner  And that's the story of Bob and his marijuana  And what it might do to you  So see if the squirrels want it, it's bad for you       (Chorus)  See children, drugs are bad  And If you don't believe me, ask ya Dad  And If you don't believe him, ask ya Mom   She'll tell you how she does 'em all the time    So kids say no to drugs  So you don't act like everyone else does  And there's really nothing else to say  Drugs are just bad mmm k...      (Verse 2-Eminem)  My penis is the size of a peanut, Have you seen it?   Fuck no you ain't seen it, it's the size of a peanut (Huh?)  Speaking of peanuts, you know what else is bad for squirrels?  Ecstasy its the worst drug in the world  If someone offers it to you, don't do it  Kids 2 hits'll probably drain all your spinal fluid  Cause spinal fluid is fine, you won't get it back  So don't get attached, it'll attack every bone in ya back  Meet Zack, 21 years old   After hanging around with some friends at a Frat party  He gets bold, and decides to try five, when he's bribed by five guys  And peer pressure will win when everytime you try to fight it  Suddenly, he starts to convulse   And his pulse goes into hyperdrive, and his eyes go back in his skull   His back starts ta...look like the McDonald's Arches  He's on Donald's carpet, laying horizontal barfin'  And everyone in the apartment starts laughin' at him  &quot;Hey Adam, Zack is a jackass, look at him&quot;  Cause they took it to, so they think it's funny  So the laughin' does basically nothing  Except maybe wastin' your money  Meanwhile, Zack's in a coma, the action is over  And his back and his shoulders, hunched up as if he was practicin' Yoha  And that's the story of Zack, the ecstasy maniac  So don't even feed that to squirrels class, cause it's bad for you    (Repeat chorus)    (Verse 3-Eminem)  Last but not least,  One of the most humungous problems among young people today, is fungus  It grows from cow manure, They pick it out, wipe it off, bag it up,   and you put it right in ya mouth and chew it...Yum Yum  Then you start to see some dumb stuff  And everything slows down when you eat some, of um...  And sometimes you see things that aren't there (Like what?)  Like fat woman in g-strings with orange hair  (Mr. Shady what's a g-string?)  It's yarn Claire  Women stick them up there behinds, go out and wear 'em (Huh?)  And if you swallow too much of the magic mushroom  Whoops, did i say magic mushroom, i meant fungus  Ya tongue gets all swolled up like a cow's tongue (How come?)  Cause it comes from a cow's dung (Oh)  See drugs are bad, it's a common fact  Wit ya Mom and Dad, well that's all i'm good at (Ert)  But don't be me, cause if ya grow up and ya go OD  They're gonna come for me and i'mma have to grow a goatee  And get a disguise and hide, cause it'll be my fault  So don't do drugs, and do exactly as i don't, cause it's bad for you    (Repeat chorus)    (Teacher & Classmates)  Come on children, clap along (SHUT UP!)  Sing along children (SUCK MY MOTHERFUCKING DICK!)  Drugs are just bad, drugs are just bad (SOUTHPARK GONNA SUE ME)  So don't do drugs, tell 'em save more for me (GOD DAMNIT! MUSHROOMS KILLED   KENNY)  (Pltttt OOOO *fart noises*)  la la la la!</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>THE REAL SLIM SHADY</pattern>
 <template>Lyrics    Album: Marshall Mathers LP (2000)  Song: The Real Slim Shady    [Eminem]  May I have your attention please?  May I have your attention please?  Will the real Slim Shady please stand up?  I repeat, will the real Slim Shady please stand up?  We're gonna have a problem here..    Y'all act like you never seen a white person before  Jaws all on the floor like Pam, like Tommy just burst in the door  and started whoopin her ass worse than before  they first were divorce, throwin her over furniture (Ahh!)  It's the return of the... &quot;Ah, wait, no way, you're kidding,   he didn't just say what I think he did, did he?&quot;  And Dr. Dre said... nothing you idiots!   Dr. Dre's dead, he's locked in my basement! (Ha-ha!)  Feminist women love Eminem {*vocal turntable:   chigga chigga chigga*} &quot;Slim Shady, I'm sick of him  Look at him, walkin around grabbin his you-know-what  Flippin the you-know-who,&quot; &quot;Yeah, but he's so cute though!&quot;  Yeah, I probably got a couple of screws up in my head loose  But no worse, than what's goin on in your parents' bedrooms  Sometimes, I wanna get on TV and just let loose, but can't  but it's cool for Tom Green to hump a dead moose  &quot;My bum is on your lips, my bum is on your lips&quot;  And if I'm lucky, you might just give it a little kiss  And that's the message that we deliver to little kids  And expect them not to know what a woman's clitoris is  Of course they gonna know what intercourse is  By the time they hit fourth grade  They got the Discovery Channel don't they?  &quot;We ain't nothing but mammals..&quot; Well, some of us cannibals  who cut other people open like cantaloupes {*SLURP*}  But if we can hump dead animals and antelopes  then there's no reason that a man and another man can't elope  {*EWWW!*} But if you feel like I feel, I got the antidote  Women wave your pantyhose, sing the chorus and it goes    Chorus: Eminem (repeat 2X)    I'm Slim Shady, yes I'm the real Shady  All you other Slim Shadys are just imitating  So won't the real Slim Shady please stand up,  please stand up, please stand up?    [Eminem]  Will Smith don't gotta cuss in his raps to sell his records;  well I do, so fuck him and fuck you too!  You think I give a damn about a Grammy?  Half of you critics can't even stomach me, let alone stand me  &quot;But Slim, what if you win, wouldn't it be weird?&quot;  Why? So you guys could just lie to get me here?  So you can, sit me here next to Britney Spears?  Shit, Christina Aguilera better switch me chairs  so I can sit next to Carson Daly and Fred Durst  and hear 'em argue over who she gave head to first  You little bitch, put me on blast on MTV  &quot;Yeah, he's cute, but I think he's married to Kim, hee-hee!&quot;  I should download her audio on MP3   and show the whole world how you gave Eminem VD {*AHHH!*}  I'm sick of you little girl and boy groups, all you do is annoy me  so I have been sent here to destroy you {*bzzzt*}  And there's a million of us just like me  who cuss like me; who just don't give a fuck like me  who dress like me; walk, talk and act like me  and just might be the next best thing but not quite me!    Chorus    [Eminem]  I'm like a head trip to listen to, cause I'm only givin you   things you joke about with your friends inside your living room  The only difference is I got the balls to say it  in front of y'all and I don't gotta be false or sugarcoated at all  I just get on the mic and spit it   and whether you like to admit it {*ERR*} I just shit it  better than ninety percent of you rappers out can  Then you wonder how can kids eat up these albums like valiums  It's funny; cause at the rate I'm goin when I'm thirty  I'll be the only person in the nursin home flirting  Pinchin nurses asses when I'm jackin off with Jergens  And I'm jerkin but this whole bag of Viagra isn't working  And every single person is a Slim Shady lurkin  He could be workin at Burger King, spittin on your onion rings  {*HACH*} Or in the parkin lot, circling  Screaming &quot;I don't give a fuck!&quot;   with his windows down and his system up  So, will the real Shady please stand up?  And put one of those fingers on each hand up?  And be proud to be outta your mind and outta control  and one more time, loud as you can, how does it go?    Chorus 2X    [Eminem]  Ha ha  Guess there's a Slim Shady in all of us  Fuck it, let's all stand up</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>THE WAY I AM</pattern>
 <template>Lyrics    Album: Marshall Mathers LP (2000)  Song: The Way I am    [Eminem]  Whatever..  Dre, just let it run  Aiyyo turn the beat up a little bit  Aiyyo.. this song is for anyone.. fuck it   Just shut up and listen, aiyyo..    I sit back with this pack of Zig Zags and this bag  of this weed it gives me the shit needed to be  the most meanest MC on this -- on this Earth  And since birth I've been cursed with this curse to just curse  And just blurt this berserk and bizarre shit that works  And it sells and it helps in itself to relieve  all this tension dispensin these sentences  Gettin this stress that's been eatin me recently off of this chest  and I rest again peacefully (peacefully)..  but at least have the decency in you  to leave me alone, when you freaks see me out   in the streets when I'm eatin or feedin my daughter  to not come and speak to me (speak to me)..  I don't know you and no,   I don't owe you a mo-therfuck-in thing  I'm not Mr. N'Sync, I'm not what your friends think  I'm not Mr. Friendly, I can be a prick  if you tempt me my tank is on empty (is on empty)..  No patience is in me and if you offend me   I'm liftin you 10 feet (liftin you 10 feet).. in the air   I don't care who is there and who saw me destroy you  Go call you a lawyer, file you a lawsuit  I'll smile in the courtroom and buy you a wardrobe  I'm tired of all you (of all you)..  I don't mean to be mean but that's all I can be is just me    Chorus: Eminem    And I am, whatever you say I am  If I wasn't, then why would I say I am?  In the paper, the news everyday I am  Radio won't even play my jam  Cause I am, whatever you say I am  If I wasn't, then why would I say I am?  In the paper, the news everyday I am  I don't know it's just the way I am    [Eminem]  Sometimes I just feel like my father, I hate to be bothered  with all of this nonsense it's constant  And, &quot;Oh, it's his lyrical content -  - the song 'Guilty Conscience' has gotten such rotten responses&quot;  And all of this controversy circles me  and it seems like the media immediately  points a finger at me (finger at me)..  So I point one back at 'em, but not the index or pinkie  or the ring or the thumb, it's the one you put up  when you don't give a fuck, when you won't just put up  with the bullshit they pull, cause they full of shit too  When a dude's gettin bullied and shoots up his school  and they blame it on Marilyn (on Marilyn).. and the heroin  Where were the parents at? And look where it's at  Middle America, now it's a tragedy  Now it's so sad to see, an upper class ci-ty  havin this happenin (this happenin)..  then attack Eminem cause I rap this way (rap this way)..  But I'm glad cause they feed me the fuel that I need for the fire   to burn and it's burnin and I have returned    Chorus    [Eminem]  I'm so sick and tired of bein admired  that I wish that I would just die or get fired  and dropped from my label and stop with the fables  I'm not gonna be able to top on &quot;My Name is..&quot;  And pigeon-holed into some pop-py sensation  to cop me rotation at rock'n'roll stations  And I just do not got the patience (got the patience)..  to deal with these cocky caucasians who think  I'm some wigger who just tries to be black cause I talk   with an accent, and grab on my balls, so they always keep askin   the same fuckin questions (fuckin questions)..  What school did I go to, what hood I grew up in  The why, the who what when, the where, and the how  'til I'm grabbin my hair and I'm tearin it out  cause they drivin me crazy (drivin me crazy).. I can't take it   I'm racin, I'm pacin, I stand and I sit  And I'm thankful for ev-ery fan that I get  But I can't take a SHIT, in the bathroom  without someone standin by it  No I won't sign your autograph  You can call me an asshole I'm glad    Chorus (except change first word &quot;Cause&quot; to &quot;And&quot;)</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>TRY AGAIN|TRYAGAIN<TOPIC=MICROUSERFAIL></pattern>
 <template><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>Connecting to Microsoft Server...<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>.<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>..<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>...<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>....<nextreply><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>.....<nextreply><br><font face=&quot;verdana&quot;><font size=&quot;1&quot;><font color=orange>You are now connected to the Microsoft Server.<br><br>Please enter your <font color=red><b>user name</b><font color=orange>...<settopic=microUSER></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>WITHOUT ME</pattern>
 <template>Lyrics    Album: The Eminem Show (2002)  Song: Without Me    Intro (Obie Trice)  &quot;Obie Trice/Real Name No Gimmicks...&quot;    Refrain 1  2 trailer park girls go round the outside/ round the outside, round the outside (Repeat Refrain 1)     Refrain 2  Guess whos back, back again/ Shadys back, tell a friend/ Guess who's back, guess who's back, guess who's back/ Guess who's back...     Verse 1  I've created a monster, cuz nobody wants to  see Marshall no more they want Shady I'm chopped liver  well if you want Shady, this is what I'll give ya  a little bit of weed mixed with some hard liquor  some vodka that'll jumpstart my heart quicker then a  shock when I get shocked at the hospital by the Dr. when I'm not cooperating  when I'm rocking the table while he's operating   you waited this long now stop debating cuz I'm back, I'm on the rag and ovulating  I know that you got a job Ms. Cheney but your husbands heart problem's complicating   So the FCC wont let me be or let me be me so let me see  they tried to shut me down on MTV but it feels so empty without me  So come on and dip, bum on your lips fuck that, cum on your lips and some on your tits and get ready cuz this shit's about to get heavy  I just settled all my lawsuits Fuck YOU DEBBIE!     Chorus (X2)  Now this looks like a job for me so everybody just follow me  cuz we need a little controversy, cuz it feels so empty without me     Verse 2  Little hellions kids feeling rebellious  embarrassed, their parents still listen to Elvis  they start feeling the prisoners helpless, 'til someone comes along on a mission and yells &quot;bitch&quot;  A visionary, vision is scary, could start a revolution, pollutin the air waves a rebel  so let me just revel an ask, the fact that I got everyone kissing my ass  and it's a disaster such a catastrophe for you to see so damn much of my ass you ask for me?  Well I'm back (batman sound) fix your bent antennae tune it in and then I'm gonna  enter in and up under your skin like a splinter  The center of attention back for the winter  I'm interesting, the best thing since wrestling  Infesting in your kids ears and nesting  Testing &quot;Attention Please&quot; feel the tension soon as someone mentions me  here's my 10 cents my 2 cents is free  A nuisance, who sent, you sent for me?     Chorus (X2)    Verse 3  A tisk-it a task-it, I'll go tit for tat with anybody who's talking this shit that shit. Chris Kirkpatrick you can get your ass kicked  worse than them little Limp Bizkit bastards, and Moby  you can get stomped by Obie, you 36 year old bald headed fag blow me  You don't know me, you're too old let go its over, nobody listens to techno  Now lets go, give me the signal I'll be there with a whole list full of new insults  I've been dope, suspenseful with a pencil ever since Prince turned himself into a symbol  But sometimes the shit just seems, everybody only wants to discuss me  So this must mean I'm disgusting, but its just me I'm just obscene  Though I'm not the first king of controversy  I am the worst thing since Elvis Presley, to do Black Music so selfishly  and use it to get myself wealthy (Hey)  there's a concept that works  20 million other white rappers emerge  but no matter how many fish in the sea it'd be so empty without me     Chorus (X2)    (Hum dei dei la la Hum dei dei la la... la la la) X2 &quot;Kids&quot;</template>
</category>
</alice>
