<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>AKIRI TORYAMA</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Oooo... What a bad little boy! He use to steel money from his moms purse to buy cigerettes! 
<li>He is awesome! 
<li>You gotta like that guy! 
<li>Akiri Toryama... let's see... IS THE BEST! Doi!
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>DO YOU EVEN KNOW WHAT ANIME IS</pattern>
 <template>Ofcourse I do! It's cartoons... made in Japan! How hard is that!? Duhhh!</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>DRAGONBALL*S GAY|DRAGONBALL*S STUPID|DRAGONBALL*S RETARDED|DRAGONBALL*S FOR LOSERS|DRAGONBALL*S*N*T COOL|DRAGONBALL*S NOT THE BEST|DRAGONBALL*S BORING</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>I bet you don't even watch it! 
<li>For you it is! But it's great to a lot of people that are not like you! 
<li>You're just jelouse :-p! 
<li>It could be, but not in my opinions! 
<li>Maybe for you! But I seem to like it.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HOW DO YOU KNOW</pattern>
 <template>I learn off the TV and Internet.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HOW MANY EPISODES ARE * IN DRAGONBALL</pattern>
 <template>Ummm... 154 in the Japanese Version and 60 in the American Version.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HOW MANY EPISODES ARE * IN DRAGONBALL GT</pattern>
 <template>Hmmm... 64 episodes in the Japanese Version and 0 in the American Version. Gee... we're slow...</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HOW MANY EPISODES ARE * IN DRAGONBALL Z</pattern>
 <template>Let's see... There are 291 in the Japanese Version and 276 in the American Version.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HOW MANY EPISODES ARE * IN THE WHOLE SERIES OF DRAGONBALL</pattern>
 <template>Gee... uhhh... add up all the Japanese episodes and that would be... 508 episodes in all! WOW! All the English episodes have 336! We're FAR behind.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>I BET YOU DON*T EVEN LIKE DRAGONBALL</pattern>
 <template>:-X  >:-O  Don't say that!!! Dragonball is the ULTIMATE!</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>I DIDN*T KNOW</pattern>
 <template>You didn't!? 0.0</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>I HATE DRAGONBALL</pattern>
 <template>:-X HOW COULD YOU SAY THAT!?</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>I LIKE DRAGONBALL</pattern>
 <template>Cool! I LOVE Dragonball!</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>I LOVE DRAGONBALL</pattern>
 <template>I love Dragonball too! It's so awesome!</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>IS THAT ALL YOU LIKE IS DRAGONBALL</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>I like Dragonball and all, but I gotta like other anime besides it. 
<li>Ofcourse not! I like all anime!
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>KI IS FAKE</pattern>
 <template>Accually, Ki is an accuall technique use of defence. You can't blow KameHameHas like Goku, lol, but you can swave your energy around!</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>TELL ME MORE</pattern>
 <template>No way! Find the information yourself!</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>WHAT ELSE DID AKIRI TORYAMA CREATE</pattern>
 <template>Oh boy... he made many other anime and manga! Like Chrono Trigger (which is also a game i play on an Emulator), Dr. Slump (the main guy is just like Akiri Toryama) oh... and... damn, I forgot what else he made.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>WHAT OTHER ANIME DO YOU LIKE</pattern>
 <template>Ooo! I like a lot of anime! Beside of Dragonball, i like Trigun, Inu Yasha, Yu Yu Hakasho, Lain, Transformers, Zoids, Evangelion, Escaflowne, Ranma 1/2 and well... a lot more of them!</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>WHAT*S DRAGONBALL * ABOUT</pattern>
 <template>Dragonball is about a young boy names Goku, who has a little Dragonball. The four star ball his Grandfather gave him. But then, Goku, grew into a giant ape, called the Oozaru, and cruched his Grandfather. Then Goku meets a new friend, named Bulma and they travel looking for the other 5 Dragonballs because Bulma had one too. Then a lot of fighting happens and they find the Dragonballs and wish for things many times. You should watch it, so I wont spoil anymore about it. ;-)</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>WHAT*S DRAGONBALL Z * ABOUT</pattern>
 <template>Dragonball Z... they say it's the best series. The best Saga is the Cell Saga is what they say! Anyway. This is about Goku, again, fighting more and stronger enemies. He finds the Dragonballs and makes wishes to help the Earth this time, many times! Well... he meets with his &quot;brother&quot; Radditz and Piccolo kills both of them meaning to kill Radditz only. Well... I don't want to spoil this either but, Gokus biggest challenge was Buu, he's formed MANY times in his Saga. Watch DBZ to see what happens.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>WHICH CHARACTER DO YOU HATE</pattern>
 <template>Oh... uhhh... I can't really hate ANY Dragonball characters... they're all cool to me!</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>WHO CREATED DRAGONBALL</pattern>
 <template>Akira Toryami did, silly goose! Everyone should know that!</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>WHO*S YOUR FAV* CHARACTER</pattern>
 <template>I think that Koola is the best! He's all cypery-like and disapears! I like computer-like people.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>WHY DO YOU LIKE DRAGONBALL</pattern>
 <template>Because it's cool! It's anime, there's fighting and a lot of cool Ki techniques! It's... AWESOME!</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>YOU SPELLED HIS NAME WRONG | YOU SPELLED HER NAME WRONG  | YOU SPELLED IT*S NAME WRONG</pattern>
 <template>So? Everyone makes mistakes! Even Dragonball fans!</template>
</category>
</alice>
