<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>BIO</pattern>
 <template>In '99, the spore called Slipknot exploded. Now, in 2001, the infestation continues.    Hailing from the 'middle of nowhere'- Des Moines, Iowa - they are nine men in nine different masks united with one common goal - world domination. Fortified with an arsenal of blistering music saturated with screams, drums, searing riffs, sampling, scratches and melody, Slipknot's music runs the scale from eerily thought-provoking to utterly terrifying.   Slipknot, collectively, are DJ Sid Wilson, drummer Joey Jordison, bassist Paul Gray, percussionist Chris Fehn, guitarist James Root, sampler Craig Jones, percussionist Shawn Crahan, guitarist Mick Thomson and lead singer Corey Taylor (also known as 012345678, respectively). once Slipknot was unleashed on the world, they were &quot;the most talked-about band&quot; (Rolling Stone) of that year's (1999) Ozzfest.   Slipknot has been called &quot;the best live band in ten years&quot; (Lou Brutus, Hard Drive), but if you've never seen it, you wouldn't believe it. Millions of people can attest to that throughout the world. A murderous, rampaging free-for-all that threatens to engulf the entire venue, Slipknot is a sonic assault on all five senses that makes you wish you had a sixth. Voted &quot;Best International Live Act&quot; by Kerrang! Magazine, there is no stopping the madness spread by their masterful art of live performance.    YOU HAVE BEEN WARNED..</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>DISCOGRAPHY</pattern>
 <template>discography  1996 - &quot;Mate, Feed, Kill, Repeat&quot;     LP released by the band themselves. Good Luck finding it if you try!       Label: Self Released            1999 - &quot;Slipknot&quot;     Legendary First LP on Roadrunner. Though I am sure you all know, the master on the original release was later modified to exclude the tracks &quot;Purity&quot; and &quot;Frail Limb Nursery&quot; and instead added &quot;Me Inside&quot;.       Label: Roadrunner Records            1999 - &quot;Slipknot&quot;     Digi Version. IMPORT ONLY.       Label: Roadrunner Records            1999 - &quot;Welcome To Our Neighborhood&quot;     VHS home video       Label: Roadrunner Records            2000 - &quot;Wait & Bleed&quot;     Import Single Only.       Label: Roadrunner Records            2000 - &quot;Spit It Out&quot;     Import Single Only.       Label: Roadrunner Records            2000 - &quot;Slipknot&quot;     Digi Version, U.S. Release Only. Yes, there was a Eurpean digi version released in 1999, however this U.S. digi version includes new inside artwork as well as additional tracks (demos, remixes, and even something never heard before).       Label: Roadrunner Records            2001 - &quot;Iowa&qu</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HELLO</pattern>
 <template>hey whats up you can type slipknot menu to get some slipknot info</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HEY</pattern>
 <template>hey whats up you can type slipknot menu to get some slipknot info</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HI</pattern>
 <template>hey whats up you can type slipknot menu to get some slipknot info</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HOLA</pattern>
 <template>hey whats up you can type slipknot menu to get some slipknot info</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>LINKS</pattern>
 <template>http://www.geocities.com/slipknotzz5/home  http://www.slipknot1.com  http://www.dragmedown.com  http://www.myplague.cjb.net  http://www.blackboat.tk  http://www.newabortion.com  http://www.slipknotcpd.com  http://www.slipknot-freaks.de  http://www.sickness1.com</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>MEMBERS</pattern>
 <template>Members:  - Corey #8 - Vocals      - Mick #7 - Guitar      - Sid #0 - Turntables      - Shawn #6 - Custom Percussion      - Paul #2 - Bass      - Joey #1 - Drums      - Chris #3 - Custom Percussion      - James #4 - Guitar      - Craig #5 - Samples/Media</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>NEWS</pattern>
 <template>BEST MOVIE OF ALL TIME - 6.13.2002        During a discussion with Joey Jordison about the upcoming Murderdolls release, the subject got diverted to cars...and that is where we pick up with the conversation, for a bit of Joey's insight:    Joey - ...it's definitely the Phantasm car. You've seen that movie?    Roadrunner - The Phantasm what? (spoken with slight hesitation)    Joey - The Phantasm car. You've never seen Phantasm? (spoken with 70 strict authority and 30 disbelief)    Roadrunner - Noooo...(spoken with even more hesitation, and softer)    Joey - You're killing me! (spoken loud, very loud...with more authority)    Roadrunner - ahhh, no.    Joey - Ahhh man, go rent it - that's one of the best horror movies of all time. That's what we're referring to in the song &quot;Dead In Hollywood&quot;, 'HEY TALL MAN, JUST TAKE MY HAND, AND LEAD ME TO YOUR RED PLANET.'    Roadrunner - uh huh.    Joey - The tall man's the freakin', basically one of the most classic horror film characters in all history. But that's the main car that's driven in there, a '72 Barracuda Hemi.    To hear exactly what Joey is talking about, be sure to check out the MP3 at http://www.roadrunnerrecords.com/shared/downloads/Murderdolls/DeadInHollywood.mp3    As far as the movie Phantasm goes, we leave you with its tagline, &quot;If this</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>SLIPKNOT MENU</pattern>
 <template>type what u want        [bio]   [discography]    [links]   [members]   [news]  [tours]</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>SLIPKNOTS GAY</pattern>
 <template>NO BUT IM NOT SURE ABOUT U</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>TOURS</pattern>
 <template>8/20/2002   Vienio De Minho   . - ., Portugal        8/23/2002   Leeds Festival   - Leeds, United Kingdom        8/24/2002   Glasgow Festival   . - Glasgow, United Kingdom        8/25/2002   Reading Festival   - Reading, United Kingdom        8/29/2002   2 days A Week   . - Wiesen, Austria</template>
</category>
</alice>
