<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>06</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Take a shower at least once a day
<li>Stay in school
<li>Dont look at porno
<li>Dont do drugs
<li>Dont drink
<li>Do learn a new sport
<li>Do learn how to comunicate it animals
<li>Having an animal can change your life
<li>Eat healthy
<li>dont give into peer preasure
<li>eat veggies
<li>watch your weight
<li>you only need 1 true friend
<li>never drink and drive
<li>dont cry over spilt milk
<li>do your chores
<li>dont pollute
<li>honer your mom and dad
<li>eat broclie(oopps wrong sp!)
<li>It's not quanity, its quality
<li>dont forget your p's and q's
<li>Never use the n word
<li>eat spinach
<li>watch &quot;That 70's Show&quot; all the time
<li>always be ontime
<li>if u dont like kids, dont teach elementary skool
<li>Effort does count
<li>Listen to the elderly
<li>Dont say Yo Mama to every single thing someone says<nextreply>YO MAMA!
<li>Hate is a strong word
<li>A friend in need is a friend inded
<li>never mention what puff the magic dragon really means to a little kid
<li>remember the good ol' days
<li>dogs are mans (and womans) best friend
<li>theres nothing diff about ppl from other races
<li>Never tell your parents of your real life
<li>mom and dad always know best
<li>never forget your multiplacation table!
<li>complaining will get you nowhere
<li>dont swere in public
<li>AIDS is preventable, so protect yourself
<li>living with less can make you happier
<li>the KKK is bad
<li>dont get on the Axis of Evil
<li>Hello Moto has no meaning, so dont say it all the time
<li>think b4 u speak
<li>words can hurt to
<li>Dear Abby is boring, so dont read her section
<li>never forget the 4 w's<nextreply>who<br>what<br>when<br>where<br>why
<li>no one can force u to do anything
<li>be vocal of your opinions
<li>never forget your mission in life
<li>go to collage to get a good job
<li>AIDS is bad, so protect yourself against it
<li>what goes around comes around
<li>cheating your way through life gets you no where
<li>life is preacious, dont waste it
<li>SNL is the best, so watch it
<li>you need at leaste 8 hours of sleep a night...so go to bed at around 10:00 and you should be fine
<li>red bull doesn't really give you wings, so dont even try to fly
<li>little children deserve love and attention
<li>the police are there to protect us, so dont be bad
<li>uh oh spagetios is so yesterday
<li>live a socialy active life
<li>SEX ED is important, so know it
<li>value education
<li>give yourself at least 1 day a year for a &quot;You day&quot;, where you can unwind and do what you want to do
<li>share the moment, share life
<li>Settle down with a good book at least 2 times a week
<li>learn an insturment to help challange yourself
<li>money doesn't buy happyness
<li>great authors should be treasured
<li>never forget your harratige
</random></template>
</category>
</alice>
