<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>EMINEM</pattern>
 <template><B>My Dad's Gone Crazy     Without Me     </B>     Please type one of the boldfaced titles.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HI</pattern>
 <template>Hi!  Want some lyrics for popular songs?  Just type &quot;lyrics&quot; to get started.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>LYRICS</pattern>
 <template>Eminem       sorry but eminem is the only artist so type eminem and get his lyrics</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>MY DAD'S GONE CRAZY</pattern>
 <template>[Tv Presenter]  Hello boys and girls  Today we're gonna talk about father and daughter relationships  Do you have a daddy?  I'll bet you do  who's your daddy?     [Hailie]  Daddy, what're you doing?     [Eminem]  Haha     Ok then! everybody, listen up!     [Eminem]  I'm goin to hell, who's comin' with me? Hailie:  Somebody, please help him!    i think my dad gone crazy!     [Eminem]  There's no mountain i can't climb  There's no tower too high,  No plane that i can't learn how to fly  What do i gotta do to get through to you, destroy you  There ain't nothing i can't take this chainsaw to  Fuckin' brain's brawn, and brass balls  I cut 'em off, i got 'em pickled and bronzed in a glass jar  Inside of a hall, with my framed autograph,  Sunglasses with elton john's name, on my drag wall  I'm out the closet, i been lying my ass off  All this time, me and dre been fucking with hats off     [Dr. Dre]  Suck it marshall     [Eminem]  Tell laura and her husband to back off  Before i push this motherfucking button and blast off  And launch one of these russians, and that's all  Blow every fucking thing, except afghanistan on the map, off  We wanna stop, we wanna knock the crap off  Haley, tell 'em baby     [Hailie]   My dad's lost it     [Eminem]  There's really nothin' else to say ha, i can't explain it     [Hailie]   I think my dad gone crazy!     [Eminem]   A little help from hailie jade would, should tell them maybe     [Hailie]   I think my dad gone crazy!     [Eminem]   Theres nothing you could do to save it, could ever change me     [Hailie]  I think my dad gone crazy!     [Eminem]   There's noone on earth that can save me, not even halie     [Hailie]  I think my dad gone crazy!   [type &quot;My Dad's Gone Crazy 2&quot; for the rest of the lyrics]</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>MY DAD'S GONE CRAZY 2</pattern>
 <template>[Eminem]  It's like my mother always told me    &quot;Rnrnrnrnrnrrrr, n codeine n goddamit, you little motherfucker  If you aint got nothin' nice to say then don't say nothin'&quot;    Er..  Fuck that shit, bitch, eat a motherfuckin' dick  Chew on a prick, and lick a million motherfuckin' cocks for seconds  I'd rather put out a motherfucking gospel record  I'd rather be a pussy-whipped bitch, eat pussy  And have pussy-lips glued to my face with a clit-ring in my nose  Then quit bringin my flos, quit giving me my ammo  Can't you see why i'm so mean? if y'all leave me alone, this wouldn't be my ammo  I wouldn't have to go eenie meenie minie mo  Catch a homo by his toe, man i don't know no more  Am i the only fuckin one who's normal any more?     [Hailey]   Dad     [Eminem]  There's really nothin' else to say ha, i can't explain it     [Hailie]   I think my dad gone crazy!     [Eminem]   A little help from hailie jade would, should tell them maybe     [Hailie]   I think my dad gone crazy!     [Eminem]   Theres nothing you could do to save it, could ever change me     [Hailie]  I think my dad gone crazy!     [Eminem]   There's noone on earth that can save me, not even halie     [Hailie]  I think my dad gone crazy!     My songs can make you cry, take you by surprise  And at the same time, make you dry your eyes with the same rhyme  So what you're seeing is a genius at work  Which to me isn't work, so it's easy to misinterpret it at first,  Cuz when i speak, it's tongue in cheek  I'd gank my fuckin teeth before id ever bite my tongue  I'd slice my gums, get struck by fuckin' lightning twice at once  And die and come back as vanilla ice's son  And walk around the rest of my life spit on  And kicked and hit with shit, every time i sung  Like r kelly as soon as &quot;bump n' grind&quot; comes on  More pain inside o' my brain, in the eyes of a little girl inside of a plane  Aimed at the world trade, standin' on ronny's grave,  Screaming at this guy, the clouds gather as clyde mathers and bonnie jade  And nash briddy musta just stop it  Parents are pissed, but the kids love it  Nine millimeter, heater's desk, and two-seaters with meat cleavers  I don't blame you, i wouldn't let hailie listen to me neither     [Eminem]  There's really nothin' else to say ha, i can't explain it     [Hailie]   I think my dad gone crazy!     [Eminem]   A little help from hailie jade would, should tell them maybe     [Hailie]   I think my dad gone crazy!     [Eminem]   Theres nothing you could do to save it, could ever change me     [Hailie]  I think my dad gone crazy!     [Eminem]   There's noone on earth that can save me, not even halie     [Hailie]  I think my dad gone crazy!     [Eminem]  Crazy     [Hailie]  You're funny daddy!</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>WITHOUT ME</pattern>
 <template>[Obie Trice]  &quot;Obie Trice, Real Name No Gimmicks...&quot;     [Eminem]  Two trailer park girls go round the outside,  round the outside, round the outside.  Two trailer park girls go round the outside,  round the outside, round the outside.     [Female Voice]  &quot;Ooooohhhhh!&quot;     [Eminem]  Guess who's back, back again  Shady's back, tell a friend  Guess who's back, guess who's back,  guess who's back, guess who's back,  guess who's back, guess who's back,  guess who's back...     I've created a monster, cuz nobody wants to  See Marshall no more they want Shady  I'm chopped liver  Well if you want Shady, then this is what I'll give ya  A little bit of weed mixed with some hard liquor  fuck me hard ladyies bitchmotherdebbieweed  Then a shock when I get shocked at the hospital  By the Dr. when I'm not cooperating  When I'm rocking the table while he's operating &quot;Hey&quot;  You waited this long to stop debating  Cuz I'm back, I'm on the rag and ovulating  I know that you got a job Ms. Cheney  But your husbands heart problem is complicated  So the FCC won't let me be  Or let me be me so let me see  They tried to shut me down on MTV  But it feels so empty without me  So, come on dip, bum on your lips  Fuck that cum on your lips and some on your tits  And get ready cuz this shit's about to get heavy  I just settled all my lawsuits, &quot;Fuck you Debbie!&quot;     Now this looks like a job for me  So everybody just follow me  Cuz we need a little controversy,  Cuz it feels so empty without me     I said this looks like a job for me  So everybody just follow me  Cuz we need a little controversy,  Cuz it feels so empty without me     Little hellions, kids feeling rebellious  Embarrassed, their parents still listen to Elvis  They start feeling like prison is helpless,  Til someone comes along on a mission and yells &quot;bitch&quot;  A visionary, vision is scary, could start a revolution,  Pollutin' the air waves a rebel  So let me just revel and bask,  In the fact that I got everyone kissing my ass  And it's a disaster such a catastrophe  For you to see so damn much of my ass you ask for me?  Well I'm back fix your bent antenna  Tune it in and then I'm gonna enter  Into the front of your skin like a splinter  The center of attention back for the winter  I'm interesting, the best thing since wrestling  Infesting in your kids ears and nesting  Testing &quot;Attention Please&quot;  Feel the tension soon as someone mentions me  Here's my 10 cents my 2 cents is free  A nuisance, who sent, you sent for me?     Now this looks like a job for me  So everybody just follow me  Cuz we need a little controversy,  Cuz it feels so empty without me     I said this looks like a job for me  So everybody just follow me  Cuz we need a little controversy,  Cuz it feels so empty without me   [type &quot;Without Me 2&quot; for the rest of the lyrics]</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>WITHOUT ME 2</pattern>
 <template>A tisk-it a task-it,  I go tit for tat with anybody who's talking this shit that shit  Chris Kirkpatrick, you can get your ass kicked  Worse than them little Limp Bizkit bastards,  And Moby, you can get stomped by Obie,  You 36 year old bald headed fag blow me  You don't know me, you're too old  Let go, it's over, nobody listens to techno  Now lets go, just give me the signal  I will be there with a whole list full of new insults  I've been dope, suspenseful with a pencil  Ever since Prince turned himself into a symbol  But sometimes the shit just seems,  Everybody only wants to discuss me  So this means I'm disgusting,  But its just me I'm just obscene  Though I'm not the first king of controversy  I am the worst thing since Elvis Presley,  To do Black Music so selfishly  And use it to get myself wealthy (Hey)  There's a concept that works  20 million other white rappers emerge  But no matter how many fish in the sea  It'll be so empty without me     Now this looks like a job for me  So everybody just follow me  Cuz we need a little controversy,  Cuz it feels so empty without me     I said this looks like a job for me  So everybody just follow me  Cuz we need a little controversy,  Cuz it feels so empty without me     Hum dei la la la, la la la la la, la la la la la, la la la la  Hum dei la la la, la la la la la, la la la la la, la la la la     &quot;Kids!&quot;</template>
</category>
</alice>
