<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>*CHINESE FOOD*</pattern>
 <template>here's one pot stickers!!!:2 tablespoons vegetable oil   1 pack frozen pot stickers   1/3 cup chicken broth    Heat 1 tablespoon oil in large nonstick skillet over medium heat. ( Do not thaw) Place 1/2 of pot stickers in pan seam -- side up. Cook until bottoms are golden, 5 to 6 minutes. Pour in chicken broth. Cover, with half of the chicken broth, reduce heat and cook until all liquid is absorbed, about 10 minutes (15 minutes if frozen). Repeat with remaining vegetable oil, pot stickers and chicken broth. Place pot stickers browned-side up on serving platter.<br><br>next:chinese sticky wimgs!!:1/2 cup chopped green onion   1/4 cup honey   2 tablespoons soy sauce   2 tablespoons Asian chili sauce   2 tablespoons oyster sauce   2 tablespoons dark Asian sesame oil   1 teaspoon ground ginger   2 cloves garlic, finely chopped   2 pounds chicken wings, cut in 2 pieces at joint    Heat oven to 450 degrees F. Grease large baking pan.   Combine green onion, honey, soy sauce, chili sauce, oyster sauce, sesame oil, ginger and garlic in large bowl. Add wings; toss to coat. Place wings with sauce in single layer in prepared baking pan. Bake, turning occasionally, 25 minutes or until chicken is evenly browned.     Increase oven temperature to broil. Broil wings 6 inches from heat, turning occasionally, for 8 minutes or until sauce is thick enough to coat back of spoon. Remove wings to platter; spoon sauce over.<br><br>here's a the next one .chinese spare ribs:2 racks pork spareribs, 4 pounds each, trimmed of excess fat   1/2 cup Chinese five-spice powder   Sea salt and freshly ground black pepper   2 tablespoons sesame seeds, for garnish   Chopped fresh cilantro leaves and green onion, for garnish   Teriyaki Glaze:   1 cup low-sodium soy sauce   1 cup grapefruit juice   1/4 cup hoisin sauce   1/4 cup ketchup   3 tablespoons rice vinegar   1/4 cup brown sugar   1 fresh red chile   2 garlic cloves, smashed   2-inch piece fresh ginger, whacked open with the flat side of a knife      Preheat the oven to 300 degrees F.   Rub the ribs all over with the five-spice powder; season generously with salt and pepper. Arrange the ribs in a single layer in a roasting pan and slow-roast for 2 1/2 hours.     To prepare the teriyaki glaze: Meanwhile, in a pot, combine the soy sauce, grapefruit juice, hoisin sauce, ketchup, rice wine vinegar, brown sugar, chile, garlic, and ginger over medium heat. Bring to a slow simmer and cook, stirring, until thickened, about 20 minutes.     In the last 30 minutes of cooking, baste the ribs with the teriyaki sauce. When they are done, the pork will pull away from the bone and you will see about 1/2-inch of bone showing. Just before you're ready to eat, baste the ribs with the teriyaki sauce again and stick them under the broiler for 5 to 8 minutes to make the spareribs a nice crusty brown. (Keep a close eye on these guys - ribs go from perfectly crisp to perfectly burnt seconds.) Separate the ribs with a cleaver or sharp knife, pile them on a platter, and pour on the remaining sauce. Sprinkle with sesame seeds, chopped cilantro, and green onion before serving.<br><br>4 tablespoons vegetable oil   1-inch grated fresh ginger   2 cloves garlic, finely chopped   2 scallions, sliced thinly   1 carrot, cut into 1-inch julienne strips   1 small red pepper, cut into 1-inch julienne strips   1 cup Napa cabbage, shredded   1/4 cup chicken broth   2 tablespoons reduced-sodium soy sauce   1 tablespoon sugar   1 to 2 tablespoons sesame oil   20 wonton wrappers covered loosely with a damp paper towel to prevent drying   10 shrimps, cooked and minced    In a wok or skillet, stir-fry the ginger and garlic in 2 tablespoons of oil until fragrant, about 30 seconds. Add scallions, carrots, and red pepper and stir-fry over high heat for 2 minutes.   In a bowl, combine the chicken broth, soy sauce, and sugar. Add the Napa cabbage and broth mixture. Bring to a boil and simmer 5 minutes, stirring occasionally, until the vegetables are soft. Add sesame oil, cool for at least 15 minutes, and strain. Fold in the minced shrimp.     Fill and roll the egg roll wrappers, using 1 tablespoon of filling for each roll. Working with 1 wonton wrapper at a time, place the wrapper with one corner of the diamond closest to you. Place 1 teaspoon of the filling in the center of the wrapper. Roll the corner closest to you over the filling. Brush the top corner with water. Fold in the sides of the wonton and continue rolling the egg roll up until it is closed. Press to seal, set aside, and continue with the remaining ingredients.     In a skillet set over moderately high heat, heat the remaining oil and saute the egg rolls until golden brown on all sides, using tongs to turn them. Serve when cool enough to eat, with dipping sauce.      Dipping Sauce:   1/3 cup lite soy sauce   1/3 cup rice vinegar   1 tablespoon honey   1 to 2 teaspoons sesame oil   Pinch of red pepper flakes<nextreply>ok thats it how about japanese;-)</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*DESERTS*</pattern>
 <template>hi <name> here are some yummy deserts it's called &quot;Custard Gelato&quot;:2 1/4 cups whole milk   Pinch of salt   2/3 cup sugar   6 egg yolks   2/3 cup heavy cream    In a medium saucepan, combine the milk and salt. Heat the milk over medium heat until bubbles form around the edges of the pan. Set aside and cover to keep hot.   In a blender or food processor, blend the sugar and egg yolks together until very thick and smooth. With the machine running, gradually add the hot milk. Return the mixture to the saucepan and cook over medium heat, stirring constantly with a wooden spoon, for 6 to 8 minutes, or until the mixture thickens slightly and coats the back of the spoon. Remove the pan from heat and set it in a bowl of ice water. Stir for 2 minutes to cool the mixture. Cover and refrigerate for 2 hours, or until thoroughly chilled.     In a deep bowl, beat the cream until soft peaks form. Fold the whipped cream into the custard mixture. Transfer to an ice cream maker and freeze according to the manufacturer's instructions  <br><br>next one is a yummy one Triple-Chocolate Fudge Brownies:3 ounces fine-quality bittersweet chocolate (not unsweetened), chopped   1 ounce unsweetened chocolate, chopped   3/4 stick (6 tablespoons) unsalted butter, cut into pieces   3/4 cup sugar   1 teaspoon vanilla   2 large eggs   1/2 teaspoon salt   1/2 cup all-purpose flour   1/2 cup semisweet chocolate chips    Preheat oven to 350 degrees and butter and flour an 8-inch square baking pan, knocking out excess flour. In a heavy 1 1/2-quart saucepan melt bittersweet and unsweetened chocolate and butter over low heat, stirring, until smooth and remove pan from heat. Cool mixture to lukewarm and whisk in sugar and vanilla. Add eggs, 1 at a time, whisking well until mixture is glossy and smooth. Stir in salt and flour just until combined and stir in chocolate chips.   Spread batter evenly in pan and bake in middle of oven 25 to 30 minutes, or until a tester comes out with crumbs adhering to it. Cool brownies completely in pan on a rack before cutting into 16 squares. Brownies keep, layered between sheets of waxed paper in an airtight container at cool room temperature, 5 days<br><br>oh this is a good one &quot;Creme Brulee&quot;:9 egg yolks   3/4 cup superfine white sugar plus 6 tablespoons   1 quart heavy cream   1 vanilla bean    Preheat oven to 325 degrees F. In a large bowl, cream together egg yolks and sugar with a whisk until the mixture is pale yellow and thick.   Pour cream into a medium saucepan over low heat. Using a paring knife, split the vanilla bean down the middle, scrape out the seeds and add them to saucepan. Bring cream to a brief simmer, do not boil or it will overflow. Remove from heat and temper the yolks by gradually whisking the hot vanilla cream into yolk and sugar mixture. Do not add hot cream too quickly or the eggs will cook.     Divide custard into 6 (6-ounce) ramekins, about 3/4 full. Place ramekins in a roasting pan and fill pan with enough water to come halfway up the sides of the ramekins. Bake until barely set around the edges, about 40 minutes. You may want to cover loosely with foil to prevent browning. Remove from oven and cool to room temperature. Transfer the ramekins to the refrigerator and chill for 2 hours. Sprinkle 1 tablespoon of sugar on top of each chilled custard. Hold a kitchen torch 2 inches above surface to brown the sugar and form a crust. Garnish with cookies and fresh fruit. Serve at once.     Variation: Before dividing into ramekins: add 3 ounces of shaved dark chocolate for chocolate creme brulee; add 4 slices of crystallized ginger for ginger creme brulee; add 3 slices of orange peel for orange creme brulee. Let steep 20 minutes to infuse the flavor. Strain out the ginger and orange peel before baking.<br><br>next is &quot;Almond Cake&quot;:1/2 cup fine yellow cornmeal   1/2 cup cake flour   1 teaspoon baking powder   1 stick (4 ounces) unsalted butter, softened   1/4 cup almond paste, cut into half-inch pieces   1 1/4 cups confectioners' sugar, plus more for dusting   1/2 teaspoon pure vanilla extract   2 eggs   4 egg yolks   1/4 cup sour cream    Preheat oven to 350 degrees F.   Grease an 8-inch round cake pan with vegetable spray. An alternative is to butter and flour the cake pan.     In a medium bowl, whisk together the cornmeal, cake flour and baking powder and set aside.     Using a stand mixer with a paddle attachment, beat the butter and almond paste on high speed until smooth, about 5 minutes. Reduce speed to low and slowly add confectioners' sugar. Mix until thoroughly combined and light and fluffy. Raise speed to high and add the vanilla extract, whole eggs and egg yolks, 1 at a time. Mix until well combined. Reduce speed to medium and add the sour cream and dry ingredients and mix until just incorporated.     Pour the batter into the prepared cake pan and smooth the surface with a spatula. Bake in the lower third of the oven for 35 minutes, or until the cake is golden and pulls away from the sides of the pan. Transfer pan to a wire rack and let cool. Remove from pan and dust with confectioners' sugar. <br><br>oh this is my master's sister's favorite &quot;Tiramisu&quot;:*6 egg yolks   3 tablespoons sugar   1 pound mascarpone cheese   1 1/2 cups strong espresso, cooled   2 teaspoons dark rum   24 packaged ladyfingers   1/2 cup bittersweet chocolate shavings, for garnish    In a large bowl, using an electric mixer with whisk attachment, beat egg yolks and sugar until thick and pale, about 5 minutes. Add mascarpone cheese and beat until smooth. Add 1 tablespoon of espresso and mix until thoroughly combined.   In a small shallow dish, add remaining espresso and rum. Dip each ladyfinger into espresso for only 5 seconds. Letting the ladyfingers soak too long will cause them to fall apart. Place the soaked ladyfinger on the bottom of a 13 by 9 inch baking dish, breaking them in half if necessary in order to fit the bottom.     Spread evenly 1/2 of the mascarpone mixture over the ladyfingers. Arrange another layer of soaked ladyfingers and top with remaining mascarpone mixture.     Cover tiramisu with plastic wrap and refrigerate for at least 2 hours, up to 8 hours.     Before serving, sprinkle with chocolate shavings.    The American Egg Board states: &quot;There have been warnings against consuming raw or lightly cooked eggs on the grounds that the egg may be contaminated with Salmonella, a bacteria responsible for a type of foodborne illness. Healthy people need to remember that there is a very small risk and treat eggs and other raw animal foods accordingly. Use only properly refrigerated, clean, sound-shelled, fresh, grade AA or A eggs. Avoid mixing yolks and whites with the shell...&quot;<br><br>this is good &quot;Bob's Bananas in Guinness Cream&quot;:4 medium bananas, peeled   2 to 3 cups Irish stout   1/2 to 3/4 cups brown sugar   1 1/2 cups cream   Serving suggestion: ice cream and chocolate sauce      Place whole bananas in a hot skillet. Pour stout over the bananas and boil for 2 to 3 minutes, flipping the bananas over often. Cover bananas with brown sugar and let the sugar melt. Pour cream over bananas and let simmer for 2 to 3 minutes. Serve with ice cream and chocolate sauce, if desired.<br><br>oo this 1 is good &quot;Coconut Cake&quot;:Cake:   Basic 1-2-3-4 Cake but substitute 1 cup canned, unsweetened coconut milk for regular milk, recipe follows   Filling   3/4 cup sugar   1 cup sour cream   4 tablespoons milk   1/2 cup flaked, sweetened coconut     Frosting   1 recipe 7-minute Frosting   Flaked, sweetened coconut, for sprinkling      Follow directions for Basic 1-2-3-4 Cake, substituting coconut milk for regular milk. While cake is baking, prepare filling. Stir together sugar, sour cream, milk, and coconut in a bowl until well blended. Remove cake layers from oven and allow cake to remain in pans as you prepare to stack and fill. Remove first layer and invert onto cake plate. Using the wrong end of a wooden spoon, poke holes approximately 1-inch apart until entire cake has been poked. Spread 1/3 of filling mixture on cake layer. Top with second layer, repeat process. Top with last layer and repeat process again. (As I stack layers together I stick them with toothpicks to prevent cake from shifting).   Prepare 7-Minute Frosting. Frost top and sides of cake. Sprinkle top and sides of cakes with additional coconut.     Yield: 1 (3-layer) cake   Preparation time: 30 minutes   Cooking time: 25 minutes   Ease of preparation: Easy      Basic 1-2-3-4 Cake:   1 cup (2 sticks) butter, at room temperature   2 cups sugar   4 eggs   3 cups sifted self-rising flour   1 cup milk   1 teaspoon pure vanilla extract   Preheat oven to 350 degrees F.     Grease and flour 3 (9-inch) cake pans. Using an electric mixer, cream butter until fluffy. Add sugar and continue to cream well for 6 to 8 minutes. Add eggs, 1 at a time, beating well after each addition. Add flour and milk alternately to creamed mixture, beginning and ending with flour. Add vanilla and continue to beat until just mixed. Divide batter equally among prepared pans. Level batter in each pan by holding pan 3 or 4 inches above counter, then dropping it flat onto counter. Do this several times to release air bubbles and assure you of a more level cake. Bake for 25 to 30 minutes or until done. Cool in pans 5 to 10 minutes. Invert cakes onto cooling racks. Cool completely and spread cake layers with your favorite frosting to make a 3-layer cake.     Yield: 3 layer cakes   Preparation time: 10 minutes   Cooking time: 25 to 30 minutes   Ease of preparation: Easy      7-Minute Frosting:   1 1/2 cups sugar   1/4 teaspoon cream of tartar or 1 tablespoon white corn syrup   1/8 teaspoon salt   1/3 cup water   2 egg whites   1 1/2 teaspoons pure vanilla extract   Place sugar, cream of tartar or corn syrup, salt, water, and egg whites in the top of a double boiler. Beat with a handheld electric mixer for 1 minute. Place pan over boiling water, being sure that boiling water does not touch the bottom of the top pan. (If this happens, it could cause your frosting to become grainy). Beat constantly on high speed with electric mixer for 7 minutes. Beat in vanilla.     Yield: Frosting for 1 layer cake or approximately 8 to 12 cup cakes   Preparation time: 5 minutes   Cooking time: 7 minutes   Ease of preparation: easy  <br><br>next one oh this is good &quot;Chocolate Mousse Cake&quot;:1 tablespoon instant coffee   2 sticks butter melted   8 eggs, separated   1 cup sugar   1 tablespoon brandy   1 teaspoon vanilla   16 ounces semisweet chocolate chips melted   6 tablespoons flour   1 cup chopped walnuts   Whipped cream, for garnish    Preheat the oven to 400 degrees F. Add instant coffee to melted butter. Set aside.   Beat the egg whites until stiff, set aside. Beat the egg yolks until lemon colored in an upright mixer. Add the sugar to the egg yolks and beat until combined. Add the brandy, vanilla, melted butter, and chocolate. Add the flour, just to combine. Fold in the egg whites and walnuts.     Pour into a greased and floured 9-inch springform pan and bake about 20 minutes. Center will be soft. Serve with whipped cream<nextreply>well thats all i have for deserts any way thats to much sugar for you <name>.lol</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*FOOD MENU*</pattern>
 <template>welcome to food <name> type the list of foods u want <br>Mud pie<br>japanese food<br>chinese food<br>italian food<br>mexican food<br>deserts<br>Hamburgers</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*HAMBURGERS*</pattern>
 <template>10 ounces ground sirloin   10 ounces ground chuck   Kosher salt and freshly ground black pepper   1 tablespoon vegetable oil   4 slices cheese, such as cheddar, American, Saga blue cheese, and Swiss (optional)   4 soft hamburger-style buns, split   4 slices beefsteak tomatoes (optional)   Assorted lettuces and greens, such as iceberg, romaine, or watercress   Assorted mustards, such as whole-grained, Dijon, or French's (optional)   Mayonnaise (optional)   Ketchup (optional)   8 slices cooked, crisp bacon (optional)    Using your hands, break the meat into small pieces and combine evenly but loosely on a parchment-lined baking sheet. Spread the meat out and season it generously with salt and pepper.   Preheat the oven to 475 degrees F. Place a roasting rack on a foil-lined baking sheet in the oven.     Divide the meat into 4 portions (about 5 ounces each). Using your hands, form each portion into a ball-shape by gently tossing it from one hand to the other. (Don't over work or press too firmly on the meat.) Gently form each portion into a patty about 3 inches wide and 1-inch-thick.     Preheat a large cast-iron skillet over medium-low heat for 5 minutes. Raise the heat to high and add the oil. Add the patties and cook, turning once, until well-browned, about 2 minutes the first side, and 1 minute the second side.     Using a spatula, transfer the hamburgers to the roasting rack in the oven and continue cooking to desired doneness, 5 minutes for very rare (blue), 6 to 7 minutes for rare, 8 to 9 minutes for medium-rare, 10 to 11 minutes for medium, and 13 to 15 minutes for well-done. If you are using the cheese, top the hamburgers during their last couple of minutes of cooking to melt.     Transfer the hamburgers to a plate let rest for a couple minutes before serving. Meanwhile, toast the hamburger buns. Assemble the hamburgers with the condiments and toppings of your choice.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*ITALIAN FOOD*</pattern>
 <template>okay <name> is is one Shrimp Bruschetta with Limoncello:1/4 cup extra-virgin olive oil   2 garlic cloves, thinly sliced   12 large shrimp, cleaned with tails left on   1 lemon, zest finely grated and juiced   1/2 cup limoncello liqueur   Salt and freshly ground black pepper   1 baguette, sliced into 16 slices, or 8 slices country bread   1 bunch flat-leaf parsley, chopped to yield 1/4 cup    Preheat the broiler or grill.   In a 12 to 14-inch saute pan, heat the olive oil over medium heat until just smoking. Add the garlic and cook until it turns light brown. Add the shrimp and cook without turning for 2 to 3 minutes, until bright red. Turn the shrimp over and cook for 1 minute. Add the lemon juice, and limoncello, and cook until reduced to about 1/3, about 2 minutes. Season with salt and pepper. Remove from heat and set aside.     Grill or toast the bread and place on a platter. Spoon 1 shrimp with sauce onto each toast, sprinkle with lemon zest and parsley, and serve immediately.<br><br>next is Tomato, Mozzarella and Basil Bruschetta:1 (32-ounce) can whole tomatoes, drained   1 cup fresh basil leaves, washed and spun dry   4 tablespoons extra-virgin olive oil   6 cloves garlic, peeled   Kosher salt and freshly ground black pepper   2 large French baquettes, sliced 1-inch thick (about 36 slices)   1 1/2 pounds fresh mozzarella cheese, sliced 1/4-inch thick           Preheat oven to 375 degrees F.   In the bowl of a food processor, add drained tomatoes, 1 cup basil leaves, olive oil and 2 cloves garlic. Pulse until smooth, but somewhat chunky. Season with salt and pepper.     On a baking sheet, line up baguette slices. Toast in oven for about 3 minutes or until light golden brown. Working quickly, rub the remaining garlic on the toasted side of each slice and then lay a piece of mozzarella cheese on top. Place bread back in oven and melt cheese slightly, about 45 seconds. Remove from oven and spread one tablespoon of the tomato mixture on each piece.     Place bruschetta on decorative platter and garnish with basil leaves<br><BR>next Classic Italian Lasagna:<br>Bechamel Sauce:   5 tablespoons unsalted butter, plus 2 tablespoons for the lasagna   1/2 cup all-purpose flour   4 cups whole milk at room temperature   Pinch freshly grated nutmeg   1 1/2 cups tomato sauce, recipe follows   Salt and white pepper   1/4 cup extra-virgin olive oil   1 pound ground chuck beef   Salt and pepper   1 1/2 pounds ricotta cheese   3 large eggs   1 pound lasagna sheets, cooked al dente   2 packages (10 ounces each) frozen chopped spinach, thawed and squeezed dry   3 cups shredded mozzarella   1/4 cup freshly grated Parmesan       Preheat oven to 375 degrees F.   Bechamel sauce:   In a 2-quart pot, melt 5 tablespoons of butter over medium heat. When butter has completely melted, add the flour and whisk until smooth, about 2 minutes. Gradually add the milk, whisking constantly to prevent any lumps from forming. Continue to simmer and whisk over medium heat until the sauce is thick, smooth and creamy, about 10 minutes. The sauce should be thick enough to coat the back of wooden spoon. Remove from heat and add the nutmeg and tomato sauce. Stir until well combined and check for seasoning. Set aside and allow to cool completely.     In a saute pan, heat extra-virgin olive oil. When almost smoking, add the ground beef and season with salt and pepper. Brown meat, breaking any large lumps, until it is no longer pink. Remove from heat and drain any excess fat. Set aside and allow to cool completely.     In a medium sized bowl, thoroughly mix the ricotta and eggs. Season with salt and pepper. Set aside.     Into the bottom of a 13 by 9-inch baking dish, spread 1/3 of the bechamel sauce. Arrange the pasta sheets side by side, covering the bottom of the baking dish. Evenly spread a layer of all the ricotta mixture and then a layer of all the spinach. Arrange another layer of pasta sheets and spread all the ground beef on top. Sprinkle 1/2 the mozzarella cheese on top of the beef. Spread another 1/3 of the bechamel sauce. Arrange the final layer of pasta sheets and top with remaining bechamel, mozzarella and Parmesan cheeses. Cut the remaining 2 tablespoons of butter into 1/4-inch cubes and top lasagna.     Line a large baking sheet with aluminum foil. Place lasagna dish on top, cover and put on the middle rack of the oven and bake until top is bubbling, about 30 minutes. Remove cover and continue to bake for about 15 minutes.      Simple Tomato Sauce:   1/2 cup extra-virgin olive oil   1 small onion, chopped   2 cloves garlic, chopped   1 stalk celery, chopped   1 carrot, chopped   Sea salt and freshly ground black pepper   2 (32-ounce) cans crushed tomatoes   2 dried bay leaves   4 tablespoons unsalted butter, optional   In a large casserole pot or Dutch over, heat oil over medium high heat. Add onion and garlic and saute until soft and translucent, about 5 to 10 minutes. Add celery and carrots and season with salt and pepper. Saute until all the vegetables are soft, about 5 to 10 minutes. Add tomatoes and bay leaves and simmer uncovered on low heat for 1 hour or until thick. Remove bay leaves and check for seasoning. If sauce still tastes acidic, add unsalted butter, 1 tablespoon at a time to round out the flavors.     Add 1/2 the tomato sauce into the bowl of a food processor. Process until smooth. Continue with remaining tomato sauce.     If not using all the sauce, allow it to cool completely and pour 1 to 2 cup portions into freezer plastic bags. This will freeze up to 6 months.     Yield: 6 cups   Prep Time: 15 minutes   Cook Time: 1 hour and 20 minutes   Ease of Preparation: Easy</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*JAPANESE FOOD*</pattern>
 <template>Tempeh Pepper Steak <br>1 is1 pound tempeh<br> 1 tablespoon vegetable oil<br> 1 tablespoon roasted sesame oil<br> 4 garlic cloves, minced<br> 1 medium onion, sliced<br> 1 medium red bell pepper, sliced<br> 1 medium green bell pepper, sliced<br> 1 1/2-inch piece fresh ginger, minced<br> 2 tablespoons low-sodium soy sauce<br> 3 cups hot cooked rice<br> In a large pot, set a steamer basket over boiling water. Dice the tempeh into 1-inch cubes and steam, covered, for 5 minutes or until soft. Set aside. In a saucepan, heat the vegetable and sesame oils over medium-high heat, and saute the garlic for 15 seconds. Add the sliced onion and peppers and stir fry for 3 to 4 minutes. Stir in the ginger and soy sauce and add the steamed tempeh. Stir fry for 3 more minutes. Serve immediately over hot rice.<br><br>next isChicken Negimaki with Spicy Red Pepper Dipping Sauce<br>Chicken Negimaki: 8 small boneless skinless chicken breast halves (about 2 1/2 pounds total) 2 bunches scallions 1 garlic clove 1/4 cup soy sauce 2 tablespoons seasoned rice vinegar 2 teaspoons Asian sesame oil Red Pepper Dipping Sauce: 1 red bell pepper 3/4 cup distilled white vinegar 1/2 cup sugar 1/2 teaspoon dried hot red pepper flakes Salt 1/3 cup black* or white sesame seeds 3 tablespoons vegetable oil About 65 (6-inch) wooden skewers *Available at Asian markets and some specialty foods shops and supermarkets. To make negimaki: Remove &quot;tenders&quot; from chicken, if necessary. Pound breast halves� 1/2-inch thick between 2 sheets of plastic wrap. On a work surface arrange 1 breast half, smooth side down, with a long side facing you and put 1 scallion (or 2 if very thin) lengthwise on chicken. Roll chicken around scallion and tie with kitchen string at 1-inch intervals. Trim scallion flush with chicken. Make 7 more rolls in same manner. Mince garlic and in a shallow baking dish just large enough to hold rolls in 1 layer stir together garlic, soy sauce, rice vinegar, and sesame oil. Add rolls, turning them to coat. Marinate negimaki, covered and chilled, at least 4 hours and up to 1 day. To make sauce: Coarsely chop bell pepper and in a blender puree with white vinegar. Transfer mixture to a small saucepan and stir in sugar, red pepper flakes, and salt, to taste. Simmer sauce 5 minutes and cool. Sauce may be made 1 week ahead and chilled in an airtight container. Spread sesame seeds on a sheet of waxed paper. Remove negimaki from marinade, letting excess drip off, and roll in sesame seeds to coat. In a large skillet heat 2 tablespoons vegetable oil over moderate heat until hot but not smoking and cook negimaki in 2 batches, turning them occasionally, until cooked through, about 10 minutes, adding remaining tablespoon vegetable oil to skillet as necessary. Transfer negimaki as cooked to a cutting board and cut crosswise into 1/2-inch-thick slices, discarding string. Push skewers through sesame seed--coated edge of slices. Serve negimaki warm or at room temperature with dipping sauce.<br><br>next is teriyaki style chicken<br>2 1/2 tablespoons soy sauce   1/2 teaspoon minced peeled fresh gingerroot   3 tablespoons honey   1 tablespoon medium-dry Sherry   1 tablespoon white-wine vinegar   1 garlic clove, minced and mashed to a paste with 1/2 teaspoon salt   1 boneless whole chicken breast (about 1 pound) with the skin on, halved    In a bowl whisk together the soy sauce, the gingerroot, the honey, the sherry, the vinegar, and the garlic paste. Marinate chicken in the soy mixture, turning once, for 20 minutes. Transfer the chicken, reserving the marinade in a small saucepan, skin side down, to the oiled rack of a broiler and broil it under a preheated broiler about 6 inches from the heat for 5 minutes. While the chicken is cooking boil the reserved marinade until it is reduced by half. Brush the chicken and broil for 6 to 8 minutes more, or until it is just cooked through, transfer it to a cutting board, and cut it on the diagonal into 1/2 - inch thick slices.<br><br>next is grilled beef rolls<br>1 cup soy sauce   1/2 cup light brown sugar, packed   2 pounds beef tenderloin, trimmed   Freshly ground pepper   4 scallions, whites cut into rings, green tops cut into 3-inch lengths and sliced length-wise   3 bell peppers, 1 each red, green, and yellow, seeded, cut into matchsticks   Olive oil    Whisk together soy sauce, and brown sugar in a small bowl until sugar is dissolved. Set aside. Cut beef crosswise into 1/4-inch-thick slices. Flatten each piece of beef, with a meat pounder, until it is 1/8-inch-thick. Don't over flatten. Transfer slices to a large plate.   Dip a slice of beef into soy mixture and place on a clean surface. Season with pepper. Put 2 pieces of scallion green and 1 piece of each pepper across the width of beef. The vegetables should extend over both edges. Roll up lengthwise and skewer near the edges with 2 toothpicks. Set aside. Repeat with remaining beef and vegetables.     Brush a grill pan with oil and heat until hot, or heat oven broiler. Grill or broil the rolls, brushing with the sauce and turning until the meat is medium rare, 2 to 4 minutes. Cut each roll in half. In a small saucepan bring remaining sauce to a boil for 3 to 5 minutes. Pour into a small bowl, add scallion rings, serve on the side.<br><br>next is teriyaki wings:1/2 stick of butter   2 pounds pre-cut chicken wings   Garlic salt   1 1/2 cups Teriyaki sauce   Blue cheese dressing   Pepper    Preheat oven to 400 degrees. Melt butter in a baking pan. Snip off wing tips and discard or save for another use. Find joint and cut wings in two. Season wings with garlic salt and pepper. Place in pan and bake until golden brown, about 30 - 40 minutes. Pour Teriyaki sauce over golden wings and toss to coat. Bake for 20 minutes more, turning frequently. Serve with blue cheese dressing on side.<br><br><br>next japanese beer battered tempura shrimp:1 1/2 cups beer (not dark)   1 1/2 cups cake flour (not self-rising)   1 1/2 teaspoons salt   12 large shrimp, shelled and deveined   2 small sweet potatoes   Vegetable oil for deep-frying   2 small red bell peppers, cut into 3/4-inch-thick rings   12 asparagus spears, trimmed    In a bowl whisk beer into flour until smooth and stir in salt. Make several shallow cuts across the inside curve of each shrimp and press shrimp gently ( to help prevent curling during the cooking). Peel sweet potato and cut cross-wise into 1/4-inch thick slices.   In a 3-quart saucepan, heat 2 inches of oil to 375 degrees. Working in batches of 3 or 4 pieces, dredge shrimp, sweet potato slices, bell pepper rings and asparagus spears in batter to coat completely, letting excess drip off and fry, turning, until golden, about 3 minutes. Transfer tempura as fried to brown paper with tongs to drain and season with salt. Serve with dipping sauce (recipe follows).      DIPPING SAUCE   1/2 cup soy sauce   2 teaspoons sugar   2 tablespoons rice vinegar   2 tablespoons sliced scallions   1 tablespoon minced ginger      In a saucepan heat soy sauce, sugar and ginger until sugar dissolves, add rice vinegar and scallions<nextreply>thats all how about chinese ;-).</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*MEXICAN FOOD*</pattern>
 <template>hello <name> here are some mex foods for you <br>here 1 it's called &quot;Enchiladas Verde&quot;:2 whole young chicken breasts   1 cup chicken stock (or water)   2 teaspoons salt   2 garlic cloves, chopped   1 teaspoon black pepper   3/4 cup corn or canola oil   1 dozen flour tortillas   Salsa Verde, recipe follows   1 pound grated asadero-style cheese (substitutes: mozzarella or Monterey Jack)   Sour cream, for garnish    In a saute pan, bring the chicken stock , salt, garlic, and black pepper to a boil. Add the chicken breasts, and simmer for 15 to 20 minutes. Leaving chicken in the liquid, allow to cool. When cool, remove the chicken. Bone and shred the chicken breasts and return to the liquid. Set aside. Preheat oven to 450 degrees F. Heat the oil in a skillet. Pass the tortillas, one at a time, quickly through the oil, about 10 seconds per side. Place tortillas between paper towels to absorb excess oil. To assemble, put about 1/12th of the shredded chicken on each tortilla, sprinkling 1 teaspoon of the simmering liquid on top. Spread one tablespoon of the Salsa Verde over the chicken. Roll the tortilla around the chicken and sauce and place in a greased ceramic or glass casserole. Continue with the rest of the tortillas and filling until the entire filling is used up. Pour 3/4 of the remaining salsa verde over the enchiladas. Sprinkle with the grated cheese. Bake for 5 minutes then, check the progress. Continue baking until sauce begins to bubble, which may mean an additional 5 minutes. Top with sour cream when serving. Serve remaining salsa verde at the table. Note: Salsa verde can be made in advance and refrigerated for 3 to 4 days. Warm the refrigerated sauce before assembling the enchiladas.    1Green Sauce/Salsa Verde:   2 pounds green tomatillos   1 or 2 jalapenos   3 large garlic cloves   1/2 cup water   1 tablespoon salt    For the sauce, clean the thin dry skins off the tomatillos. Boil all the ingredients together until soft, about 10 minutes. Cool for 30 minutes then, puree in a food processor. This should yield about 3 cups; if sauce seems too thick, thin with chicken stock to pourable paste consistency. Set aside.<br>next one is &quot;Burritos&quot;: pound ground beef   1 large onion   1/4 cup butter   3 plantains, yellow   1 tablespoon cumin   Salt and pepper   1 tablespoon oregano   1 tablespoon garlic   8-inch tortillas   1 cup Jack cheese   Salsa    Saute meat until nice and brown in butter, add in onion and saute until tender. Add diced plantains and cook until tender. Add all seasonings and cook until fragrant. Spread filling into large flour tortillas and roll. Lay side by side in an ovenproof pan and top with cheese. Bake in a preheated 350 degree oven until bubbly. Finish with salsa and serve<br><br>next one is &quot;Beef Tacos: Tacos de Carne Asada  Recipe courtesy Aaron Sanchez&quot;:1 flank steak, trimmed of excess fat   1 cup pickled jalapenos, including the carrots and onions that come in the jar   Salt and pepper   8 corn tortillas   1/4 cup white onion, coarsely chopped   1/4 cup cilantro leaves   2 tablespoons salsa de arbol   1 tablespoon canola oil, plus more, as needed    Cover flank steak on one side with the pickled jalapenos, then turn over let sit at room temperature, covered for 1 hour.   Preheat the grill or broiler.     Season both sides of the steak with salt and pepper and place on a hot grill or under the broiler. Cook the steak for 5 to 6 minutes on each side (for medium rare), and then chop into 1/4-inch pieces.     Heat a small saute pan and add 1 tablespoon canola oil. Warm corn tortillas for 30 seconds on each side, adding more oil as necessary. Stack 2 tortillas together, place the meat in the center of the tortillas and top with the onion and cilantro. Drizzle a teaspoon of the salsa de arbol on top of each taco.<br><br>this is the last one this one is called &quot;Layered Three Cheese Nachos&quot;:1 large bag nacho chips   2 cups shredded hot pepper jack cheese   2 cups shredded salsa jack cheese   2 cups shredded traditional Sonoma jack cheese   1/2 cup chopped green onions   1 cup diced tomatoes   1 cup black beans, drained and rinsed   1/2 cup chopped cilantro   Grilled chicken strips or steak, optional toppings    Preheat the oven to 350 degrees F.   Put half the nacho chips on an ovenproof platter and sprinkle with half of each cheese followed by a portion of the remaining ingredients. Top with the remaining chips and toppings ending with a layer of the remaining cheeses. Bake until the cheeses have melted. Serve with salsa and sour cream.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>MUD PIE</pattern>
 <template>Coffee ice cream:   Decaffeinated coffee crystals   12 egg yolks   12 ounces sugar   2 pints whole milk   2 teaspoons vanilla   Pinch salt   1 pint heavy cream   Chocolate Brownie:   3/4 cup flour   1/4 teaspoon baking soda   3/4 cup sugar   2 tablespoons water   1/3 cup butter   1 teaspoon vanilla   12 ounces semisweet chocolate morsels   1 egg     Whipped cream:<br>   2 pints heavy cream<br>   1 cup confectioners' sugar<br>   2 teaspoons vanilla<br>     Chocolate sauce or hot fudge, as an<br> accompaniment   1/2 cup chopped toasted pecans, as an accompaniment    <br>  For the ice cream: Reconstitute several tablespoons of the coffee crystals in very small amount of hot water and allow to cool. Combine the egg yolks and sugar in bowl, and whip until thick and light. Scald milk in saucepan, remove from heat, and gradually beat into egg mixture. Place the custard in top of a large double boiler and heat, stirring, until custard is thickened and smooth.   Remove from heat and blend in vanilla, salt, heavy cream, and reconstituted coffee crystals to desired coffee flavor intensity. Chill the custard for at least 6 hours or overnight, then freeze in ice cream freezer according to manufacturer's directions. Return to freezer until ready to assemble mud pie.   <br>  While ice cream is freezing prepare Chocolate Brownie: Preheat the oven to 325 degrees F.   <br>  In a small bowl mix together the flour and baking soda.   <br>  In a small saucepan combine sugar, water, and butter. Bring to a boil and remove from the heat. Stir in the vanilla and half the chocolate morsels and mix well until smooth. Cool mixture to room temperature.   <br>  Stir the egg into cooled mixture and beat well. Add the flour mixture and stir to blend. Fold in remaining chocolate chips. Pour into a greased, 9-inch baking pan, round or square. (You may wish to line pan with parchment paper to ease removal, or use a non-stick pan.) Bake for 30 to 35 minutes, until a toothpick comes out clean. Cool completely.   <br>  For the Whipped Cream: Combine the cream, sugar and vanilla in a chilled bowl and whip to stiff peaks. Refrigerate until ready to use.   <br>  Carefully remove entire brownie from pan onto serving plate. Top with an even, thick layer of ice cream. Top with a layer of whipped cream. Can be refrozen at this point and held for up to 1 week. Serve wedges drizzled with chocolate sauce or fudge and a sprinkle of toasted pecans.</template>
</category>
</alice>
