<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>*JOKES*</pattern>
 <template>To hear a joke type <i>Tell me a joke</i>. Keep typing it to keep hearing more jokes.   <br><br> <b>To return to the fun menu type <i>Fun</i>.</b></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*TELL ME A JOKE*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Yo Mama is so short, she poses for trophies.
<li>Q: What did the cannibal do after he dumped his girlfriend?  <nextreply> A: He wiped his butt.
<li>Your family is so poor that when I came to your house and asked, &quot;Where's the bathroom?&quot; your Mama said, &quot;Fifth bucket to the right.&quot;
<li>There once was a man named Joe and he was talking to God and he asked, &quot;How much is a penny worth in heaven?&quot; God replied, &quot;One million dollars.&quot; Then Joe asked, &quot;How long is a minute in heaven?&quot; God said, &quot;One million years.&quot; So Joe asked for a penny and God said, &quot;Sure, just wait a minute.&quot;
<li>Yo mama's so fat, when she runs, she makes the CD player skip... at the Radio station.
<li>Q: What do Mike Tyson and a Metallica concert have in common? <nextreply> A: At a Metallica concert you get ringing in the ears, and at a Mike Tyson fight, you get ears in the ring!
<li>Don't trust volleyball players with your drinks.&quot; &quot;Why?&quot; &quot;They might spike 'em.&quot;
<li>Did you hear about Helen Keller's new book? &quot;Around The Block In 80 Days!&quot;
<li>A husband, proving to his wife that women talk more than men, showed her a study which indicated that men use (on the average) only 15,000 words a day, however women use 30,000 words a day. She thought about this for a while and then told her husband that women use twice as many words as men because they have to repeat everything they say. Looking stunned, he said, &quot;What?&quot;
<li>You might be a redneck if you think the last words of the &quot;Star Spangled Banner&quot; are &quot;Gentlemen! Start your engines!&quot;
<li>The room was full of pregnant women and their partners. The Lamaze class was in full swing. The instructor was teaching the women how to breathe properly, and informing the men how to give the necessary assurances at this stage of the plan. &quot;Ladies, exercise is good for you,&quot; announced the teacher. &quot;Walking is especially beneficial. And, gentlemen, it wouldn't hurt you to take the time to go walking with your partner!&quot; The room was very quiet. Finally, a man in the middle of the group raised his hand. &quot;Yes?&quot; asked the instructor. &quot;Is it all right if she carries a golf bag while we walk?&quot;
<li>&quot;Hey, there's a dikfer on your forehead?&quot; &quot;A what?&quot; &quot;A dikfer.&quot; &quot;What's a dikfer?&quot; &quot;Well, if you don't know I'm not gonna tell you.&quot;
<li>Yo mama so poor, I saw her shopping and told her to get the hell out of my trash can!
<li>Q: How are politicians like diapers? <nextreply> A: You have to change them both often, and for the same reason.
<li>Yo mama is so stupid that she tried to find the &quot;11&quot; button so she could dial 911!
<li>3 bums were outside a bar. The first one went in and asked for a fork. The second one went in and also asked for a fork. Then the third one went in and wanted a straw. At this point, the bartender became curious. &quot;How come all your friends want forks and you want a straw?&quot; &quot;Well,&quot; the bum said, &quot;the dog threw up and the chunks are all gone.&quot;
<li>Yo Mama is so fat, she uses duct tape for Band-aids.
<li>&quot;I have good news and bad news,&quot; the defense lawyer says to his client.&quot; &quot;What's the bad news?&quot; The lawyer says, &quot;Your blood matches the DNA found at the murder scene.&quot; &quot;Dammit!&quot; cries the client. &quot;What's the good news?&quot; &quot;Well,&quot; the lawyer says, &quot;Your cholesterol is down to 140.&quot;
<li>Yo mama's so old that, when she breast-feeds, powdered milk comes out!
<li>If it weren't for the olives in martinis, yo mama would starve to death.
<li>Did you hear about the constipated accountant? He couldn't budget so he had to work it out with a pencil and paper.
<li>Yo mama's so fat, she wore an X-Files T-shirt and a helicopter landed on her.
<li>Q: What do you get when a ghost goes? <nextreply> A: A handful of sheet.
<li>One day the king of a fairly large country was greeted by a tiny knight. The knight told him the story of how he escaped a battle with a dragon, but his small horse had been killed. He begged the king for a horse, and the king was more than happy to offer him one. The problem, however, was that the knight was too small for the horses the king had. Finally, the king decided to give him a trained Great Dane to ride on. When he presented the Great Dane to the knight, the knight was horrified. He exclaimed, &quot;You would send a knight out on a dog like this?&quot;
<li>Yo mama is so fat she jumped up and when she came down she knocked the earth out of orbit!!!
<li>You're just like a telephone -- even a three-year-old can pick you up.
<li>Q: What do you get when you cross a fortune teller with a prostitute? <nextreply> A: Your whoroscope!
<li>Charles Dickens walks into a bar and orders a martini. The bartender asks, &quot;Olive or twist?&quot;
<li>Q: Why did the ant fall off the toilet bowl? <nextreply> A: He got pissed off.
<li>Q: What did the man say when he walked into the bar? <nextreply> A: Ouch!
<li>Three robbers walk into a bank then the cops bust in. The first robber jumps behind a cow. The second robber jumps behind a chicken. The third robber jumps in a pile of hay. The cops then say &quot;Talk Now!&quot; The robber behind the cow says &quot;Moooo!!!, the robber behind the chicken says &quot;Cluck-k-k-k&quot;, and the robber in the hay pile says &quot;Hay-Hay&quot;.
<li>Three men jump in a well. Only two men's hair get wet. Q: How can this be? <nextreply> A: One was bald!
</random></template>
</category>
</alice>
