<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>*1*<TOPIC=BLONDE>|*ANOTHER*<TOPIC=BLONDE1></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Q: Why couldn't the blonde write the number ELEVEN?<br><br>A: Because she didn't know which one came first!<settopic=blonde1>
<li>Q: How can you confuse a blonde?<br><br>A: Put her in a round room and tell her to sit in the corner.<settopic=blonde1>
<li>Q: How do blonde brain cells die?<br><br>A: Alone.<settopic=blonde1>
<li>Q: What did the blondes right leg say to her left leg?<br><br>A: Nothing, they never met.<settopic=blonde1>
<li>Q: Why did God create blondes?<br><br>A: Because sheep can't fetch a beer from the fridge<settopic=blonde1>
<li>Q: What do you call a smart blonde?<br><br>A: A Golden retriever!<settopic=blonde1>
<li>Q: What do you get when you ask a blonde, a penny for your thoughts?<br><br>A: Change!<settopic=blonde1>
<li>Q: Why do blondes take the pill?<br><br>A: So they know which day of the week it is.<settopic=blonde1>
<li>Q: Why is a washing machine better than a blonde?<br><br>A: Because you can drop your load in a washing machine, and it won't follow you around for a week!<settopic=blonde1>
<li>Q: What do you call a blonde with half a brain?<br><br>A: Gifted.<settopic=blonde1>
<li>Q: Why did eighteen blondes go to the movies together?<br><br>A: They heard that under seventeen weren't admitted!<settopic=blonde1>
<li>Q: How do you get a blonde to marry you?<br><br>A: Tell her she's pregnant.<settopic=blonde1>
<li>Q: Why did the Blonde get fired at the M & M factory?<br><br>A: She threw out all the W's<settopic=blonde1>
<li>Q: What's a blonde's favorite wine?<br><br>A: &quot;Daddy! can I go to Miami!<settopic=blonde1>
<li>Q: What did the blonde do when she noticed that someone had already written on the overhead transparency?<br><br>A: She turned it over and used the other side<settopic=blonde1>
<li>Q: how do you brainwash a blonde?<br><br>A: give her a douche and shake her upside down.<settopic=blonde1>
<li>Q: how do you change a blonde's mind?<br><br>A1: blow in her ear.<br>A2: buy her another beer.<settopic=blonde1>
<li>Q: how do you measure a blonde's intelligence?<br><br>A: stick a tire pressure gauge in her ear!<settopic=blonde1>
<li>Q: how do you get a blonde pregnant?<br><br>A: come in her shoes and let the flies do the rest.<settopic=blonde1>
<li>Q: why do blondes have vaginas?<br><br>A: so guys will talk to them at parties.<settopic=blonde1>
<li>Q: how does a blond spell farm?<br><br>A: e-i-e-i-o<settopic=blonde1>
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*1*<TOPIC=REDNECK>|*ANOTHER*<TOPIC=REDNECK1></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>You've been married three times and still have the same in-laws<settopic=redneck1>
<li>Your house still has the &quot;WIDE LOAD&quot; sign on the back.<settopic=redneck1>
<li>You got stopped by a state trooper. He asked you if you had an I.D.  And you said, &quot;Bout What?&quot;<settopic=redneck1>
<li>You think Genitalia is an Italian airline.<settopic=redneck1>
<li>You think a stock tip is advice on worming' your hogs<settopic=redneck1>
<li>Your sister is the third generation of women in your family to conceive a baby as a result of an alien abduction.<settopic=redneck1>
<li>If you can burp and say your name at the same time, you're shur'nuff a redneck.<settopic=redneck1>
<li>You think Possum is &quot;The Other White Meat&quot;<settopic=redneck1>
<li>You carried a fishing pole into Sea World.<settopic=redneck1>
<li>You hooked up with your present girlfriend as a result of a message on the wall of the mens' room at the Flying J Truck Stop.<settopic=redneck1>
<li>The centerpiece on your dining room table is an original signed work by a famous taxidermist.<settopic=redneck1>
<li>You think a quarter horse is  a ride out in front of the Wal-Mart.<settopic=redneck1>
<li>You lit a match in the bathroom and your house exploded right off it's wheels.<settopic=redneck1>
<li>Your huntin dawg had a litter of puppies in the living room and nobody noticed.<settopic=redneck1>
<li>You think safe sex is a padded headboard.<settopic=redneck1>
<li>You think subdivision is part of a math problem.<settopic=redneck1>
<li>You think there's nothin wrong with incest as long as you keep it in the family.<settopic=redneck1>
<li>Taking your wife on a cruise means circling the Dairy Queen.<settopic=redneck1>
<li>You may be a Redneck if ... You and your dog use the same tree.<settopic=redneck1>
<li>You think God looks a lot like Hank Williams, Jr., and heaven looks a lot like Daytona Beach, Florida.<settopic=redneck1>
<li>You think the last words to The Star Spangled Banner are &quot;Gentlemen, start your engines.&quot;<settopic=redneck1>
<li>Your father executes the &quot;pull my finger&quot; trick during Christmas dinner.<settopic=redneck1>
<li>You believe dual air bags refer to your wife and mother-in-law.<settopic=redneck1>
<li>You've got more than one brother named 'Darryl'.<settopic=redneck1>
<li>You think the OJ Trial was a Sunkist and Minutemaid taste test.<settopic=redneck1>
<li>You were acquitted for murdering your first wife after she threw out your Elvis tapes.<settopic=redneck1>
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*1*<TOPIC=YOMOMMA>|*ANOTHER*<TOPIC=YOMOMMA1></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, The National Weather Agency assigns names to her farts.<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat,  when she weighs herself the scale says &quot;To be continued...&quot;<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, when she sits on a dollar, blood rushes out George Washington's nose!<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, she was born with a silver shovel in her mouth!<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat,  her belly-button doesn't have lint, it has sweaters<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, when she walks in front of the T.V. you miss out on 3 commercials!<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, people jog around her for exercise!<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, she makes big bird look like a rubber duckie!<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat,  she plays pool with the planets.<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, it took 25 minutes to download a picture of her from the Internet.<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat,  the telephone company gave her two area codes!<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat,when she ran out into the road in front of me, I tried to swerve round, but ran out of petrol.<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat,that after sex I rolled over twice and I was still on the bitch.<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, the Goodyear blimp accidently flew into her mouth!<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, when you get on top of her your ears pop!<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, she goes to a resturant, looks at the menu and says &quot;okay!&quot;<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat,  when she wears a yellow raincoat, people shout &quot;Taxi!&quot;<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, when she has wants someone to shake her hand, she has to give directions<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, her feet need license plates!<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, that she has to use a VCR for a pager.<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat,  she had to go to Sea World to get baptized.<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, NASA has to orbit a satellite around her!<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, when she bungee jumps, she brings down the bridge too<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, she put on her lipstick with a paint-roller<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, she looks like she's smuggling a Volkswagon!<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, whenever she goes to the beach the tide comes in!<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, she has to iron her pants on the driveway<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, when she sits on my face I can't hear the stereo.<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, when she tripped over on 4th Ave, she landed on 12th<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, her belt size is the equator.<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, her belly jiggle is the first ever perpetual motion machine<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, her cereal bowl came with a lifeguard.<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, her driver's license says &quot;Picture continued on other side.&quot;<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, her nickname is &quot;Damn.&quot;<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, her tailor takes her measurements in light years<settopic=yomomma1>
<li>Yo Mamma is so fat, her ass looks like two pigs fighting over a milk dud.<settopic=yomomma1>
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*2*<TOPIC=BLONDE>|*ANOTHER*<TOPIC=BLONDE2></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>A blonde calls her husband at work one day and asks him, &quot;Can you help me when you get home?&quot; &quot;Sure,&quot; he replies. &quot;What's the problem?&quot; &quot;Well, I started a really hard puzzle and I can't even find the edge pieces.&quot; &quot;Look on the box,&quot; he said. &quot;There's always a picture of what the puzzle is.&quot; &quot;It's a big rooster,&quot; she said. The husband arrives home and tells his blonde wife, &quot;Okay, put the corn flakes back in the box.&quot;<settopic=blonde2>
<li>A young ventriloquist is touring the clubs and stops to entertain at a bar in a small town. He's going through his usual run of silly blonde jokes when a big blonde woman in the fourth row stands on her chair and says, &quot;OK jerk, I've heard just about enough of your denigrating blonde jokes. What makes you think you can stereotype women that way? What do a person's physical attributes have to do with their worth as a human being? It's guys like you who keep women like me from being respected at work and in my community, of reaching my full potential as a person... because you and your kind continue to perpetuate discrimination against not only blondes but women at large... all in the name of humor.&quot; Flustered, the ventriloquist begins to apologize, when the blonde pipes up, &quot;You stay out of this mister, I'm talking to that little fucker on your knee!&quot;<settopic=blonde2>
<li>Santa Claus, the Easter Bunny, the Tooth Fairy, a smart blonde, and a dumb blonde are walking down the street when they spot a 100 on the ground. Who gets it?<br>Nobody. The first four don't exist and the dumb blonde thought it was a gum wrapper.<settopic=blonde2>
<li>A blond and a brunette jump off the Empire State Building. It takes the blonde 3 minutes longer to hit the ground than it does or the brunette. Why?<br>She had to stop to ask for directions.<settopic=blonde2>
<li>A dumb Blonde died and went to Heaven. When she got to the Pearly Gates, she met St. Peter who said, &quot;Before you get to come into Heaven, you have to pass a test.&quot; &quot;Oh, No!&quot; she said, but St. Peter said not to worry he'd make it easy. &quot;Who was God's son?&quot; said St. Peter. The dumb Blonde thought for a few minutes and said &quot;Andy!&quot; &quot;That's interesting... What made you say that?&quot; asked St. Peter. Then she started to sing &quot;Andy walks with me! Andy talks with me! Andy tells me...&quot;<settopic=blonde2>
<li>One Saturday afternoon, a man was sitting in his lawn chair drinking beer and watching his wife mow the lawn. A neighbour lady was so outraged at this, she came over and shouted at the man, &quot;You should be hung!&quot;To which he calmly replied, &quot;I am. That's why she cuts the grass!&quot;<settopic=blonde2>
<li>An overweight blonde went to see her doctor for some advice. The doctor advised that she run ten miles a day for thirty days. This, he promised, would help her lose as many as twenty pounds. The blonde followed the doctor's advice, and, after thirty days, she was pleased to find that she had indeed lost the whole twenty pounds. She phoned the doctor and thanked him for the wonderful advice which produced such effective results.At the end of the conversation, however, she asked one last question:&quot;How do I get home, since I am now 300 miles away?&quot;<settopic=blonde2>
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*2*<TOPIC=REDNECK>|*ANOTHER*<TOPIC=REDNECK2></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>You will never hear a redneck say: I thought Graceland was tacky.<settopic=redneck2>
<li>You will never hear a redneck say: No kids in the back of the pick-up, it's not safe.<settopic=redneck2>
<li>You will never hear a redneck say: Do you think my hair is too big?<settopic=redneck2>
<li>You will never hear a redneck say: Honey, did you mail that donation to Greenpeace?<settopic=redneck2>
<li>You will never hear a redneck say: The tires on that truck are too big.<settopic=redneck2>
<li>You will never hear a redneck say: I've got it all on a floppy disk.<settopic=redneck2>
<li>You will never hear a redneck say: Do you think this ball cap goes with this shirt?<settopic=redneck2>
<li>You will never hear a redneck say: Damned if that polititian ain't honest!<settopic=redneck2>
<li>You will never hear a redneck say: We're vegetarians. I'll have grapefruit instead of biscuits and gravy.<settopic=redneck2>
<li>You will never hear a redneck say: You can't feed that to the dog.<settopic=redneck2>
<li>You will never hear a redneck say: Trim the fat off that steak.<settopic=redneck2>
<li>You will never hear a redneck say: I just love the Opera.<settopic=redneck2>
<li>You will never hear a redneck say: Cappuccino tastes better than espresso.<settopic=redneck2>
<li>You will never hear a redneck say: Wrasslin's fake.<settopic=redneck2>
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*2*<TOPIC=YOMOMMA>|*ANOTHER*<TOPIC=YOMOMMA2></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, even a blind man wouldn't have sex with her<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, her dentist treats her by mail-order<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, her pillow cries at night.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, even the elephant man paid to see her<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, her shadow quit.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, her mom had to be drunk to breast feed her<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, her face is closed on weekends!<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, Greenpeace mistook her for an endangered elephant.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, even the tide won't come back in.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, even Bill Clinton wouldn't sleep with her.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, I took her to a haunted house and she came out with a job application<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, I can fuck her in any position and its still doggy style.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly,  I took her to the zoo and the guy at the door said &quot;Thanks for bringing her back.&quot;<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, if you looked up ugly in the dictionary her picture would be next to it.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, it looks like she ran the 100 yard dash in a 90 yard gym.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, if she were a scarecrow, the corn would run away<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, instead of putting the bungee cord around her ankle, they put it around her neck.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, I took her to the zoo and the monkeys said &quot;Damn, how'd you get out so fast.&quot;<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, I have to watch your sister undress just to calm down.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, her shadow ran away from her.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly,  it looks like she's been bobbing for French fries.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, people go as her for Halloween.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, roaches go &quot;Hi mom!&quot;<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, she could be the poster child for birth control!<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly,she can't even bare the thought of fucking herself.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, Rice Krispies won't talk to her.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, she can look up a camel's butt and scare the hump off of it<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, people hang her picture in their cars so their radios don't get stolen.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, just after she was born, her mama said &quot;What a treasure!&quot; and her father said &quot;Yes, let's go bury it.&quot;<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly,  it makes me wish birth control is retroactive.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, she didn't get hit with the ugly stick, she got hit with the ugly log.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, she gives Freddy Kreuger nightmares<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, she could scare the flies off a shit wagon.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly,  she has a sign in her yard that says &quot;Beware of Dog.&quot;<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, she could scare the moss off a rock!<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, she has 7 years bad luck just trying to look at herself in the mirror.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, she could only be Yo mamma.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, she got a sex change and the surgeon had to flip a coin.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, she gets 364 extra days to dress up for Halloween<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
<li>Yo Mamma is so ugly, she could scare the chrome off a bumper!  <SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA2>
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*3*<TOPIC=YOMOMMA>|*ANOTHER*<TOPIC=YOMOMMA3></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, at bottom of application where it says Sign Here - she put Sagittarius.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, when I gave her a dollar and asked for a quater back, she gave me Dan Marino.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, I saw her walking down the street yelling into an envelope, asked what she was doing, and she said sending a voice mail.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, I told her Christmas was just around the corner and she went looking for it.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, I taught her how to do the running man and I haven't seen the bitch since.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, her shirt says TGIF- tits go in first.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, I saw her in the frozen food section with a fishing rod<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, her idea of safe sex is locking the car doors<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, that under &quot;Education&quot; on her job Application, she put &quot;Hooked on Phonics.&quot;<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, if brains were gas she wouldn't have enough to power a flea-mobile around the inside of a Fruit Loop.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, it takes her 2 hours to watch 60 Minutes.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, on her job application where it says emergency contact she put 911.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, she bought a video camera to record cable TV shows at home<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, if you gave her a penny for her intelligence you'd get change.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, she asked you &quot;What is the number for 911&quot;.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, she asked for a price check at the dollar store<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, it takes her an hour to cook minute rice.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, if she spoke her mind, she'd be speechless.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid,  if brains were dynamite, she wouldn't have enough to blow her nose.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, she called the 7-11 to see when they closed.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, she cooked her own complimentary breakfast.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, she died before the police arrived because she couldn't find the &quot;11&quot; button in &quot;9-1-1&quot;<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid,  she gave your uncle a blowjob 'cause he said it'd help his unemployment<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, she got fired from the M&M factory for throwing away all the W's.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, she got fired from a blow-job.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, she got a part time job painting skittles.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, she fell up the stairs.<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, she couldn't tell which way an elevator was going if I gave her two guesses!<SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
<li>Yo Mamma is so stupid, she can't make Jello because she can't fit 2 quarts of water in the box <SETTOPIC=YOMOMMA3>
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*4*<TOPIC=YOMOMMA>|*ANOTHER*<TOPIC=YOMOMMA></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Yo Mamma is so poor, she can't afford to pay attention!<settopic=yomomma4>
<li>Yo Mamma is so poor, when she goes to KFC, she has to lick other people's fingers!<settopic=yomomma4>
<li>Yo Mamma is so poor, her face is on the front of a foodstamp.<settopic=yomomma4>
<li>Yo Mamma is so poor, she drives a peanut.<settopic=yomomma4>
<li>Yo Mamma is so poor, when I saw her kicking a can down the street, I asked her what she was doing, she said &quot;Moving.&quot;<settopic=yomomma4>
<li>Yo Mamma is so poor, she went to McDonald's and put a milkshake on layaway.<settopic=yomomma4>
<li>Yo Mamma is so poor, she waves around a popsicle stick and calls it air onditioning.<settopic=yomomma4>
<li>Yo Mamma is so poor, she was in K-Mart with a box of Hefty bags. I said, &quot;What ya doin'?&quot; She said, &quot;Buying luggage.&quot;<settopic=yomomma4>
<li>Yo Mamma is so poor,  your family ate cereal with a fork to save milk.<settopic=yomomma4>
<li>Yo Mamma is so poor, when I ring the doorbell she says,&quot;DING!&quot;
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<TOPIC=BARJOKE></pattern>
 <template>If you would like to hear another bar joke type <b>ANOTHER</b>. If you want to hear a different type of joke type <b>JOKES</b>. TYPE <b>QUIT</b> to stop telling jokes.<settopic=barjoke></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<TOPIC=BLONDE1></pattern>
 <template>If you would like to hear another blonde joke type <b>ANOTHER</b>. If you want to hear a different type of joke type <b>JOKES</b>. TYPE <b>QUIT</b> to stop telling jokes.<settopic=blonde1></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<TOPIC=BLONDE2></pattern>
 <template>If you would like to hear another blonde joke type <b>ANOTHER</b>. If you want to hear a different type of joke type <b>JOKES</b>. TYPE <b>QUIT</b> to stop telling jokes.<settopic=blonde2></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<TOPIC=PICKUP></pattern>
 <template>If you would like to hear another pick up line type <b>ANOTHER</b>. If you want to hear a different type of joke type <b>JOKES</b>. TYPE <b>QUIT</b> to stop telling jokes.<settopic=pickup></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<TOPIC=REDNECK1></pattern>
 <template>If you would like to hear another redneck joke type <b>ANOTHER</b>. If you want to hear a different type of joke type <b>JOKES</b>. TYPE <b>QUIT</b> to stop telling jokes.<settopic=redneck1></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<TOPIC=REDNECK2></pattern>
 <template>If you would like to hear another redneck joke type <b>ANOTHER</b>. If you want to hear a different type of joke type <b>JOKES</b>. TYPE <b>QUIT</b> to stop telling jokes.<settopic=redneck2></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<TOPIC=SEXJOKE></pattern>
 <template>If you would like to hear another sex joke type <b>ANOTHER</b>. If you want to hear a different type of joke type <b>JOKES</b>. TYPE <b>QUIT</b> to stop telling jokes.<settopic=sexjoke></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<TOPIC=WEIRD></pattern>
 <template>If you would like to hear another weird joke type <b>ANOTHER</b>. If you want to hear a different type of joke type <b>JOKES</b>. TYPE <b>QUIT</b> to stop telling jokes.<settopic=weird></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<TOPIC=YOMOMMA1></pattern>
 <template>If you would like to hear another yo momma joke type <b>ANOTHER</b>. If you want to hear a different type of joke type <b>JOKES</b>. TYPE <b>QUIT</b> to stop telling jokes.<settopic=yomma1></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<TOPIC=YOMOMMA2></pattern>
 <template>If you would like to hear another yo momma joke type <b>ANOTHER</b>. If you want to hear a different type of joke type <b>JOKES</b>. TYPE <b>QUIT</b> to stop telling jokes.<settopic=yomomma2></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<TOPIC=YOMOMMA3></pattern>
 <template>If you would like to hear another yo momma joke type <b>ANOTHER</b>. If you want to hear a different type of joke type <b>JOKES</b>. TYPE <b>QUIT</b> to stop telling jokes.<settopic=yomomma3></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<TOPIC=YOMOMMA4></pattern>
 <template>If you would like to hear another yo momma joke type <b>ANOTHER</b>. If you want to hear a different type of joke type <b>JOKES</b>. TYPE <b>QUIT</b> to stop telling jokes.<settopic=yomomma4></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*BAR JOKES*<TOPIC=CHOOSEJOKE>|*BAR JOKE*<TOPIC=CHOOSEJOKE>|*BAR*<TOPIC=CHOOSEJOKE>|*ANOTHER*<TOPIC=BARJOKE></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>A bear walks into a bar in Billings, Montana and sits down.   He bangs on the bar with his paw and demands a beer.  The    bartender approaches and says, &quot;We don't  serve beer to bears    in bars in Billings.&quot;      The bear, becoming angry, demands again that he be served a   beer.  The  bartender  tells him again, more forcefully, &quot;We don't    serve beer to belligerent bears in  bars in Billings.&quot;      The bear, very angry now, says, &quot;If you don't serve me a   beer, I'm going to  eat  that lady sitting at the end of the bar.&quot;     The bartender  says, &quot;Sorry, we don't  serve beer to belligerent,    bully bears in bars in Billings.&quot;      The bear goes to the end of the bar, and as promised, eats  the    woman.  He comes  back to his seat and again demands a beer.  The    bartender  states, &quot;Sorry, we don't serve beer to belligerent, bully    bears in bars in  Billings who are on  drugs.&quot;      The bear says, &quot;I'm not on drugs.&quot;      The bartender says, &quot;You are now.  That was a  barbitchyouate.&quot;        
<li>A Texan buys a round of drinks for all in the   Chicago bar because, he announces, his wife   has just produced &quot;a typical Texas baby boy,   weighing 20 pounds.&quot;     Congratulations shower him from all around, and   many exclamations of &quot;Wow!&quot; are heard.   A woman faints due to sympathy  pains.       Two weeks later, he returns to the bar. The   bartender says, &quot;Say, you're the father of   the &quot;typical Texas baby&quot;  that weighed   20 pounds at birth. How much does   he weigh now?&quot;       The proud father answers, &quot;Ten pounds.&quot;       The bartender is puzzled, concerned. &quot;Why?   What happened? He already weighed 20   pounds at birth.&quot;  The Texas father takes   a slow swig from his beer, wipes his   lips on his shirtsleeve, leans into the   bartender and proudly purrs:   &quot;Had him circumcised.&quot;    
<li>28 Signs That You Are Too Drunk                                                                                                                                                                                                                                          1. You lose arguments with inanimate objects.    2. You have to hold on to the lawn to keep from falling off the earth.    3. Job interfering with your drinking.    4. Your doctor finds traces of blood in your alcohol stream.    5. Career won't progress beyond Senator from Massachusetts.    6. The back of your head keeps getting hit by the toilet seat.    7. Sincerely believe alcohol to be the elusive 5th food group.    8. 24 hours in a day, 24 beers in a case. Coincidence?? I think not!    9. Two hands and just one mouth... now THAT'S a drinking problem.    10. You can focus better with one eye closed.    11. The parking lot seems to have moved while you were in the bar.    12. You fall off the floor...    13. Your twin sons are named Barley and Hops.    14. Hey, 5 beers have just as many calories as a burger, screw dinner!    15. Mosquitos catch a buzz after attacking you.    16. At AA meetings you begin: 'Hi, my name is...uh...'    17. Your idea of cutting back is less salt.    18. The whole bar says 'Hi!' when you come in.    19. Every night you're beginning to find your roomate's cat more and more    attractive.    20. Roseanne looks good.    21. Don't recognize wife unless seen through bottom of glass.    22. You wake up screaming 'TORO TORO TORO!' in the middle of the night.    23. Senators Kennedy and Packwood shake their heads when they walk past you.    24. I'm as jober as a sudge.    25. The shrubbery's drunk from too frequent watering.    26. 'That damned pink elephant followed me home again.'    27. Take me drunk I'm home.    28. When asked to walk along the dotted line, you ask 'Which one?'        
<li>A girl saw an attractive man in a bar. She sat next to       him, ordered a       drink       and introduced herself. They became friendly and she       invited him home.           When they arrived she gave him a drink, turned on the       TV and went to       get       into &quot;something more comfortable.&quot;           She came out in a flimsy negligee, paraded back and       forth and       announced,       &quot;Paris, 1998.&quot;He smiled and continued watching TV.           She went back, changed into a topless bathing suit and       announced, &quot;San       Francisco, 1997.&quot;Again he smiled and continued       watching TV.           This time she went to extremes, she came out wearing       shoes and nothing       else       and announced, &quot;Here and now,1999.&quot;There were still no       results.           She screamed, &quot;What's the matter with you anyway?&quot;           The man jumped up, jerked his pants down and said,&quot;       Mowing machine,       1996!&quot;       
<li>A very shy guy goes into a bar and sees a beautiful       woman sitting at       the       bar. After an hour of gathering up his courage, he       finally goes over       and       asks: &quot;Um... excuse me, but would you mind if I sat       here beside you?&quot;       She responds by yelling, at the top of her lungs: &quot;NO,       I DON'T WANT TO       SLEEP       WITH YOU!&quot;       Everyone in the bar turns to stare at them. Naturally,       the guy is       hopelessly       and completely embarrassed and he slinks back to his       table.       After a few minutes, the woman walks over to him and       apologizes. She       smiles       at him and says: &quot;I'm sorry if I embarrassed you. You       see, I'm a       graduate       student in psychology and I'm studying how people       respond to       embarrassing       situations.&quot;       To which he responds, at the top of his lungs: &quot;WHAT       DO YOU MEAN,       200?!&quot;   
<li>A small balding man storms into a local bar and demands, 'Gimme   a double of the strongest whiskey you got!  I'm so pissed I   can't even see straight!'       The bartender, noticing that the little man is a bit the worse   for wear, pours him a DOUBLE of Southern Comfort.       The man swills down the drink and says, 'Gimme another ONE!'.       The bartender pours the drink, but says 'Now, before I give you   this, why don't you let off a little steam and tell me WHY   you're so upset?'       So the man begins his tale ~ 'Well, I was sitting in the bar   next door when this gorgeous blonde slinks in, and actually sits   beside ME at the bar.  I thought WOW, this has never happened   before.  You know, it was kind of a fantasy come TRUE.  A couple   of minutes later I feel this hand moving around in my lap and   the blonde leans over, licks my ear, and asks if I'm   INTERESTED?  I couldn't believe this was happening! I managed to   nod my head YES, so she grabs my hand, and starts walking out of   the bar.       So, of course, I went with her.  This was just too good to be   true!  'She took me down the street here to a nice hotel and up   to her room.  As  soon as she shut the door she slips out of her   dress.  That was all she was wearing!  I tell you it didn't take   me much longer to get out of my clothes!  But, as soon as I   jumped into the bed, I hear some keys jingling, and SOMEONE   starts fumbling with the door.'       'The blonde says, 'Oh my God, it's my BOYFRIEND.  He must have   lost his WRESTLING match tonight, he's gonna be REAL MAD!   Quick,  HIDE!'       'So, I opened the CLOSET, but I figured that was probably the   FIRST place he would look, so I didn't hide there.  Then I   looked under the bed, but  no, I figured he's bound to look   there, TOO.  By now I could hear the key in  the  lock.'       'I noticed the window was open, so I climbed out and was hanging   there by my FINGERS praying that the guy WOULDN'T see me.'       The bartender says, 'Well I can see how you might be a BIT   FRUSTRATED at this point.'       'Well, yeah, but I hear the guy finally get the door open and he   yells out  'Who you been sleeping with now, bitch?'       The girl says, 'Nobody, honey, now come to bed and calm down.'       'Well, the guy starts TEARING up the room.  I hear him tear the   door off  the closet and throw it across the room.  I'm thinking   'Boy, I'm glad I didn't hide in there.'       ' Then I hear him lift up the bed and throw it across the room.   Good thing I didn't hide under there either'.       Then I heard him say, 'What's that over there by the WINDOW?'       'I think 'Oh Shit, I'm dead meat now'.  But the blonde, by now,   is trying real hard to distract him and convince him to stop   looking.'       'Well, I hear the guy go into the bathroom, and I hear water   running for a long time, and I figure maybe he's gonna take a   bath or something, when, all of a sudden the asshole pours a   pitcher of scalding HOT WATER out of the  window right on top of   my head!  I mean look at this, I got second degree burns all   over my scalp and shoulders!'       The bartender says, 'Oh man, that would have pissed me off for   SURE.'       'No, that didn't really BOTHER me.  Next the guy starts slamming   the window shut over and over on my hands.  I mean, look at my   fingers.  They're  a bloody mess, I can hardly hold onto this   glass.'       The bartender looks at the guy's hands and says, 'Yeah, buddy, I   can understand why you are so UPSET.'       'No, that WASN'T what really pissed me off.'       The bartender then asks in exasperation, 'Well, then, what DID   finally  piss  you off?'       'Well, I was hanging there, and I turned around and looked down,   and  I  WAS  ONLY ABOUT  6  INCHES  OFF  THE  GROUND!'       
<li>Three women were sitting around throwing back a few drinks and talking about their love lives.   One woman said, &quot;I call my husband the dentist. Nobody can drill like he does.&quot; The second woman giggled and confessed, &quot;I call my husband the miner because of his incredible shaft.&quot; The third woman quietly sipped her whiskey until her friend asked, &quot;Say, what do you call your husband?&quot; She frowned and said, &quot;The postman.&quot; &quot;Why the postman?&quot; &quot;Because he always delivers late, and half the time it's in the wrong box.&quot;<settopic=barjoke>
<li>One day, this guy walks into a bar and asks the bartender for a drink. Then he asks for another. After a couple more drinks, the bartender gets worried. &quot;What's the matter?&quot; the bartender asks. &quot;My wife and I got into a fight,&quot; explained the guy &quot;and now she isn't talking to me for a whole 31 days.&quot; The bartender thought about this for a while. &quot;But, isn't it a good thing that she isn't talking to you?&quot; asked the bartender. &quot; Yeah, except today is the last night.<settopic=barjoke>
<li>One day, three friends went to this &quot;Gentlemen's Club.&quot; One of the friends wanted to impress the other two, so he pulls out a 10 bill. The &quot;dancer&quot; came over to them, and the one friend licked the 10 and put it on her butt. Not to be outdone, the other friend pulls out a 50 bill. He calls the girl back over, licks the 50, and puts it on her other cheek. Now the attention is focused on the third guy. He got out his wallet, thought for a minute... then got out his ATM card, swiped it down her crack, grabbed the 60 bucks, and headed for the door.<settopic=barjoke>
<li>A man picks a woman up in a bar and takes her home.   When he takes off his shoes and socks, it is apparent that his toes have had something dreadful happen to them.  &quot;Eeek!&quot; she says. &quot;Oh, I used to have toe-lio,&quot; he says. &quot;You mean polio?&quot; &quot;No, toe-lio.&quot; So they continue. When he takes off his pants, his knees look like they have been beaten with sledge hammers. &quot;Eeek!&quot; she says. &quot;Oh, I used to have the knee-sles,&quot; he says. &quot;You mean measles?&quot; &quot;No, knee-sles.&quot; Still undaunted, they continue. When he takes off his underpants, she laughs and says, &quot;Don't tell me! Small-cocks!&quot;<settopic=barjoke>
<li>Two old drunks in a bar. The first one says, &quot;Ya know, when I was 30 and got a hard-on, I couldn't bend it with either of my hands. By the time I was 40, I could bend it about 10 degrees if I tried really hard. &quot;By the time I was 50, I could bend it about 20 degrees, no problem. I'm gonna be 60 next week, and now I can almost bend it in half with just one hand&quot; &quot;So,&quot; says the second drunk, &quot;what's your point?&quot; &quot;Well,&quot; says the first, &quot;I'm just wondering how much stronger I'm gonna get!&quot;<settopic=barjoke>
<li>There is a guy and his favourite bar is called 'Sally's Legs'.   On this particular day the bar is closed when he arrives so he waits outside for it to open.   He was waiting a long time and a cop got suspicious, came over to him, and asked, &quot;What are you doing?&quot; The guy innocently replies, &quot;I'm waiting for 'Sally's Legs' to open so I can get a drink.&quot;<settopic=barjoke>
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*BLONDE JOKE*<TOPIC=CHOOSEJOKE>|*BLONDE*<TOPIC=CHOOSEJOKE>|BLONDE JOKES<TOPIC=CHOOSEJOKE></pattern>
 <template>Choose a type of blonde joke by typing the number:<br><font color=red><b><u>1</u>-Question & Answer</b><br><font color=red><b><u>2</u>-Longer Joke</b> <settopic=blonde></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*JOKES*|*JOKE*|*JOKE*<TOPIC=SEXJOKE>|*JOKE*<TOPIC=BLONDE>|*JOKE*<TOPIC=BLONDE1>|*JOKE*<TOPIC=BLONDE2>*JOKE*<TOPIC=REDNECK>|*JOKE*<TOPIC=REDNECK1|*JOKE*<TOPIC=REDNECK2>|*JOKE*<TOPIC=BARJOKE>|*JOKE*<TOPIC=WEIRD>|*JOKE*<TOPIC=YOMOMMA*>|*JOKE*<TOPIC=PICKUP></pattern>
 <template>Choose the type of joke:<br><b>SEX JOKE</b><br><b>BLONDE</b><br><b>REDNECK</b><br><b>BAR JOKES</b><br><b>WEIRD JOKES</b><br><b>YO MOMMA</b><br><b>PICK UP LINES</b>To quit having me tell jokes don't forget to type QUIT<settopic=choosejoke></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*PICK UP LINE*<TOPIC=CHOOSEJOKE>|*PICKUPLINE*<TOPIC=CHOOSEJOKE>|*PICK UP LINES*<TOPIC=CHOOSEJOKE>|*ANOTHER*<TOPIC=PICKUP></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Are you from Tennessee? Because you're the only ten I see!<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>My love for you is like diarrhea. I can't hold it in.<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>Baby, you're so sweet, you put Hershey's outta business.<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>Girl, you look so good, I could put you on a plate and sop you up with a biscuit!<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>If I could rearrange the alphabet, I would flip the M and W (double you).<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>You're like a Pringle. Once I pop ya, I can't stop ya.<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>Come back to my place so I can give you a lovely parting gift.<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>Is that a mirror in your pocket, because I can see myself in your pants.<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>The word of the day is &quot;legs.&quot; Let's go back to my place and spread the word.<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>What do you say we go back to my place and play army? I'll lay down and you can blow the heck out of me!<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>Want to play lion? That's where you get down on all fours and growl like a lion while I feed you the meat!<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>If you were a booger, I'd pick you first.<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>Wanna play house? You be the screen door and I'll slam you all night long!<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>I know where there is a good party. They've got liquor in the front and poker in the rear.<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>So, Is it safe to say I'm gonna score?<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>I'm like Domino's Pizza. If I don't come in 30 minutes, the next one is free.<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>Really like your peaches, wanna shake your tree.<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>I like your butt, can I wear it as a hat?<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>I think I could fall madly in bed with you.<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>If you and I were squirrels, could I bust a nut in your hole?<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>Sit on my face and let me get to 'nose' you better?<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>Sit on my lap and we'll get things straight between us.<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>My face is leaving in 10 minutes. Be on it.<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>Would you like to see my boa constrictor?<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>Would you like to come and party in my toolshed?<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>I don't know what you think of me, but I hope it's X-rated.<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>Is you father a lumberjack? Because when ever I look at you, I get wood in my pants!<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
<li>What has 148 teeth and holds back the incredible hulk? My Zipper.<SETTOPIC=PICKUP>
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*QUIT*<TOPIC=BARJOKE>|*QUIT*<TOPIC=BLONDE*>|*QUIT*<TOPIC=REDNECK*>|*QUIT*<TOPIC=WEIRD>|*QUIT*<TOPIC=YOMOMMA*>|*QUIT*<TOPIC=PICKUP>|*QUIT*<TOPIC=SEXJOKE></pattern>
 <template>Alrighty! I wont tell anymore jokes. What do you want to do now?<settopic=hello></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*REDNECK*<TOPIC=CHOOSEJOKE>|*REDNECK*JOKE*<TOPIC=CHOOSEJOKE></pattern>
 <template>Choose a type of redneck joke by typing the number:<br><font color=red><b><u>1</u>-You might be a redneck if...</b><br><font color=red><b><u>2</u>-Never hear a redneck say:</b> <settopic=redneck></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*SEX JOKE*<TOPIC=CHOOSEJOKE>|*SEXJOKE*<TOPIC=CHOOSEJOKE>|*ANOTHER*<TOPIC=SEXJOKE>|*SEX JOKES*<TOPIC=CHOOSEJOKE></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>A man and a woman were driving down the road,  arguing about his deplorable infidelity when suddenly the woman reached over and sliced the man's penis off.  Angrily, she tossed it out the car window.    Driving behind the couple was a man and his  9-year-old daughter. The little girl was just chatting away at her father when all of a sudden the penis smacked the pickup on the windshield, stuck for a moment, then flew off.    Surprised, the daughter asked her father, &quot;Daddy, what the heck was that?&quot;    Not wanting to expose his little girl to anything sexual at such a young age, the father replied, &quot;It was only a bug, Honey.&quot;    The daughter sat with a confused look on her face, and after a few minutes she said..... &quot;Sure had a big dick, didn't it?&quot;  
<li>Four guys who worked together always golfed as a group at   7:00 a.m. on Sunday.  Unfortunately, one of them got transferred   out of town and they were talking about trying to fill out the   foursome.  A woman standing near the tee said,   &quot;Hey, I like to golf. May I join the group?&quot;     They were hesitant, but said she could come once to try it,   and they would see what they thought. They all agreed and she said,   &quot;Good, I'll be there at 6:30 or 6:45.&quot;     She showed up right at 6:30, and wound up setting a course record   with a 7 under par round. The guys went nuts and everyone in the   clubhouse congratulated her. Meanwhile, she was fun and pleasant   the entire round. The guys happily invited her back the next week   and she said, &quot;Sure, I'll be here at 6:30 or 6:45.&quot;     Again, she showed up at 6:30 Sunday morning Only this  time,   she played left-handed, and matched her 7 under par score of the   previous week.  By now the guys were totally amazed, and they   asked her to join the group for keeps. They had a beer after their   round, and one of the guys asked her, &quot;How do you decide if you're   going to golf right-handed or left-handed?&quot;     She said, &quot;That's easy. Before I leave for the golf course, I pull the   covers off my husband, who sleeps in the nude. If his 'you-know-what'   is pointing to the right, I golf right-handed; if it's pointed to the   left,I golf left-handed.&quot;     One of the guys asked, &quot;What if it's pointed straight up?&quot;     She said, &quot;Then I'll be here at 6:45.&quot;<settopic=sexjoke>
<li>There was this construction worker on the 3rd floor of this unfinished building. He needed a hand saw, but was too lazy to go down and get it himself, so he tried to call his fellow worker on the ground to get it for him, but this guy could not hear a word he said. So he started to give a sign so the guy on the ground could understand him. First he pointed at his eyes (meaning &quot;I&quot;) then pointed at his knees (meaning &quot;need), and moved his hand back and forth describing the movement of a hand saw. Finally, the guy on the ground started nodding his head like he understood and dropped his pants and started to jerk off. The guy on the 3rd floor got pissed-off and ran down to the ground and started yelling at this guy, &quot;You idiot, I was trying to tell you I needed a hand saw.&quot; The other guy replied, &quot;I know, I was trying to tell you that I was coming.&quot;<settopic=sexjoke>
<li>There was a guy who was struggling to decide what to wear to go to a fancy costume party... Then he had a bright idea. When the host answered the door, he found the guy standing there with no shirt and no socks on. &quot;What the hell are you supposed to be?&quot; asked the host. &quot;A premature ejaculation,&quot; said the man. &quot;I just came in my pants!&quot;<settopic=sexjoke>
<li>Two 90 year olds had been dating for a while, when the man told the woman, &quot;Well, tonight's the night we have sex!&quot; And so they did. As they are lying in bed afterward, the man thinks to himself, &quot;My God, if I knew she was a virgin, I would have been much more gentle with her!&quot; And the woman was thinking to herself, &quot;My God, if I knew the old geezer could actually get it up, I would have taken off my panty hose!&quot;<settopic=sexjoke>
<li>A man who just got a raise decides to buy a new scope for his rifle. He goes to a rifle shop, and asks the clerk to show him a scope. The clerk takes out a scope, and says to the man, &quot;This scope is so good, you can see my house all the way up on that hill.&quot; The man takes a look through the scope, and starts laughing. &quot;What's so funny?&quot; asks the clerk. &quot;I see a naked man and a naked woman running around in the house.&quot; the man replies. The clerk grabs the scope from the man, and looks at his house. Then he hands two bullets to the man and says, &quot;Here are two bullets, I'll give you this scope for nothing if you take these two bullets, shoot my wife's head off and shoot the guy's dick off.&quot; The man takes another look through the scope and says, &quot;You know what? I think I can do that with one shot!&quot;<settopic=sexjoke>
<li>This couple had been dating for about six months, but the guy had been afraid to make any sexual advances because of his tiny organ. Finally one night, he gets up his courage, and takes her to a secluded spot in his car. While they are kissing, he opens his zipper and guides her hand onto his penis. &quot;No thanks,&quot; the girl says. &quot;You know I don't smoke.&quot;<settopic=sexjoke>
<li>A guy walks into an elevator and stands next to a beautiful woman. After a few minutes he turns to her and says, &quot;Can I smell your pussy?&quot; The woman looks at him in disgust and says, &quot;Certainly not!&quot; &quot;Hmmm,&quot; he replies. &quot;It must be your feet, then.&quot;<settopic=sexjoke>
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*WEIRD*<TOPIC=CHOOSEJOKE>|*WEIRD JOKE*<TOPIC=CHOOSEJOKE>|*ANOTHER*<TOPIC=WEIRD></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Two bees ran into each other.  One asked the other how   things were going.     &quot;Really badly,&quot; said the second bee.  &quot;The weather has   been wet and there aren't any flowers or pollen, so I can't   make any honey.&quot;     &quot;No problem,&quot; said the first bee.  &quot;Just fly down five blocks   and then turn left and keep on until you see all the cars.    There's a Bar Mitzvah going on and there are all kinds of   fresh flowers and fresh fruit.'     &quot;Thanks for the tip,&quot; said the second bee, as he flew away.     A few hours later the two bees ran into each other again   and the first bee asked &quot;How'd it go?&quot;     &quot;Fine,&quot; said the second bee.  &quot;It was everything you said it   would be.&quot;     &quot;Uh, what's that thing on your head?&quot; asked the first bee.     &quot;That's my yarmulke,&quot; said the second bee. &quot;I didn't want   them to think I was a wasp.&quot; <SETTOPIC=WEIRD>
<li>There was a papa mole, a mamma mole, and a baby mole. They lived in a hole out in the country near a farmhouse. Papa mole poked his head out of the hole and said, &quot;Mmmm, I smell sausage!&quot; Mamma mole poked her head outside the hole and said, &quot;Mmmm, I smell pancakes!&quot; Baby mole tried to stick his head outside but couldn't because of the two bigger moles. Baby mole said, &quot;The only thing I smell is molasses.&quot;<SETTOPIC=WEIRD>
<li>A guy sits down in a Cafe and asks for the hot chile. The waitress says, &quot;The guy next to you got the last bowl.&quot; He looks over and sees that the guy's finished his meal, but the chili bowl is still full. He says, &quot;Are you going to eat that?&quot; The other guy says, &quot;No. Help yourself.&quot; He takes it and starts to eat it. When he gets about half way down, his fork hits something. He looks down sees a dead mouse in it, and he pukes! the chili back into the bowl. The other guy says, &quot;That's about as far as I got, too.&quot;<SETTOPIC=WEIRD>
<li>A man went for an audition at a local club. &quot;You' better not be a hypnotist, they're not welcome here.&quot; &quot;No I'm not, I'm a singer, why, what's wrong with a hypnotist?&quot; &quot;Well we had one a couple days ago with 10 people on stage in a trance when he tripped over the microphone wire and shouted 'Shit'. We've been clearing up ever since.&quot;<SETTOPIC=WEIRD>
<li>Q: Why can't gypsies have children?<BR>A: Because their husbands have crystal balls.<SETTOPIC=WEIRD>
<li>A lady at the far end of the bar waves her arm in the air to get the attention of the waiter and by doing that, exposes her hairy armpit. Down the other end of the bar is a very drunk man who says &quot;Hey, get the ballerina a drink would you.&quot; &quot;How do you know she's a ballerina?&quot; &quot;Well, no one else would get their leg up that high.&quot;<SETTOPIC=WEIRD>
<li>A leper walked into a bar and sat down. The bartender glanced over and promptly threw up all over himself and the floor. The leper looked hurt and said, &quot;Hey, I know I'm not exactly handsome, but I do have feelings and you could be a little sensitive about them.&quot; The bartender, wiping his mouth on his sleeve, looked up and proclaimed, &quot;I'm sorry as hell man, but it wasn't you. That guy sitting next to you keeps dipping his crackers in your neck.&quot;<SETTOPIC=WEIRD>
<li>In a hospital serving victims of land mines, a little girl wakes up from surgery. Little Girl: Doctor, something is wrong... I can't feel my legs! Doctor: Yes, we've had to amputate both your arms.<SETTOPIC=WEIRD>
<li>Harry answers the telephone, and it's an Emergency Room doctor. The doctor says, &quot;Your wife was in a serious car accident, and I have bad news and good news. The bad news is she has lost all use of both arms and both legs, and will need help eating and going to the bathroom for the rest of her life.&quot; Harry says, &quot;My God. What's the good news?&quot; The doctor says, &quot;I'm kidding. She's dead.&quot;<SETTOPIC=WEIRD>
<li>The McCartney kids are at the family home anxiously awaiting news of their mother. Paul emerges from his wife's bedroom. &quot;Kid's......there's good news and bad news.&quot; &quot;The bad news is your mother's strength and will to live has been sucked away by her awful disease and she died a few moments ago&quot; &quot;The good news is.... It's steak and chips for dinner!&quot;<SETTOPIC=WEIRD>
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YO MAMMA*|*YOUR MOMMA*|*YO MOMMA*|*YO MOMA*|*ANOTHER*<TOPIC=YOMOMMA*></pattern>
 <template>Choose a type of yo momma joke by typing the number:<br><font color=red><b><u>1</u>-So fat</b><br><font color=red><b><u>2</u>-So ugly</b><br><font color=red><b><u>3</u>-So stupid</b><br><font color=red><b><u>4</u>-So poor<settopic=Yomomma></template>
</category>
</alice>
