<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>*FORTUNE*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Never underestimate the power of stupid people in large groups.
<li>You will be crushed by a 50ft. cucumber, unless you eat a sparrow, boil all the bones, and make a necklace out of them.
<li>Beware of the black cat.
<li>Today will be a good day, provided you avoid midgets.
<li>A mime will be your ultimate downfall.
<li>You will publish a book.  However, you won't see a dime, and people will only read it after you die.
<li>That cookie was poisoned.
<li>Ask again... it's a bit hazy.
<li>What am I, a magic 8-ball?
<li>Get lost!  You didn't pay me any rupees!
<li>You will live today.  That will be 900 rupees.  Cough it up, sucker.
<li>A gear in your head will break today.  You can fix it by sticking a screwdriver in your ear.
<li>Don't walk in the street naked.
<li>Control your impulses today.  Loud gurgling noises in the midddle of a quiz or exam is usually not a good idea.
<li>Be nice to EVERYONE.  There is a maniac on the loose.
<li>A fortune will curse your luck for the rest of the day.<nextreply>cursecursecursecursecursecurse
<li>Your significant other has something to tell you.
<li>One of your homies is plotting against you... kill the rebel.
<li>You will find an amazing piece of treasure, if you look hard.  All day.
<li>You will stay up too late.
<li>Don't talk to the guy with brown hair.  He likes Michael Jackson.
<li>If you don't say hi to the right person, you will end the day as a homeless bum.
<li>You are cursed to forever read these fortunes until your eyes melt from their sockets.
<li>You will finally meet your stalker today.  Or maybe vice-versa.
<li>A virus will infest your computer today, unless you smash your hard drive with a mallet.
<li>The light at the end of the tunnel is a BAD THING when accompanied by a horn.
<li>A friend in need is a friend on speed.
<li>Midgets are always the last to know when it's raining.
<li>People who live in spaghetti houses shouldn't throw meatballs.
</random></template>
</category>
</alice>
