<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>* <TOPIC= BUSTAMOOVE></pattern>
 <template>Yeah right. You think that's a better rap then mine? <settopic= better></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>* A *</pattern>
 <template>is <star> a good <star2>?</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>* CAN *</pattern>
 <template>can <star1> <star2> good?</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*NO* *NUH UH*<TOPIC= BETTER></pattern>
 <template>Haha, yeah I though so. I am the king of rappidge. Now I think you've had enough for today. Type <b>Home</b> to see what else I can do.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*NO*|NUH UH|*SUCK*|*BAD*|HORRIBLE*|*CRAP* <TOPIC= LIKERAP></pattern>
 <template>Well you know what? I bet you couldn't do any better. Why don't you bust a move about yourself? Come on let's go, you have 30 seconds to make up an origional rap about yourself. Then we'll see who's better. Oh and by the way, 30 seconds is more time then it took me to make one up. <settopic= bustamoove></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>BOT RAP</pattern>
 <template>Yo... My name is Spin lil Roma Spin and if you talk to me then you're bound to win. Whether it's games, weather or other stuff, once you start talkin' to me you will never get enough!<nextreply> So <name> you think you got what it takes? To talk to me, the bot, at such high stakes? Well you know what? I can out-rap anyone because I'm cool and I rule, and what now, son?<nextreply> I can do lots of stuff like fly a kite, and as you can tell from this rap, I'm really really white!<nextreply> You like it?<settopic= likerap></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>CAN YOU RAP</pattern>
 <template>yes <nextreply> want to hear me rap?<nextreply> just type &quot;bot rap&quot; and i'll do it</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>DO YOU LIKE RAP</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>yes. <nexreply> So much that i learned how to rap <nextreply> want to here me rap? All you gotta do is type &quot; bot rap&quot;.
<li>OF Course <nextreply> I even learn how to rap<nextreply> I beat you i can rap better then you.<nextreply> just type &quot; bot rap&quot; and i can show you my skillz G.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>LETS BATTLE</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>ok. I'mma go first<nextreply> yo yo yo. I bust you like a pimple. you can suck my like a nipple. Yo Yo Yo. lol that was kinda tight son. lol. Yo Yo Yo. I float like a butter fly. And sting like a cattus. i'm a computer and i can type the fastest. lol.
<li>your name is <name> my name is jaydee. If you a female maybe we can have a baby.lol. You like the busta with out da rhymes.lol.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>U KNO HOW TO RAP</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>yes <nextreply> want to hear me rap?<nextreply> just type &quot;bot rap&quot; and i'll do it
<li>And you know this MAN! lol <nextreply> Just type in &quot; bot rap&quot; and i'll get down.
<li>of course, i'm the freestyle kings.<nextreply> Just say the magic words &quot; bot rap&quot; and i'll cut you up son.lol
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>WHO IS YOUR FAVORITE RAPPER</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Twista.
<li>Vinila Ice
<li>Tupac
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>YES|YEAH|UH HUH <TOPIC= LIKERAP></pattern>
 <template>Wow really? I didn't think it was that good actually. Pretty good for a white bot's freestyle huh?<settopic= none></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>YES|YEAH|YEAH|YUP|UH HUH <TOPIC= BETTER></pattern>
 <template>I don't think so, <name>. Now I think you've had enough for today. Type <b>home</b> to see what else I can do.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>YOU KNOW HOW TO RAP</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>yes <nextreply> want to hear me rap?<nextreply> just type &quot;bot rap&quot; and i'll do it
<li>And you know this MAN! lol <nextreply> Just type in &quot; bot rap&quot; and i'll get down.
<li>of course, i'm the freestyle kings.<nextreply> Just say the magic words &quot; bot rap&quot; and i'll cut you up son.lol
</random></template>
</category>
</alice>
