<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>DUMB BLONDE JOKES</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>a blonde and a brunette jumped off a building...who hit the ground first? the brunette, the blonde had to stop and ask for directions.
<li>i saw a blonde screaming at an envelope..i asked her what she was doing and she said she was sending a voicemail
<li>Did you hear about the blonde who put under Education on her job application, 'Hooked On Phonics'...
<li>what did the blonde girl name her pet zebra? spot.
<li>why did the blonde have tire marks on her back? because she crawled across the street when the sign said &quot;DON'T WALK&quot;
<li>what did the blonde owl say? what, what?
<li>how did the blonde try to kill a bird? drop it off a building.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>MICHAEL JACKSON JOKES</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>what is michael jackson's bedtime?when the big hand touches the little hand
<li>Knock Knock. Whos there? Little boy blue. Little boy blue who? michael jackson.
<li>if you play the song Thriller backwards, its the names of the little boys michael jackson has molested. thats why its 14 minutes long.
<li>i bought a new car stereo...and when u shout out &quot;Soul&quot; it plays soul music.when u shout out &quot;rock&quot; it plays rock music. then one day kids were playing on my car and i yelled &quot;F*CKING KIDS!&quot; and it played michael jackson.
<li>why did michael jackson get food poisoning? he ate a 9 year old wiener!
<li>what does michael jackson and a play station 2 have in common? they are both plastic and little boys turn them on!
<li>why did michael jackson go to K-mart? because he heard boys'pants were half off!
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>REGULAR JOKES</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>why can't u tell a joke while ice skating? because the ice might crack up
<li>what do u call a mix breed of a bulldog and a shitzuo? a bullsh*t
<li>what did the alien say to the book? take me to your reader
<li>why did the gum cross the road? because it was stuck to a chicken's foot
<li>there are 2 muffins in an oven...one muffin says to the other &quot;its getting hot in here...&quot; and the other one says back &quot;HOLY SH*T! A TALKING MUFFIN!&quot;:-P
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>TELL ME A JOKE</pattern>
 <template>Pick a subject of jokes you want to see.............Regular Jokes.................Yo Momma Jokes..........Dumb Blonde Jokes.......or,Michael Jackson Jokes</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>YO MOMMA JOKES</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>yo momma is like a vacume cleaner..she sucks,blows, and gets laid in the closet afterwards
<li>yo momma is like an SUV..big,black, and can fit 6 construction workers.
<li>yo momma so fat when she goes to the beach all the whales start to sing &quot;WE ARE FAMILY!&quot;
<li>yo momma so ugly her reflection quit
<li>yo momma so poor i saw her kicking a can down the street and i asked her &quot;what are you doing?&quot; and she said &quot;moving...&quot; 
<li>yo momma so poor i saw her wearing 1 shoe and i said &quot;did u loose a shoe?&quot; and she said &quot;no, i just found 1!&quot;
<li>yo momma so poor i took a step in her house and fell out the window
<li>yo momma so ugly she trick-or-treats by  e-mail
<li>yo momma so fat she saw a yellow school bus filled with white kids and said &quot;STOP THAT TWINKIE!&quot;
</random></template>
</category>
</alice>
