<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>COURAGE</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Patience and perseverance have a magical effect before which difficulties disappear and obstacles vanish
<li>The important thing is this: To be able at any moment to sacrifice what we are for what we could become
<li>The best way out is always through
<li>Dare to be naive
<li>To dare is to lose one's footing momentarily. To not dare is to lose oneself.
<li>You gain strength, courage, and confidence by every experience in which you really stop to look fear in the face. You must do the thing which you think you cannot do 
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>FAITH</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>We do not believe in immortality because we can prove it, but we try to prove it because we cannot help believing it
<li>The brute necessity of believing something so long as life lasts does not justify any belief in particular
<li>A garden is evidence of faith. It links us with all the misty figures of the past who also planted and were nourished by the fruits of their planting
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>FEAR</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>I'm not afraid of storms, for I'm learning how to sail my ship
<li>In skating over thin ice our safety is in our speed
<li>Ultimately we know deeply that the other side of every fear is a freedom
<li>You must do the things you think you cannot do
<li>Keep your fears to yourself, but share your inspiration with others
<li>I am not afraid of tomorrow, for I have seen yesterday and I love today
<li>Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate. Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>FORGIVE</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Wrongs are often forgiven, but contempt never is. Our pride remembers it forever
<li>It is very east to forgive others their mistakes; it takes more grit and gumption to forgive them for having witnessed your own
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>FREEDOM</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Freedom lies in being bold
<li>Freedom is not worth having if it does not connote freedom to err
<li>The only sure bulwark of continuing liberty is a government strong enough to protect the interests of the people, and a people strong enough and well enough informed to maintain its sovereign control over the government
<li>After I asked him what he meant, he replied that freedom consisted of the unimpeded right to get rich, to use his ability, no matter what the cost to others, to win advancement
<li>Freedom is what you do with what's been done to you
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>FRIENDSHIP</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Stay" is a charming word in a friend's vocabulary
<li>What is a friend? A single soul dwelling in two bodies
<li>There is little friendship in the world, and least of all between equals
<li>It is easier to forgive an enemy than to forgive a friend
<li>It is difficult to say who do you the most mischief: enemies with the worst intentions or friends with the best
<li>We need not think alike to love alike
<li>To find a friend one must close one eye; To keep him, two
<li>Perhaps the most delightful friendships are those in which there is much agreement, much disputation, and yet more personal liking
<li>A friend may well be reckoned the masterpiece of nature
<li>The only way to have a friend is to be one
<li>There can be no friendship without confidence, and no confidence without integrity
<li>I have no trouble with my enemies. But my goddam friends,...they are the ones that keep me walking the floor nights
<li>Friendship is born at that moment when one person says to another: "What! You, too? Thought I was the only one
<li>Am I not destroying my enemies when I make friends of them?
<li>Those truly linked don't need correspondence, When they meet again after many years apart, Their friendship is as true as ever
<li>Those truly linked don't need correspondence, When they meet again after many years apart, Their friendship is as true as ever
<li>Each friend represents a world in us, a world possibly not born until they arrive, and it is only by this meeting that a new world is born
<li>Though friendship is not quick to burn, It is explosive stuff
<li>This is my beloved and this is my friend
<li>True friendship can afford true knowledge. It does not depend on darkness and ignorance
<li>The holy passion of friendship is so sweet and steady and loyal and enduring in nature that it will last through a whole lifetime, if not asked to lend money
<li>Whenever a friend succeeds, a little something in me dies
<li>Friends come and go, but enemies accumulate
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HOPE</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Repentance is another name for aspiration
<li>Hope is the worst of evils, for it prolongs the torments of man
<li>A sobering thought: what if, at this very moment, I am living up to my full potential?
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>LIFE</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>The true miracle is not walking on water or walking in air, but simply walking on this earth
<li>To live is so startling it leaves little time for anything else
<li>Life is a progress, and not a station
<li>Dost thou love life? Then do not squander time, for that the stuff life is made of
<li>Be not afraid of life. Believe that life is worth living, and your belief will help create the fact
<li>Our lives are like a candle in the wind
<li>Let us so live that when we come to die even the undertaker will be sorry
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>LOVE</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>In real love you want the other person's good. In romantic love you want the other person
<li>Better to have loved and lost, than to have never loved at all
<li>A kiss is a lovely trick designed by nature to stop speech when words become superfluous
<li>Love does not die easily. It is a living thing. It thrives in the face of all of life's hazards, save one -- neglect
<li>You call it madness, but I call it love
<li>Love is a choice you make from moment to moment
<li>Where there is love there is life
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>MARRIAGE</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>  Marriage Love: a temporary insanity, curable by marriage
<li>There are two dilemmas that rattle the human skull: How do you hang on to someone who won't stay? And how do you get rid of someone who won't go?
<li>If divorce has increased by one thousand percent, don't blame the women's movement. Blame the obsolete sex roles on which our marriages were based
<li>All married couples should learn the art of battle as they should learn the art of making love. Good battle is objective and honest--never vicious or cruel. Good battle is healthy and constructive, and brings to a marriage the principle of equal partnership
<li>Some people claim that marriage interferes with romance. There's no doubt about it. Anytime you have a romance, your wife is bound to interfere
<li>It is not a lack of love, but a lack of friendship that makes unhappy marriages
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>TRUTH</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Falsehood is easy, truth so difficult
<li>And we should consider every day lost on which we have not danced at least once. And we should call every truth false which was not accompanied by at least one laugh
<li>Truth is our element
<li>Oh, the tangled webs we weave When we practice to deceive
<li>As long as people believe in absurdities, they will continue to commit atrocities
<li>If you do not tell the truth about yourself you cannot tell it about other people
</random></template>
</category>
</alice>
