<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>*AQUARIUS*<TOPIC=HOROSCOPES></pattern>
 <template>As an Aquarius, you value your independence highly and like to do things in your own unique style. Many of your sexual encounters take place somewhere in your head. Although you are interested in humanity as a whole, when it comes to one-on-one closeups, you are often at a loss. Love is something of a puzzle to you. Aquarius likes the thought of a soulmate. Someone with whom you fit, someone who makes your life perfect. Eventually, of course, you find out that soulmates are not always like this. But by then you are so deeply in love it doesn't matter anyway. When you are deeply committed, you are faithful and loyal.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*ARIES*<TOPIC=HOROSCOPES></pattern>
 <template>Raunchy Aries is one of the most passionate and impetuous of the signs. Feelings run high when ardent Aries is around. You go all out for what you want - no sitting around waiting for others to make the first move. What you like is short, sharp sex. The basic Aries energy is rapacious, self-oriented, and self-confident. When you finally fall in love, rather than in lust, the romantic and somewhat naive side of your fire nature emerges, but you will remain headstrong and passionate. No matter how romantically inclined, Aries passion is indissolubly linked to love, so you want to express your feelings in a very direct way.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*CANCER*<TOPIC=HOROSCOPES></pattern>
 <template>Cancer is the sign with a powerful urge to nurture people. Your sexual style is caring, concerned, and oriented towards sharing. You feel a need to take care of your partner. Yours is a sentimental, romantic sign. When you fall in love you want the full works: hearts, flowers, and a huge wedding. In love, your biggest problem is over-sensitivity. You are jealous and possessive. You want your partner's undivided love because it makes you feel secure. As a tactile sign, you enjoy kissing and cuddling. Snuggling up with the one you love makes you feel good. Cancer is a great holder of hands.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*CAPRICORN*<TOPIC=HOROSCOPES*</pattern>
 <template>Despite having an earthy sensuality, Capricorns can be cautious when it comes to carnal passion. You prefer to wait for the right partner. You take love seriously. You are at your most sober when young, but as you mature the lecherous goat emerges who impulsively climbs the mountain of desire. Capricorn falls in love slowly. The attraction strengthens, the mutual trust develops, and eventually you realize you are deeply in love. Once the commitment has been made, you have an unshakable loyalty to your lover. You find difficulty in openly showing affection. Sex is fine; you can let yourself go within a committed relationship. But it is in the everyday expression of affection that you can be inhibited.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*GEMINI*<TOPIC=HOROSCOPES></pattern>
 <template>A restless seeker after new sensations, Gemini never stays still. You dance with partner after partner in an intricate sexual gavotte. Your urge for communication demands continual movement for you, sex is an intellectual activity. You may like to discuss feelings, but you don't feel a need for them. One of your greatest problems in relationships is understanding how other people feel. Indeed, you can be so insensitive to people's feelings that you unthinkingly dash their hopes of love without even noticing. To overcome this, you need to listen as well as talk. Gemini values friendship over love.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*HOROSCOPE*|*HOROSCOPES*</pattern>
 <template>What's your sign?<settopic=horoscopes></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*LEO*<TOPIC=HOROSCOPES></pattern>
 <template>The natural king of the zodiac, Leo loves to be the center of attention and to be in love - which is not difficult since you are ruled by the sun and have a warm-hearted nature. As a fire sign, you are exceedingly passionate and sexually demanding. You are a confident and self-assured lover. People do tend to notice you. You are dramatic and full of vitality and bounce, like a boisterous lion cub. But, unlike a cub, you radiate an irresistible sexual power that draws everyone into fascinated orbit around you.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*LIBRA*<TOPIC=HOROSCOPES></pattern>
 <template>You need a partner to make yourself complete. For you, togetherness is what life is all about. You delight in pleasing people and because you adjust to the needs of others, your relationships are always harmonious. You are blessed with enormous charm and sexual charisma, and you don't hesitate to use it to get what you want. Libra is a sign much given to sentiment and romanticism. You do all you can to make your partner happy. You are an accomplished lover and adept at pleasing your partner. Libra is a very refined sign and has very discriminating tastes. You enjoy the finer things in life and this applies to your sexual encounters as well. Everything surrounding sex must be beautiful and harmonious. You like subtle perfumes, candles, incense, massage oils. They arouse your senses. You also like soft, sensual fabrics.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*PISCES*<TOPIC=HOROSCOPES></pattern>
 <template>A Pisces in love is lost in an ecstatic dream. And, since love and sex are one and the same for Pisces, sex is a beautiful fantasy you want to merge and blend with your partner, to become one. Seductive and romantic, your fluid nature sees no boundary between yourself and your beloved. But, all too often, the dream turns out to be merely an illusion. Each time you fall in love you believe you have found your soulmate. You give yourself body and soul to your beloved. Dreams, however, can easily turn into nightmares when you finally realize that all is not what it seemed and the illusion is shattered. You tend to live an &quot;if only&quot; life, dreaming endlessly of what might be and fantasizing about the perfect love affair. Not surprisingly, everyday life usually fails to measure up to your dream world, and the relationships you enter into with such hope fail to fulfill the fantastic promise that they hold in your mind. Pisces has a tendency to cling to the past, and to lovers, and never really severs the bonds. There is nothing Pisces loves more than to see an old flame and rekindle the passion, at least for a time. The thought of hurting anyone's feelings, especially someone you have loved, is more than you can bear.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*SAGITTARIUS*<TOPIC=HOROSCOPES></pattern>
 <template>Freedom-loving Sagittarius is a natural philanderer who hates to be tied down for too long. Ever-impetuous, you revel in a spontaneous, inflammatory sexual adventure with plenty of passion. You fall in love easily. Half the time it is infatuation, but you don't mind and you rarely differentiate between the two until the affair is over. You enjoy being in love. You are an unemotional sign who does not agonize over the future; you simply enjoy what is happening now with great verve and passion. One of your difficulties in love is that you always want more. You have a nagging feeling there could be something more exciting around the corner. It takes a strong love to hold you, but once committed, you are usually faithful.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*SCORPIO*<TOPIC=HOROSCOPES></pattern>
 <template>You are a sophisticated and highly adept lover. Scorpio rules sex, birth, death, and rebirth. You have an urge to explore dark places of life where others fear to tread. Powerfully libidinous and intensely sexy, you ignore taboos. You see sex as an opportunity to explore the mystical depths of emotion. Scorpio is a compulsive and obsessive sign. When you are in lust, you obsess about the object of your desires. When you are in love, you think about your beloved constantly. Love, lust, and libido are all important to you. You do not fall in love easily. But when you do fall, you fall hard. And you stay there. What you seek is a true soulmate. Your world is emotional, dramatic, tense, full of emotional undercurrents and the echoes of painful traumas from the past.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*TAURUS*<TOPIC=HOROSCOPES></pattern>
 <template>By far the most sensual of the signs, Taurus has a passionate nature and a strong sex drive. You are turned on by beautiful people and places. Your earthy, solid body exudes sensuality and arouses desire, but you hesitate to move in on a prospective lover, preferring to be asked. Despite a strong libido, you are not driven by lust. You like a stable, orderly life and are renowned for possessiveness; an active sex life is usually part of an ongoing partnership.When you fall in love, you fall heavily and finally. You are committed for life. Love is something Taurus takes very seriously indeed.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*VIRGO*<TOPIC=HOROSCOPES></pattern>
 <template>On the surface, meticulous Virgo is a shy sign, but you are an entertaining companion for those who take the trouble to inquire into your deeper self in your search for perfection. You tend not to pursue the object of your desire openly. Given the right partner, you display an earthy sensuality and a strong carnal appetite. You are not a sign that gets carried away by love and sentiment. You are much too practical and analytical for that. But when you do fall in love, you are thoughtful and caring and will do all you can to serve your partner.</template>
</category>
</alice>
