<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>SING SLIPKNOT</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>I've felt the hate rise up in me... Kneel down and clear the stone of leaves... I wander over where you can't see... Inside my shell, I wait and bleed... (_WAIT AND BLEED_)
<li>I - I want it all! Fuck this shit, I'm sick of it You're goin' down, this is a war! (_SIC_)
<li>FUCK IT ALL! FUCK THIS WORLD! FUCK EVERYTHING THAT YOU STAND FOR! DON'T BELONG! DON'T EXIST! DON'T GIVE A SHIT! DON'T EVER JUDGE ME! (_SURFACING_)
<li>SPIT - IT OUT All you wanna do is drag me down All I wanna do is stamp you out (_SPIT IT OUT_)
<li>Tattered and torn Something aches Tattered and torn Bad things slither Tattered and torn My floors are burning down Tattered and torn And I can't find a window (_TATTERED AND TORN_)
<li>Maze...psychopathic daze...I create this waste Back away from tangents, on the verge of drastic ways...can't escape this place...I deny your face Sweat gets in my eyes, I think I'm slowly dying (_PURITY_)
<li>Liberate - My madness (One of me, all of you) Liberate - My madness I just want to... (_LIBERATE_)
<li>Even if you run... I will find you I decided I wanted you Now I know...I NEED If you can't be bought, tougher than I thought Keep in mind - I am with you Never left out fate, can't concentrate (_PROSTHETICS_)
<li>No kind of life! This is no kind of life! (I've got to get out!) It's no kind of life! This is no kind of life! (You can't blame me!) (_NO LIFE_)
<li>What the hell - did I - do to deserve - all of this? (_DILUTED_)
<li>People = Shit People = Shit (Whatcha gonna do?) People = Shit (Cuz I am not afraid of you) People = Shit (I'm everything you'll never be) People = Shit (_PEOPLE = SHIT_)
<li>I know why you blame me(yourself) I know why you plague me(yourself) I'm turning it around like a knife in the shell I wanna understand why,but I'm hurting myself I haven't seen a reasons to stop it I can't just drop it I'm just a bastard,but at least I admit it At least I admit it (_MY PLAGUE_)
<li>You are wrong,fucked,and overrated I think I'm gonna be sick and it's your fault This is the end of EVERYTHING You are the end of EVERYTHING I haven't slept since I woke up And found my whole life was a lie,motherfucker This is the end of EVERYTHING You are the end of EVERYTHING (_END OF EVERYTHING_)
<li>If you're 555,then I'm 666 If you're 555,I'm 666 (What's it like to be a heretic?) (_HERETIC ANTHEM_)
<li>(I ignore you) As I close my eyes,I feel it all slipping away (I come toward you) We all got left behind,we let it all slip away 
<li>Relax...it's over,you belong to me,I fill your mouth with dirt Relax...it's over,you can never leave I take your second digit with me... Love... You are...my first,I can breath I find you fascinating You are...my favorite,lay you down to sleep It's all that I can do to stop...Love... So blue...so broken,paper doll decays I haven't left you yet So cold...subversive,your eyes are full of bleach Tomorrow,I will go away again...Love... YOU ARE MINE,YOU WILL ALWAYS BE MINE,I CAN TEAR YOU APART I CAN RECOMBINE YOU ALL I WANT IS TO COVET YOU ALL YOU BELONG TO ME I WILL KILL YOU TO LOVE YOU.(LOVE) (_IOWA_)
</random></template>
</category>
</alice>
