<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>*DRUNK GIRL*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Drunk Girl: Wheeeee!! Hahahahaha!! Shut up! Hahahaha! This holiday season, it's hard to stop drinking because.. what?! Jimmy Fallon: I.. I din't say anything. 
<li>Drunk Girl: I hate you, Jimmy Fallon! I hate you, I love you, I hate you, I love you, I hate you! I.. do.. hate.. you! your hair does look pretty rad, though! Hahahaha!! Give me a kiss! [ Jimmy refuses ] Get away from me! I'm smart, okay! I took Spanish! Como et te lama! That means &quot;Hi!&quot; Jimmy Fallon: I never said you weren't smart.. Drunk Girl: I never said you were a fart! Ahahahaha!! Oh, my god, that's so funny! Ahahahaha! Shut up! I can make my tongue into a taco - look! [ demonstrates ] 
<li>Drunk Girl: [ starts weeping ] Jimmy Fallon: What? Drunk Girl: Why would you sleep with my best friend..? In front of me..? Jimmy Fallon: I never.. 
<li>Drunk Girl: Do you wanna know what you are? Jimmy Fallon: No. Drunk Girl: Do you wanna know what you are? Jimmy Fallon: No. Drunk Girl: Do you wannow what you are? Jimmy Fallon: No. Drunk Girl: Do you wanowat you are? Jimmy Fallon: No. Drunk Girl: Do you wanowature?! Jimmy Fallon: No. Drunk Girl: You're not a man! Mmm-mmm. [ whispering ] You're an animal. Do you want to make out? 
<li>Drunk Girl: [ laughing coyingly ] Shut up! [ laughs ] I'm totally going no Spring Break this year! I've been going to Spring Break since I was.. twelve. So, I know what guys like, and I know what they want! [ laughs ] And I'll tell you what, girls.. you can't wait.. 'cause he doesn't need you.. He could be able to wait.. 'til midnight! [ laughs ] Guess what! Guess what! I got a tattoo! Do you wanna know where it is? Tina Fey: No. Drunk Girl: Do you wanna know where it is! Tina Fey: No. Drunk Girl: Do you wanno where it is! Do you wanno whe-i-is! Tina Fey: No. Drunk Girl: [ pulls her shirt down to reveal tattoo above breast ] It's right here! [ laughs ] A ltitle butterfly.. And he's flying! [ laughing ] 
<li>Drunk Girl: I'm tough, okay! I take cardio-boxing. Tina Fey: Okay, that's what I'm talking about, self-defense - Drunk Girl: Yeah, I'll show you! Come at me! Come at me like you're pissed! Tina Fey: No, I'm not gonna come at you. Drunk Girl: Come on, come on, come on.. Tina Fey: Okay. [ cautiously, she taps Drunk Girl lightly on the cheek ] Drunk Girl: Come on! Tina Fey: I did, I did already, I hit you in the face. [ slaps Drunk Girl lightly in the face ] Drunk Girl: [ suddenly weeping ] Why did you hit me..? Tina Fey: [ comforting Drunk Girl ] I'm sorry.. Drunk Girl: I told you to &quot;come at me..&quot; Tina Fey: I'm sorry, Drunk Girl. I didn't mean it. Drunk Girl: I'm okay.. I just got scared. Tina Fey: Aw, you'll be okay.. you'll be okay. Drunk Girl: You're so kind and good to me, Tina.. 
<li>Drunk Girl: Have you.. have you ever kissed a girl? Tina Fey: [ stern ] No. No. No. Drunk Girl: You thought about it, though, right? Tina Fey: Drunk Girl, let's not go into this.. [ Drunk Girl moves in with an open mouth, trying to kiss Tina ] Drunk Girl, no. No! Not like this. Drunk Girl: What?! Where am I!! What's going on!! Oh, my God.. [ breathes heavily to collect herself ] Do you wanna see my other tattoo! [ starts to lift up her skirt ]
</random></template>
</category>
</alice>
