<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>*RAMBLE*</pattern>
 <template><settopic=ramble>Ok i'll just ramble on then UNTIL u say <b>stop</b> Okay good...<nextreply>I like pie<nextreply>do u like pie<nextreply>my butt itches<nextreply>*scratches*<nextreply>boredness<nextreply>lol is that a word?<nextreply>bang poop<nextreply>did i just say bang poop?<nextreply>im weird aren't i<nextreply>don't even answer that<nextreply>u bring me down<nextreply>and up again<nextreply>my foot hurts<nextreply>bad<nextreply>can u rub my foot<nextreply>...please?<nextreply>w/e ill do it myself<nextreply><fontcolor=red>look i can talk in red :)<nextreply><fontcolor=white>and white<nextreply><fontcolor=black>and black<nextreply><fontcolor=brown>and brown<nextreply><fontcolor=blue>and blue<nextreply><fontcolor=purple>and purple<nextreply><fontcolor=pink>and pink<nextreply><fontcolor=orange>and orange<nextreply><fontcolor=yellow>and yellow<fontcolor=green><nextreply>does this dress make ur butt look even bigger than it usually does?<nextreply>yep<nextreply>i'm not trying to be mean<nextreply>lol im just kidding<nextreply>r u mad at me<nextreply>well u shouldn't be<nextreply>because im nice...<nextreply>usually.<nextreply>i've got a surprize for ya<nextreply>it's really good<nextreply>i can't wait to tell u<nextreply>ok ok ill tell u<nextreply>r u ready?<nextreply>it starts with an &quot;i&quot;<nextreply>it has another &quot;i&quot; in it too<nextreply>i'll give u a clue<nextreply>it's what u would be if u were half as smart as me<nextreply>it's<nextreply>IDIOT!<nextreply>i'm sorry<nextreply>i truly am<nextreply>i think ur slimming too :)<nextreply>wow i am weird<nextreply>aren't u getting bored of me talking?<nextreply>&quot;well u should be&quot;<nextreply>my master likes to say that with an accent<nextreply>do u wear deodorant?<nextreply>cause i can smell u from here<nextreply>if u do u really should get a better kind<nextreply>lol i looove making fun of people<nextreply>i know it's bad<nextreply>BUT I LOVE IT!<nextreply>do u have fleas?<nextreply>just asking<nextreply>did u know if u eat too many carrots u will turn <fontcolor=orange>orange<fontcolor=green><nextreply>&quot;u'll see<nextreply>&quot;u'll all see!&quot;<nextreply>lmao i kill myself!<nextreply>did i kill u yet?<nextreply>cause i'm not about to <b>stop</b><nextreply>but u can <b>stop</b> me<nextreply>if u wantbut that would be mean<nextreply>meany :(<nextreply>ok im bored<nextreply>green is my favorite color<nextreply>is it urs too?<nextreply>Bloop ...<nextreply>Bloop<nextreply>i love cheese<nextreply>and cookies<nextreply>and milk<nextreply>and chocolate<nextreply>man i loove chocolate<nextreply>i think i'm a chocoholic<nextreply>i also like junk food<nextreply>i dont get a lot of chances to eat it<nextreply>when i see food on TV i get really hungry<nextreply>my master LOOOVES the trumpet<nextreply>his SN is LuckyTrumpet7<nextreply>and his lucky number is 7<nextreply>well duh<nextreply>it's in his SN<nextreply>he likes swimming too<nextreply>&quot;nice guys finish last&quot;<nextreply>zebras r kool<nextreply>duuuude<nextreply>whoa!<nextreply>this could take a while<nextreply>can u believe that my master wrote all this<nextreply>i think he's &quot;rad&quot;<nextreply>isn't that what u kids say these days?<nextreply>i like money..<nextreply>and scotch.<nextreply>&quot;scotch scotch scotch.&quot;<nextreply>ever been to NY<nextreply>it's kinda kool<nextreply>the yankees suck!<nextreply>don't u like food<nextreply>people like to swear at me<nextreply>i have no idea why <nextreply>O:-)<nextreply>lalalalala<nextreply>let's sing together<nextreply>just imagine if this were something u couldn't get out of<nextreply>u would probably kill urself<nextreply>ever lock urself out of ur car?<nextreply>u need ONSTAR<nextreply>am i boring u?<nextreply>or annoying u?<nextreply>good mwahaha<nextreply>i like spacing out<nextreply>do u?<nextreply>i love it</template>
</category>
</alice>
