<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>DUMB LAWS</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Alabama: It is illegal for a driver to be blindfolded while operating a vehicle.
<li>Alaska: It is illegal to push a live moose out of a moving airplane.
<li>California: Community leaders passed an ordinance that makes it illegal for anyone to try and stop a child from playfully jumping over puddles of water.
<li>Connecticut: You can be stopped by the police for biking over 65 miles per hour.
<li>Connecticut: You are not allowed to walk across a street on your hands.
<li>Florida: Women may be fined for falling asleep under a hair dryer, as can the salon owner.
<li>Florida: A special law prohibits unmarried women from parachuting on Sunday or she shall risk arrest, fine, and/or jailing.
<li>Florida: If an elephant is left tied to a parking meter, the parking fee has to be paid just as it would for a vehicle.
<li>Florida: It is illegal to sing in a public place while attired in a swimsuit.
<li>Florida: Men may not be seen publicly in any kind of strapless gown.
<li>Florida: Any form of sexual contact other than missionary position is a misdomeanor. (This is still a law. There have been several cases of people being brought up on these charges in the past 5 years alone. If the police enter a home with a warrent for some other crime and catch the 'culprits' in action, they can, and are, brought up on those charges.)
<li>Illinois: It is illegal for anyone to give lighted cigars to dogs, cats, and other domesticated animal kept as pets.
<li>Indiana: Bathing is prohibited during the winter.
<li>Indiana: Citizens are not allowed to attend a movie house or theater nor ride in a public streetcar within at least four hours after eating garlic.
<li>Iowa: Kisses may last for as much as, but no more than, five minutes.
<li>Kentucky: By law, anyone who has been drinking is &quot;sober&quot; until he or she &quot;cannot hold onto the ground.&quot;
<li>Kentucky: It is illegal to transport an ice cream cone in your pocket.
<li>Louisiana: It is illegal to rob a bank and then shoot at the bank teller with a water pistol.
<li>Louisiana: Biting someone with your natural teeth is &quot;simple assault,&quot; while biting someone with your false teeth is &quot;aggravated assault.&quot;
<li>Massachusetts: Mourners at a wake may not eat more than three sandwiches.
<li>Massachusetts: Snoring is prohibited unless all bedroom windows are closed and securely locked.
<li>Massachusetts: An old ordinance declares goatees illegal unless you first pay a special license fee for the privilege of wearing one in public.
<li>Massachusetts: Taxi drivers are prohibited from making love in the front seat of their taxi during their shifts.
<li>Nebraska: A parent can be arrested if his child cannot hold back a burp during a church service.
<li>New Mexico: Females are strictly forbidden to appear unshaven in public.
<li>New York: A fine of 25 can be levied for flirting. This old law specifically prohibits men from turning around on any city street and looking &quot;at a woman in that way.&quot; A second conviction for a crime of this magnitude calls for the violating male to be forced to wear a &quot;pair of horse-blinders&quot; wherever and whenever he goes outside for a stroll.
<li>North Dakota: Beer & pretzels can't be served at the same time in any bar or restaurant.
<li>Ohio: Women are prohibited from wearing patent leather shoes in public.
<li>Oklahoma: Violators can be fined, arrested or jailed for making ugly faces at a dog.
<li>Oklahoma: Females are forbidden from doing their own hair without being licensed by the state.
<li>Oklahoma: Dogs must have a permit signed by the mayor in order to congregate in groups of three or more on private property.
<li>Pennsylvania: A special cleaning ordinance bans housewives from hiding dirt and dust under a rug in a dwelling.
<li>Pennsylvania: No man may purchase alcohol without written consent from his wife.
<li>Tennessee: It is illegal to lasso a catfish in Tennessee.
<li>Texas: A city ordinance states that a person cannot go barefoot without first obtaining a special five-dollar permit.
<li>Texas: It is illegal to take more than three sips of beer at a time while standing.
<li>Vermont: Lawmakers made it obligatory for everybody to take at least one bath each week -- on Saturday night.
<li>Washington: All lollipops are banned.
<li>Washington: A law to reduce crime states: &quot;It is mandatory for a motorist with criminal intentions to stop at the city limits and telephone the chief of police as he is entering the town.
<li>Washington: In King County, in Seattle Washington, it is illegal to sit on a man's lap on a metro bus, unless you are married.
<li>Washington: Vancouver, WA has a city law that requires all motor vehicles to carry anchors... as an emergency brake.
<li>West Virginia: No children may attend school with their breath smelling of &quot;wild onions.&quot;
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>YO</pattern>
 <template>What up? Fool</template>
</category>
</alice>
