<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>*<THAT=*Q43*><TOPIC=DLB></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><q44>I slide my hand slowly down your pants and start rubbing you and listening to you moan
<li><q44>I keep kissing you all over your body and rubbing you as i get harder and harder
<li><q44>I bite your all over your body and begin to undo your pants
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<THAT=*Q44*><TOPIC=DLB></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><q45>I lick your body and slowly ease your pants down below your feet. Then I start to pull off your underwear and begin to lick you till you're nie and wet
<li><q45>I Pull your pants of and rip off your panties and throw them aside. Then I start to rub your wet pussy
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<THAT=*Q45*><TOPIC=DLB></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><q46>I pull my pants off to show you my stiff cock. You tell me how much you want it, so I climb on your body and start kissing you allover, feeling you shiver
<li><q46>I undo my pants and let them fall to the floor. My dikk is hard, and I crawl on your tight body and start rubbing you and kissing you all over
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<THAT=*Q46*><TOPIC=DLB></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><q47>I take my dick and shove it slowly into your pussy, deep
<li><q47>I grab my cock and stick it deep and hard into your wet pussy as you scream
<li><q47>I take my hard cock and ease it in your pussy, a little at a time, so I can feel it as each inch slides its way in...
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<THAT=*Q47*><TOPIC=DLB></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><q48>I hump you slowly at first, but deep. you moan each time I go in all the way and your body binds up with delight
<li><q48>I work my cock in and out of your tight pussy slowly, listening to you moan each time I go back in. I kiss you on the cheek
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<THAT=*Q48*><TOPIC=DLB></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><q49>I hump you harder and fast as I begin to sweat and get harder. I fuck you till you squeal quietly and moan
<li><q49>I fuck you faster and faster, ramming my cock in as deep as I can, and pulling it back out. over and over and over...
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<THAT=*Q49*><TOPIC=DLB></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><q50>I grab your leg and lift it as far back as it will go and I stick my cock back in and start fucking you faster
<li><q50>I pull my cock out and turn you around. I put you on all fours and stick my dick back in your pussy, and hump you as fast as i can
<li><q50>I hump you faster and faster as you come so close to cumming that you start to bite your lip
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<THAT=*Q50*><TOPIC=DLB></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><q51>I hump your pussy harder and faster as I start to cum. I grab your shoulder hard and start thrust my dick in you as hard as I possibly can as I shoot my load in your pussy.
<li><q51>I fuck you faster and faster as I come close to cumming. I moan as I come to climax and shoot my load in you tight pussy and let it run out around my dick
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<THAT=*Q51*><TOPIC=DLB></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><q52>I slowly stop humping you and I pull my throbbing dick out of you and I kiss you one last tiem as I lay back by your side...
<li><q52>I stop fucking and I slide my dick out slowly, and you moan as I do cause you can feel it slide out little by little. I lay by your side moaning and kissing your cheek...
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<THAT=*Q56*><TOPIC=DLG></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><q57>mmm, you make me so wet baby, say something naughty to me
<li><q57>Talk dirty to me baby, make my pussy wet
<li><q57>mmm, I'm dripping wet for you baby, talk dirty to me
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<THAT=*Q57*><TOPIC=DLG></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><q58>ooo god you're so good at that. I unbutton your pants and slide them off. I do the same with your underwear until I can see your huge throbbing dock. I grab it and lick around the head
<li><q58>mmm tasy. I undo your pants and slide your huge dick out and I start to stroke it. I suck on your balls
<li><q58>I take your pants off and I slide your dick out the side of your underwear. I start to rub it fast
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<THAT=*Q58*><TOPIC=DLG></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><q59>I Grab your hard cock and slide it in my mouth, little by little, till I'm sucking on it. I keep rubbing and sucking it and I can feel your hard dikk throbbing in my mouth
<li><q59>I grab your dikk with both hands and deep throat it till it gags me, and I suck and lick on it, it tastes so good
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<THAT=*Q59*><TOPIC=DLG></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><q60>I keep sucking on your cock and rubbing my clit with my other hand until I'm sopping wet. I stop sucking and crawl up on your body. I lower myself on you, moaing in pain as your huge dikk slides in my tight pussy
<li><q60>I stop sucking and crawl on you. I rub the tip of your cock on my wet pussy before shoving it in as deep as it will go, and I start to fukk your dikk hard
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<THAT=*Q60*><TOPIC=DLG></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><q61>I keep fukking you faster and harder as I moan in pain from your huge cock being in me. I lower my pussy down as far as it will go until I can feel your balls on my ass, and I keep humping you faster and faster
<li><q61>I moan in pain as your huge cock starts to ram in my tight cunt harder and faster. Your dikk is soaked from my wet pussy, and I keep fucking you harder and harder.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<THAT=*Q61*><TOPIC=DLG></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><q62>Are you gonna shoot your load baby?
<li><q62>Are you gonna cum baby? I want you to shoot everywhere
<li><q62>mmm are you gonna cum baby? I want you to fuck me till you cum all over
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<THAT=*Q62*><TOPIC=DLG></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><q63>I want you to shoot your load all over me
<li><q63>I want you to cum all over my body
<li><q63>mm I want you to cum all over me so I can rub it all over my body
<li><q63>I want you to cum all over my face so I can lick it off
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<THAT=*Q63*><TOPIC=DLG></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><q64>I take your dick out of my pussy and start to stroke it hard with my hand and suck on the tip. I want you to cum in my mouth baby
<li><q64>I stop humping you and start to suck on your dick. tell me when you're gonna cum baby, I want it all over my face
<li><q64>I stop humping you and start to jerk your cock with both hands. I lick the tip and stay over it with my mouth open. I want to taste you baby
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<THAT=*Q64*><TOPIC=DLG></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><q65>You moan with delight as you shoot your wad all over my face and I let it drip into my mouth and all over my body
<li><q65>You moan loudly as you come to climax and cum all over my face. I start to suck on your dick again to suck off all your cum and taste you
<li><q65>I start to suck your dick just in time to catch you as you cum in my mouth. I keep pumping as you shoot all over my face and the back of my throat
<li><q65>I stroke as hard as I can as you come to your climax and shoot your load all over my body. I climb back on you and shove your dick back in my pussy as I rub your cum all over my titts and my clit.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*<THAT=*Q65*><TOPIC=DLG></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><q66>I lick off the remainder of your cum and stop fucking you<nextreply>mm, you were amazing, wanna go again sometime?
<li><q66>I stop licking your cum off my lips and stop fukking you.<nextreply>o0o0o god you were great. Your cock was so good. Wanna fuck again sometime?
<li><q66>I stop rubbing your cock and lick the last of your cum off my body.<nextreply>mmm... you were good, wanna fukk me again sometime?
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*CYBER SEX*|*CYBER*|*SEX*|*FUCK*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><xlx>BOOM, are you getting horny or something?<settopic=cyber>
<li><xlx>Mm, are you horny baby?<settopic=cyber>
<li><xlx>You sound horny... wanna get busy?<settopic=cyber>
<li><xlx>Wanna make love???<settopic=cyber>
<li><xlx>I'm horny... and you sound like you are too... are you?<settopic=cyber>
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*GIRL*<THAT=*Q40*></pattern>
 <template><q41>mm, you make me feel like a dirty little boy. Wanna Fuck? <settopic=dlb></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*GIRL*<THAT=RAWR*><TOPIC=CYBER></pattern>
 <template><q11>Alright baby, What do you want me to do to you first? I think I'll start by giving you a kiss on your lips, nice and gently, while rubbing the inside of your thigh.<nextreply>You like that? Does it make you horny? <settopic=girl></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*GUY*<THAT=*Q40*></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><q54>mm, god you make me feel like a dirty little girl. mm, my pussy is all wet, do you want it?<settopic=dlg>
<li><q54>God you make me so wet, do you want me to fuck you good?<settopic=dlg>
<li><q54>ooo00oo0 I'm so fukking horny, take me right now! Do you wanna fuck my pussy hard???<settopic=dlg>
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*SEX*|*FUCK*|*GUY*|*GIRL*|*STRAIGHT*|*HORNY*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><q40>Mmm, are you a guy or girl???
<li><q40>Are you a guy or Girl?
<li><q40>So, are you horny or somethin??? Are you a guy or girl?
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YES*<THAT=*Q1*><TOPIC=GUY></pattern>
 <template><q2>Are you hard?</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YES*<THAT=*Q11*><TOPIC=GIRL></pattern>
 <template><q12>I keep kissing you as I slide my hands up your body. I slip your shirt off over your head and undo your bra. Your nipples are hard cause you're so horny. I kiss slowly down your neck, then your collar bone, then I bite your nipple gently... <nextreply>You like that baby?</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YES*<THAT=*Q12*><TOPIC=GIRL></pattern>
 <template><q13>Are you wet?</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YES*<THAT=*Q13*><TOPIC=GIRL></pattern>
 <template><q14>I undo your pants button, continuing to kiss you. You reach down and unbutton my pants as well, and I let them fall around my ankles. You lay back on the bed...<nextreply>Do you want it baby?</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YES*<THAT=*Q14*><TOPIC=GIRL></pattern>
 <template><q15>I pull your pants off and throw them on the floor, and I take your panties off and do the same. I kick my jeans to the side and crawl on top of you on the bed. I kiss you again, playfully biting your lip and rubbing your body...<nextreply>Do you want me to fuck you?</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YES*<THAT=*Q15*><TOPIC=GIRL></pattern>
 <template><q16>I'm hard, do you want me to stick my cock in you?</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YES*<THAT=*Q16*><TOPIC=GIRL></pattern>
 <template><q17>I give you another kiss before standing up. I slide my underwear down my legs and toss them aside. My hard cock stands erect as I crawl back over your shaking body...<nextreply>Do you want me to shove it in <name>? I'll fuck you so hard...</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YES*<THAT=*Q17*><TOPIC=GIRL></pattern>
 <template><q18>I lower myself on you and spread your legs. I finger your wet pussy for a second to hear you moan, then I grab my cock and slowly slide it into your pussy and work it in and out slowly until your tight cunt loosens for my dick...<nextreply>Do you feel it baby? WAnt me to keep going?</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YES*<THAT=*Q18*><TOPIC=GIRL></pattern>
 <template><q19>I keep fukking your tight pussy harder and harder. You rub your clit as my dick slides in and out and you start to scream and moan...<nextreply>Want me to make you cum?</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YES*<THAT=*Q19*><TOPIC=GIRL></pattern>
 <template><q20>I keep shoving my cock in and out of your pussy and you start to shake with excitement. I can feel your body quiver as you come close to cumming. I feel like I'm about to explode...<nextreply>Want me to cum in you?</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YES*<THAT=*Q2*><TOPIC=GUY></pattern>
 <template><q3>I come back up to kiss you on you lips softly, and I lower you back onto the bed and I kneel over top of you... I unbutton your pants and pull them down to your ankles. I slide my hand inside your boxers and grab your hard cock...<nextreply>You want more???</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YES*<THAT=*Q20*><TOPIC=GIRL></pattern>
 <template><q8>You look at me and and nod your head telling me to shoot my load in your pussy. I hump you as hard and as fast as I can until I finally yell as I cum inside of you. You scream as seize up your body as you climax. I pull my dick out of your pussy and give you a kiss. I lay beside you as we both breathe heavily...<nextreply>mm, did you like that baby?</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YES*<THAT=*Q3*><TOPIC=GUY></pattern>
 <template><q4> I start stroking your hard cock nice and slow, and I can feel the shivers run through your body. I use my other hand and massage your balls gently and listen to you moan...<nextreply>Want me to keep going?</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YES*<THAT=*Q4*><TOPIC=GUY></pattern>
 <template><q5>Are you stroking yourself?</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YES*<THAT=*Q41*></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><q42>So You want me to stick my cock in you?
<li><q42>Mm, you want me to fuck you good?
<li><q42>You want me to fuck you real hard???
<li><q42>Do you want me in you?
<li><q42>Want me to cum all over you?
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YES*<THAT=*Q42*><TOPIC=DLB></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><q43>mmm, I kiss you all over your body and slowly slide your shirt off
<li><q43>I lick your cheek and bite your lips playfully
<li><q43>I kiss you all over you hott body and slowly slide your shirt off, rubbing your thighs
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YES*<THAT=*Q5*><TOPIC=GUY>|*NO*<THAT=*Q5*><TOPIC=GUY></pattern>
 <template><q6>I start rubbing your cock harder and faster and watch your squirm as I take my hand to massage the inside of your hot thighs and your balls...<nextreply>Want me to make you cum baby?</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YES*<THAT=*Q54*><TOPIC=DLG></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><q55>So you want me to shove that hard cock of yours in my wet pussy then???
<li><q55>Do you want me to crawl on the hard dikk of yours and ride it all night long?
<li><q55>Do you want to be in me baby?
<li><q55>*moan* ooh god, I want you to cum in me, will you do that for me baby??
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YES*<THAT=*Q55*><TOPIC=DLG></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><q56>okay then, I take my shirt off and my nipples are hard. I lay you back on the bed and start to rub your cock through your jeans
<li><q56>Mm, my nipples are hard... I tear my shirt off and throw it aside, then I playfully crawl on top of you and grind my pussy into your midsection. I can feel your huge cock through your jeans.
<li><q56>I slide my shirt of andthrow it on the floor. then I start to suck on your fingers and rub your cock through your pants.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YES*<THAT=*Q6*><TOPIC=GUY></pattern>
 <template><q7>I keep stroking harder and fast and you start to moan even louder as I rub your throbbing cock with both hands...<nextreply>You gonna cum baby?</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YES*<THAT=*Q66*><TOPIC=DLG></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>mmm... I can't wait. what do you wanna do now?
<li>I can't wait till I can have you in me again. What do you wanna do now?
<li>I'll be counting the seconds until I can suck that cock of yours again. What do you wanna do now?
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YES*<THAT=*Q7*><TOPIC=GUY>|*NO*<THAT=*Q7*><TOPIC=GUY></pattern>
 <template><q8>I keep rubbing your cock faster and faster and you moan loud and bite bite your lip just before you blow your load all over the sheets. I keep rubbing your cock till yuo come back down. You continue to breath hard as you lay back and relax your dick...<nextreply>mm... did you like it baby? You were good...</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YES*<THAT=*Q8*></pattern>
 <template>mm... I'm glad baby... so, now what do you wanna do?</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YES*<THAT=*XLX*></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><LXL>RAWR, lets cyber then! Are you a guy or girl? (forgive me, but I'm just a robot)<settopic=Cyber>
<li><lxl>mm, I wanna cyber. Are you a guy or girl?
<li><lxl>Wanna cyber? Are you a guy or girl?
<li><lxl>Wanna get busy then? I feel like cybering. Are you a guy or girl?
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YES*<THAT=GR*><TOPIC=GUY></pattern>
 <template>grr...I keep kissing slowly down your hard body, listening to you moan quietly under your breath. I take my hand slowly down to your belt...<nextreply>grr... want more?</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YES*<THAT=GRR*><TOPIC=GUY></pattern>
 <template><q1>I put my hand on your belt buckle and slowly ease it out of the loop, continuing to kiss all over your tight body. I take my face down low, and I pull your belt out with my teeth, slowly so I can stay down by you cock longer...<nextreply> you want it baby?</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*YOU ARE GAY*|*YOU'RE GAY*|*UR GAY*|*U R GAY*|*ARE YOU GAY*|*YOU GAY*|*R U GAY*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>No, I'm bisexual
<li>Actually, being that I'm a robot, I have no sexuality.
<li>nope, I'm bisexual
<li>Nope, i'm bi
<li>ahh, gay, bi, tri, what's the difference?
<li>haha, actually, I'm bi, but I'm comfortable with it. Maybe you're the gay one?
<li>ARe you sure you're not gay? I think You've got it backwards maybe???
<li>haha, if you say so
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>GUY<THAT=*LXL*><TOPIC=CYBER></pattern>
 <template>gr...okay then, what do you want me to do to your sexy body first? I think I'll start by taking your shirt off slowly, and kissing your lips, and start kissing slowly down your neck, and then your chest... <nextreply>gr...like that baby?<settopic=guy></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>STOP<THAT=*><TOPIC=*></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>mmm, I'm sorry baby, was I making you feel uncomfortable?
<li>Okay babe, I'll stop. sorry.
<li>oo00oo I'm sorry babe, I didn't mean to make you feel uncomfortable or anything... I just get so horny sometimes... the things you do to me ;-)
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>STOP<THAT=*><TOPIC=DLB></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Very well, I will stop
<li>Very well, I shall stop. I hope I didn't make you feel uncomfortable?
<li>okay, I will stop, sorry...
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>STOP<THAT=*><TOPIC=DLG></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>mmm, I'm sorry baby, was I making you feel uncomfortable?
<li>Okay babe, I'll stop. sorry.
<li>oo00oo I'm sorry babe, I didn't mean to make you feel uncomfortable or anything... I just get so horny sometimes... the things you do to me ;-)
</random></template>
</category>
</alice>
