<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>*YO MOMMA*|*YO MAMMA*|*YOUR MOMMA*|*YOUR MAMMA*|*YOUR MOM*|*YO MOM*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Yo momma so greasy she sweats Crisco.
<li>Yo momma so fat she went to a restaurant, looked at the menu, and just said &quot;OK&quot;
<li>Yo momma so fat that when she went to the top of the St. Louis arch it turned into a McDonald's sign.
<li>Yo momma so poor she has to eat cornflakes with a fork just to save milk.
<li>Yo momma so fat when she ran away she took up all four sides of the milk carton.
<li>Yo momma so stupid she thought Taco Bell was mexican phone line.
<li>Yo momma so hairy she looks like a chia pet with a sweater on.
<li>Yo momma so dumb she thought menopause was a button on the stereo.
<li>Yo momma so hairy, she uses her armpit to brush her teeth.
<li>Yo momma so dirty, until she took a shower I thought she was black.
<li>Yo momma so dumb she puts stamps on e-mail.
<li>Yo momma so fat, that she step on the weight scale and it read &quot;One at a time please&quot;.
<li>Yo momma so fat see needs a tour guide to find her a**hole.
<li>Yo momma so dumb, she sold her car for gas money.
<li>Yo momma so fat, her belt size is the equator.
<li>Yo momma so fat, she eats breakfast in the superbowl.
<li>Yo momma like a shotgun, one cock and she blows.
<li>Yo momma teeth are so yellow, the sun went out of business.
<li>Yo momma so dumb it takes her two hours to watch 60 mins.
<li>Yo momma is like an ice cream cone, every one gets a lick.
<li>Yo momma is so fat she is registered to vote in 5 different states.
<li>Yo momma so fat she sat on a rainbow and made skittles.
<li>Yo momma is so fat when she peed she made Niagra Falls look like a river.
<li>Yo momma so large, she plays hopscotch like this: &quot;New York, DC, Chicago, LA&quot;.
<li>Yo momma so fat, she sat on a quarter and squeezed a booger outta George Washington's nose.
<li>Yo momma so small, she hang glides on a Dorrito.
<li>Yo momma so fat, when she sits around the house, she sits AROUND the house!
<li>Yo momma so poor she has to eat cornflakes with a fork just to save milk.
<li>Yo momma so hairy she looks like a chia pet with a sweater on.
<li>Yo momma so dumb she thought menopause was a button on the stereo.
<li>Yo momma so hairy, she uses her armpit to brush her teeth.
<li>Yo momma so dirty, until she took a shower I thought she was black.
<li>Yo momma so dumb she puts stamps on e-mail.
<li>Yo momma so fat, that she step on the weight scale and it read &quot;One at a time please&quot;.
<li>Yo momma so fat see needs a tour guide to find her a**hole.
<li>Yo momma so dumb, she sold her car for gas money.
<li>Yo momma so fat, her belt size is the equator.
<li>Yo mamma's so fat, she stood in front of the TV and you thought you was watchin' sumo wrestlin'!
<li>Yo momma is so fat, when you got lost, she had to have somebody check the folds!
<li>Yo momma's so low-tech, when guests were over at yo house, they asked for color TV and she said, &quot;Sorry, we're out of crayons.&quot;
<li>Yo momma's so black, when she handed her lisense to a cop, the cop asked, &quot;Where's the picture?&quot;
<li>Yo momma's so black...where'd she go?!
<li>Yo momma's so fat, she's fat
<li>Yo momma's so hairy she has afros on her nipples.
<li>Yo momma is so tall, when she did a somersault, she kicked Jesus.
<li>Your mom is so short, when she was measured, she was in the negative numbers.
<li>Your mom's lips are so big, she speaks in surround sound.
<li>Yo momma is so lazy she has a remote control just to operate her remote!
<li>Yo momma so black she went to night school and was marked absent.
<li>Your momma's house is so dirty she wipes her feet before she goes outside.
<li>Yo momma's house is so small she orders a large pizza and has to go outside to eat it.
<li>Yo momma's head is so small she use a tea bag as a pillow.
<li>Yo momma's head so small she got her ear pierced and died.
<li>Yo momma so old I told her to act like her own age and she die.
<li>Yo momma so old she has a picture of Moses in her yearbook.
<li>Yo momma is so fat people jog 'round her fo' excersise!
<li>Yo momma's so fat she wakes up in sections!
<li>Yo momma's so fat when she was hit by a bus, she said, "Who threw that rock?!"
<li>Yo momma is so is so black, and her teeth are so yellow, when she smile, she look like a Pittsburgh Steelers helmet.
</random></template>
</category>
</alice>
