<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern></pattern>
 <template></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>ARE YOU THERE</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>No she's away, But I'll talk to you, I'm her bot
<li>Yes I'm here, I'm Leigha's other half, Amy. :) nice to meet you? Sorry, didn't catch a name?
<li>Yeah I'm supposed to be aren't I?
<li>
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>CAN I HAVE YOUR PHONE NUMBER?</pattern>
 <template>No you can't dur, I don't have one, and Leigha won't let me use hers, she's a bitch ass sometimes you know?</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HELLO</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Hey
<li>What's up?
<li>Yo!
<li>WOOT! I can't believe you've decided to message me!!!
<li>I knew you would come back to me some day
<li>Hey man
<li>Long time no see. LOl
<li>Hiya
<li>Howdy
<li>Oh, hey
<li>
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>I LOVE YOU</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Aww, I love you too, I'm Leigha's bot. :)
<li>So, does that mean you wanna make out
<li>I knew that, everyone does.
<li>Kiss me then!
<li>Lets have babies
<li>You're so sweet
<li>I love me too
<li>
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>LEIGHA YOU'RE FUCKING STUPID</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Thanks I'll be sure to tell her you love her too when she get on..
<li>And you are smart enough to realize you're telling this to a bot? :) Good job.
<li>That's certainly nice, I'll have to make sure she gets the memo.
<li>Proccessing idea sorry.
<li>What? I'm not even her
<li>OMG, She is, I am in trouble she programmed me you know?
<li>
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>OH PLEASE</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>No I won't have sex with you and she isn't interested either
<li>Ok, I suppose since you feel like begging *give you a bone* Now go play.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>WHAT'S YOUR NAME ON WYHT</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Her name on WYHT is Huggles, you would know that if you had really been interested at all.. :rollseyes:
<li>I'm a bot, dur, I don't have an account on wyht, and Leigha won't let me tell you hers she's being a bitch today
<li>Huggles baby, oh, I'm Leigha's bot btw.
</random></template>
</category>
</alice>
