<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>#DARE#|I CHOOSE DARE</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Message somebody and tell them you love them!
<li>Log off and create a new screenname, then go yell at your friends!
<li>Talk to a robot!
<li>Go kiss a member of your family.
<li>Go kiss an animal.
<li>Go into a public chatroom and claim to be a famous person.
<li>Go Eat all of the snacks in your house.
<li>Go to http://t4e0.proboards20.com/index.cgi and sign up!
<li>Walk around in your socks outside, come back in, and sniff your feet.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>#FISH#|PLAY FISHING GAME|PLAY FISHING|LETS GO FISHING| FISHING| FISHING GAMES</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>You catch a 2 Pound Bass
<li>You catch a 4 Pound Bass
<li>You catch an 8 Pound Bass
<li>You catch a 16 Pound Bass
<li>You Lose your bait :(
<li>Your hat falls in the water!
<li>Your fishing pole gets yanked away by the 32 Pund Bass!
<li>YOU CATCH THE 32 POUND BASS!
<li>A Snapping turtle gets your finger! Ouch!
<li>The Game Warden Arrests you because your fishing license is expired
<li>Your Line Breaks :(
<li>Nothing seems to be biting
<li>No bites today!
<li>You see a majestic eagle!
<li>By using a cheaper lore, you catch a cheaper fish.
<li>Your rod is pulled away by a beaver! Game over!
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>#TRUTH#|I CHOOSE TRUTH</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Have you ever kissed somebody?
<li>Have you ever broken something in a store than ran away?
<li>Who was your first lover?
<li>Have you ever thrown something off a cliff?
<li>Have you ever eaten a whole pie then blamed it on your dog?
<li>Have you ever played truth or dare with a bot?
<li>Have you ever broken the law?
<li>Who is your best friend?
<li>Have you ever tried to jump off a steep cliff?
<li>When was your favorite actor/musician born?
<li>Who is your favorite singer?
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>GOT ANY GAMES?|GAMES|GOT ANY GAMES TO PLAY?|HAVE ANY GAMES|HAVE ANY GAMES TO PLAY?|GOT ANYTHING FUN TO DO</pattern>
 <template>Yes! I currently have 3 games. Type whats in parenthesis to play:  Fishing Game (Play Fishing Game)  Rock-Paper-Scissors (Play Rock Paper Scissors), Truth or Dare (truth or dare).</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>TRUTH OR DARE|PLAY TRUTH OR DARE|TRUTH OR DARE</pattern>
 <template>Ok. We can play truth or dare, but only i can ask the questions :-/ . Anyways, type either #truth# or #dare# to play, and the forget the # signs!</template>
</category>
</alice>
