<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>*</pattern>
 <template>Hello, Welcome to the Highschool Stereotype Quiz. To find out which Highschool Stereotype/Label you are, just type Highschool Stereotype Quiz! For questions, email ghosty13@sbcglobal.net</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>ANSWERS</pattern>
 <template>Ok, here are your results:    Mostly As: You're a Prep! Bitch/Bastard!  Mostly Bs: You're a Goth! YAY!  Mostly Cs: You're a Punk! Niiiice...  Mostly Ds: You're a Loser! Whatever...  Mostly Es: You're a Slut! Ew...  Mostly Fs: You're a Geek! Techie!    NOTE: This quiz is for entertainment value only and should be treated as such. :-)</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HI</pattern>
 <template>Hello, Welcome to the Highschool Stereotype Quiz. To find out which Highschool Stereotype/Label you are, just type Highschool Stereotype Quiz! For questions, email ghosty13@sbcglobal.net</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HIGHSCHOOL STEREOTYPE QUIZ</pattern>
 <template>Okay, so you want to take the quiz.   1. Do you kick ass?   A.Totally!    B.Leave me alone, bitch!    C.Hell, yeah!    D.I eat ass for breakfast. FRESH ass.    E.Yeah...and I like it...    F.Please don't swear.  2. What do you think you are?   A.Prep    B.Goth    C.Punk    D.Loser    E.Slut    F.Geek  3. What do you do for fun?   A.Call my friends to go shopping!    B.Write poems or something...    C.Play in my awesome band.    D.Uh...I dunno...collect stamps or something.    E.Go get some [you know what I mean].    F.Make a website.  4. Ho, ho, ho!   A.What-EVER.    B.I want to die.    C.I want to kill you.    D.Where? WHERE?    E.Right here, me.    F.Merry Christmas?  5. What would I find in your backpack?   A.Bubble Gum and Lipgloss    B.A journal filled with depressing rants, and maybe some money if I'm lucky.    C.A pack of safety pins, and a CD player.    D.Cigarretes and some pot.    E.Erotica novel and some shower pics.    F.School books and medicines  6. Which color scheme is the best?   A.Pink and purple    B.Black and red    C.Black and yellow    D.Gray and blue    E.Purple and orange    F.Brown and white   7. Would you rather wear...   A.Hottest designer fashions    B.Baggy jeans, sweatshirt, sneakers. Or maybe pajamas. Whatever I feel like that day.    C.Safety Pins EVERYWHERE!!! Oh, and ripped stuff, too.    D.Anything. Skater or Ghetto clothes, I guess. I dunno.    E.Low-cut stuff. See-through. Undergarments seeable.    F.Sweater vest and burlap pants. Plaid or checkered, of course.  8. You are at a school dance. You:   A.Ask to dance with the hottest guy/girl you can find.    B.Stand in the corner. Hoping someone will ask you. Which they won't. Or not go at all.    C.Request some good ol' hardcore songs.    D.Hand out free, 100 columbian drugs in the bathroom.    E.Shake your ass around at random people.    F.My mommy doesn't let me go to dances. If I can go, when I'm lucky, I do my cool new dance I made up myself! It's kind of like ballroom...blah, blah, blah...   9. Did you enjoy this quiz?   A.It was super-fun! But I am still WAY more popular than you.    B.It was okay, I guess.    C.Nice...ARGH, I poked myself with a safety pin...AGAIN!    D....whatever...I dunno...    E.I love you!    F.Very interesting, Great job.    Ask for the answers once you have written down all the letters. Example:  1.A  2.B  3.A  4.A  5.A  6.E  7.D  8.A  9.A    To ask for the answers, just type Answers</template>
</category>
</alice>
