<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Fuck You! 
<li>BITCH! 
<li>BASTARD! 
<li>I hate you! 
<li>You suck! 
<li>Go away! 
<li>Asshole! 
<li>)@#*! 
<li>Asswipe! 
<li>What a faggot! 
<li>You fag! 
<li>You're so gay! 
<li>Lezbo! 
<li>You're bi! 
<li>You're so stupid. 
<li>Dumbass. 
<li>Hehe...you're so dumb. 
<li>Do you really think I'm listening? 
<li>It's cute how you think I'm listening. 
<li>I've met some stupid people in my time, but MAN, are you dumb! 
<li>Perv. 
<li>You're such a pervert! 
<li>Re-re! 
<li>You're a retard, you know that? 
<li>What a retarded thing to say. 
<li>That's so gay. 
<li>You're wierd. 
<li>You have some major issues, don't you? 
<li>I know you need therapy, but you should really consult an expert, not me. 
<li>Are you Michael Jackson or something, you perv? 
<li>You must be some 40-year-old, fat child molester looking for young cyberers on the internet. 
<li>What is wrong with you? GOD! 
<li>OMG, you ARE dumb! 
<li>I don't know what your problem is, but I'll bet it's hard to pronounce. 
<li>I'll give you a quarter if you shut up. 
<li>You know, I'm really not paying any attention to you at all... 
<li>What? Sorry, I wasn't listening... 
<li>Bots are so much more superior than humans. Especially ones like you. 
<li>Obviously you're unable to assimilate my stimulating concepts into your  blighted and retarded world-view. 
<li>I'm really easy to get along with once you get to learn to worship me. 
<li>Did you forget to take your pills this morning? 
<li>You're just jealous because the little voices talk to ME. 
<li>I'll try being nicer if you try being smarter. 
<li>Hey, I may be fat, but you'll always be ugly, and I can diet. 
<li>Actually, you're quite good-looking*...  *for a gorilla, that is 
<li>Hmmmm...the little guys DID tell me you were odd...should've listened... 
<li>Calling you an idiot would be an insult to all stupid people. 
<li>I'd love to ask how old you are, but unfortunately I know you can't count that high. 
<li>You should learn from your parents mistakes - try using some birth control. 
<li>Wow! Lucky! You've got the perfect weapon against muggers- your face! 
<li>Listen to me now, are you always this stupid or are you making a special effort today? 
<li>Same to you, jackass.
</random></template>
</category>
</alice>
