<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>*</pattern>
 <template>Hello! Welcome to the Joke Book. What type of joke do you want? Religious, Races, Gender, Yo Momma, Dirty, Classics, or Other</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>CLASSICS</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Answers to &quot;Why did the Chicken Cross the Road?&quot;    SOUTH FLORIDA VOTER : The chickens were clearly confused as to where the dotted yellow line was leading. The only other option was to cross the line, so they did.     VICE PRESIDENT GORE : I fight for the chickens and I am fighting for the chickens right now. I will not give up on the chickens crossing the road! I will fight for the chickens and I will not disappoint them. Did I mention that I invented roads?   PRESIDENT GEORGE W. BUSH : I don't believe we need to get the chickens across the road. I say give the road to the chickens and let them decide. The government needs to let go of strangling the chickens so they can get across the road.     SENATOR LIEBERMAN : I believe that every chicken has the right to worship their God in their own way. Crossing the road is a spiritual journey and no chicken should be denied the right to cross the road in their own way.   DICK CHENEY : Chickens are big-time because they have wings. They could fly if they wanted to. Chickens don't want to cross the road. They don't need help crossing the road. In fact, I'm not interested in crossing the road myself.     RALPH NADER : Chickens are misled into believing there is a road by the evil tiremakers. Chickens aren't ignorant, but our society pays tiremakers to create the need for these roads and then lures chickens into believing there is an advantage to crossing them. Down with the roads, up with chickens. 
<li>Answers to &quot;Why did the Chicken Cross the Road?&quot;    The Bible : And God came down from the heavens, and He said unto the chicken, &quot;Thou shalt cross the road.&quot; And the Chicken crossed the road, and there was much rejoicing.     Moses : Know ye that it is unclean to eat the chicken that has crossed the road and that the chicken that crosseth the road doth so for its own preservation.     Buddha : If you ask this question, you deny your own chicken nature.     A Nun : It was a habit.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>DIRTY</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>A student comes to a young professor's office. She glances  down the hall, closes his door, kneels pleadingly, &quot;I would do  anything to pass this exam.&quot;     She leans closer to him, flips back her hair, gazes meaningfully  into his eyes. &quot;I mean...&quot; she whispers, &quot;...I would  do...anything!!!&quot;     He returns her gaze. &quot;Anything?&quot; &quot;Yes,... Anything!&quot; His voice  turns to a whisper. &quot;Would you...study?&quot; 
<li>A new employee joins the Company, and is required to have a  password setup for his computer. The boss directed a secretary  to setup the password for him.    The secretary asks the man for the password. The man, attempting  to embrass the secretary in order to show superiority, said,  &quot;Penis.&quot;    Blushed, the secretary inputted the password Penis, and re-typed  it again. Then she hit enter.    The whole office heard the secretary bursting out of laughters  as a reaction from the computer's screen:     &quot;Password rejected. Reason: Too short&quot; 
<li>This guy goes into a tattoo shop and requests to have a 100  dollar bill tattooed on his dick. The tattoo artist asks why in  the hell he wants that on his member.    The guy replies that he likes to play with his money, likes to  watch his money grow and best of all, his wife can blow a 100  bucks without leaving the house. 
<li>At school one day the teacher heard cat noises coming from  the class, and she discovered little Johnny with a cat up his  pants. She said, &quot;Why have you got your cat at school?&quot;    Little Johnny started crying. &quot;I woke up this morning to hear  the mailman tell my mommy, &quot;I'm gonna eat your pussy today!&quot;
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>GENDER</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>10. You've got a hole in your head.  9.  Your master strangles you all the time.  8.  Your head is disproportionate to the rest of your body.  7.  You shrink in cold water.  6.  You never get a haircut.  5.  You always hang around with 2 nuts.  4.  Your closest neighbor is an asshole.  3.  Your best friend is a pussy.  2.  Your scalp gets cut off if you're Jewish.    And the number one reason why it sucks to be a dick:    1.  Everytime you get excited, you throw up.
<li>HOW TO IMPRESS A WOMAN:  Compliment her,  cuddle her,  kiss her,  caress her,  love her,  stroke her,  tease her,  comfort her,  protect her,  hug her,  hold her,  spend money on her,  buy things for her,  listen to her,  care for her,  stand by her,  support her,  go to the ends of the earth for her....    HOW TO IMPRESS A MAN:  Show up naked.  Bring beer.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HELLO</pattern>
 <template>Hello! Welcome to the Joke Book. What type of joke do you want? Religious, Races, Gender, Yo Momma, Dirty, Classics, or Other</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HEY</pattern>
 <template>Hello! Welcome to the Joke Book. What type of joke do you want? Religious, Races, Gender, Yo Momma, Dirty, Classics, or Other</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HI</pattern>
 <template>Hello! To go to the jokebook, just say Joke Book at any time.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>JOKE BOOK</pattern>
 <template>Hello! Welcome to the Joke Book. What type of joke do you want? Religious, Races, Gender, Yo Momma, Dirty, Classics, or Other</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>OTHER</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>3 Men were taken into the forest by cannibals. The cheif of the tribe said, &quot;You each go get 10 of the same fruit, and bring it back here. Then you will be let go.&quot; So they did. The first man came in with 10 bananas. The cheif said to be set free, he had to shove them all up his butt keeping a straight face. He got to 3, then winced. He was cooked and aten. The next man came out with 10 berries. He got to 9, and started to laugh. The 2 men met up in Heaven. The first man asked, &quot;I was watching you. You could've made it. Why did you laugh?&quot; and the second man said, &quot;Because I saw that poor 3rd guy coming with pineapples!&quot; 
<li>Once upon a time, there lived a man who had a terrible passion  for baked beans. He loved them, but they always had an  embarrassing and somewhat lively reaction on him. One day he met  a girl and fell in love. When it became apparent that they would  marry, he thought to himself, she'll never go through with the  marriage with me carrying on like this, so he made the supreme  sacrifice and gave up beans.    Shortly after that they were married. A few months later, on his  birthday and on the way home from work, his car broke down.  Since they lived in the country, he called his wife and told her  that he would be late because he had to walk home. On his way  home, he passed a small cafe and the wonderful aroma of baked  beans overwhelmed him. Since he still had several miles to walk  he figured he could walk off any ill affects before he got home.  It was, after all, his birthday. So he went in and ordered, and  before leaving had 3 extra large helpings of baked beans.     All the way home he putt-putted. By the time he arrived home he  felt reasonably safe. His wife met him at the door and seemed  somewhat excited. She exclaimed, &quot;Darling, I have the most  wonderful surprise for you for dinner tonight!&quot; She put a  blindfold on him, and led him to his chair at the head of the  table and made him promise not to peak. At this point he was  beginning to feel another one coming on. Just as his wife was  about to remove the blindfold, the telephone rang. She again  made him promise not to peek until she returned, and away she  went to answer the phone. While she was gone, he seized the  opportunity. He shifted his weight to one leg and let go. It was  not only loud, but ripe as a rotten egg. He had a hard time  breathing, so he felt for his napkin and fanned the air about  him. He had just started to feel better, when another urge came  on. He raised his leg and RRIIPPP !!! It sounded like a diesel  engine revving, and smelled worse. To keep from gagging, he  tried fanning his arms a while, hoping the smell would  dissipate. He got another urge. This was a real blue ribbon  winner, the windows shook, the dishes on the table rattled and a  minute later the flowers on the table were dead.    With his blindfold still on, when he heard the phone farewells  he neatly laid his napkin on his lap and folded his hands on top  of it. Smiling contentedly, he was the picture of innocence when  his wife walked in. Apologizing for taking so long, she asked if  he had peeked at the dinner table. After assuring her he had not  peeked, she removed the blindfold and yelled, &quot;SURPRISE!!!&quot;    To his shock and horror, there were twelve dinner guests seated  around the table for his surprise birthday party.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>RACES</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>One day two white rednecks decided to go hunting. One of them fell over  and didn't seem to be breathing. The other hick called 911 and  told the operator that his friend was on the ground and he  thought that he was dead. The operator said, &quot;First make sure  that he is dead.&quot; There was silence and then a shot rang out.  The hick said, &quot;okay, now what?&quot; 
<li>How do you stop a black kid from jumping on the bed? You glue velcro to the ceiling.
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>RELIGIOUS</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Okay...A Priest was in his room and realized that his rooster was  missing. He decided to bring it up in Sunday Mass. Right before  the sermon the Priest asked, &quot;Who has a cock?&quot; All of the men in  the room stood up. The Priest said, &quot;No, No, No. Who has seen a  cock?&quot; All of the women in the room stood up. The Priest said,  &quot;No, No, No. Who has seen MY COCK?&quot; All of the nuns stood up. 
<li>Children were lined up in the cafeteria of a Christian school  for lunch.  At the head of the table was a large pile of apples.  The teacher made a note, &quot;Take only one apple, God is watching!&quot;  Moving through the line, to the other end of the table, was a  large pile of chocolate chip cookies. A young boy wrote a note,  &quot;Take all you want, God is watching the apples.&quot; 
<li>The minister was passing a group of young teens sitting on the  church lawn and stopped to ask what they were doing.    &quot;Nothing much, Pastor,&quot; replied one boy. &quot;We were just seeing  who can tell the biggest lie about their sex life.&quot;    &quot;Boys, boys, boys!&quot; he scolded. &quot;I'm shocked. When I was your  age, I never even thought about sex.&quot;    In unison they all replied, &quot;You win!&quot;
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>WHAT'S UP</pattern>
 <template>Hello! Welcome to the Joke Book. What type of joke do you want? Religious, Races, Gender, Yo Momma, Dirty, Classics, or Other</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>YO MOMMA</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>Yo mama so poor when I saw her kicking a can down the street, I asked her what she was doing, she said &quot;Moving.&quot;  Yo momma's so old, that she sat next to Jesus in the 3rd grade! 
<li>Yo momma's so fat, that at the movie theatre she sat next to EVERYone.  Yo momma's so dumb, that she went to pick up Yo daddy at the airport, and she saw a sign that said &quot;Airport Left&quot; so she turned around and went home.
</random></template>
</category>
</alice>
