<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>AUDIO</pattern>
 <template>Linkin Park has created many great singles and thanks to www.linkin-inside.com I can share some of these with you. The following commands send you a link to the cooresponding song: Somewhere I Belong, Hit The Floor, Faint, Breaking The Habit, Nobodys Listening, Numb, Pts Of Athrty, Enth E Nd, Plc4 Mie Haed, PPR KUT, My Dsmbr, Papercut, One Step Closer, Crawling, and In The End.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>BAND</pattern>
 <template>The Band Linkin Park began with just Mike Shinoda and Brad Delson in bedroom studio. These two had attended high school together. Rob Bourdon was the drummer at the time and he also went to their high school. Mike met Joe Hahn at an Art Center in Pasadena. Brad on the other hand was attending UCLA at this time where he share an apartment with Phoenix. They were known as Xero at this time. In the year of 1999 Chester was the last missing link to this chain. When he was added this is at the time when they first were known as Hybrid Theory. But they changed their name to Linkin Park later for legal reasons. After being turned down at a discouraging three times, Warner Bros. Signed them in late 1999. At this time the got to work on their debut album. Using some things from the past they named their album Hybrid Theory. This album was released in the fall of 2000.  Crawling and One Step Closer were major hits. Their videos became very popular, too In the year of 2001 the did a total number of 324 shows. In 2002 Hybrid Theory brought three Grammy nominations for &quot;Best Rock Album&quot; and &quot;Best New Artist&quot;. 30 days later Linkin Park took home the award for Best Hard Rock Performance for &quot;Crawling&quot; Hybrid Theory hit platinum eight times. In the year of 2003 Meteora was released. The song Somewhere I belong was the major first hit for this album.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>BIO</pattern>
 <template>Which member did you want to know about? Chester, Mike, Rob, Brad, Phoenix, or Joe? Or did you want to know about the band in general? If so, type Band. *** These biographies courtacy of www.chestersings.com</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>BRAD</pattern>
 <template>Brad Delson was born on December 1,1977 in Agoura, California. Brad grew up in Agoura with Mike. They met in the 7th grade. Brad's first band was called Pricks. Then he went on to form a band which included Rob. But this band lasted not long at all. Brad had a mullet in high school. Brad graduated in 1996. In the year of 1996 is when Xero was formed. After high school he went on to attend UCLA where he got his bachelor's degree in communications. Brad met Phoenix at UCLA  Brad has played the trumpet and the flute. In the year of 1996 is when Xero was formed.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>BREAKING THE HABIT</pattern>
 <template>http://linkin-inside.com/dnload/audio/meteora/09-Breaking_The_Habit.mp3</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>CHESTER</pattern>
 <template>Chester Bennington born on March 20, 1976 in Phoenix , Arizona. When Chester was at the age of 11 his parents went through a divorce. He has two half sisters and a half brother. Chester attended Centennial High School at the beginning of his freshmen year. But later he went to Greenway High. Around this time Chester was battling a drug addiction. This is where ,his first band , Grey Daze became. Grey Daze started in 1993. Grey daze releases two CDs &quot;Sun Today&quot; and &quot;Wake Me&quot;. He graduated in the year of 1994 from Washington High. Chester got married to Samantha on October 31, 1996. Draven Sebastian Bennington , Chester's first child, was born on April 19, 2002.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>COLLISION COURSE</pattern>
 <template>Release Date: November 30th, 2004 Producer: Matt Caltabiano 01 Dirt Off Your Shoulder/Lying From You  02 Big Pimpin'/Papercut  03 Jigga What/Faint  04 Numb/Encore  05 IZZO/In The End  06 Points Of Authority/99 Problems/One Step Closer</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>CRAWLING</pattern>
 <template>http://linkin-inside.com/dnload/audio/hybrid_theory/05-Crawling.mp3</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>DISC</pattern>
 <template>Linkin Park has released many CDs. Which one would you like information on? Hybrid Theory EP, Hybrid Theory, ReAnimation, LP Underground v2.0, Meteora, Live In Texas, LP Underground v3.0, LP Underground v4.0, or Collision Course? *** These discographys couracy of www.forfeitthegame.com</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>ENTH E ND</pattern>
 <template>http://linkin-inside.com/dnload/audio/reanimation/03-Enth_E_Nd.mp3</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>FAINT</pattern>
 <template>http://linkin-inside.com/dnload/audio/meteora/07-Faint.mp3</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>FANSITES</pattern>
 <template>www.lpfuse.co.uk is a great fansite! It actually is a fansite for Machine Shop Records, a Record Company set up by Linkin Park that has contracts with four bands excluding Linkin Park. www.forfeitthegame.com has lots of good information about Linkin Park. Check out the rare downloads section that is updated every few days. You can find some pretty hard to find live preformances and promotional songs there! www.linkin-inside.com is the best place for finding linkin park music. Though it is in German, it has the largest known collection of Linkin Park music hosted. So check out the media section for me! :-p www.chestersings.com is the greatest place to download live preformances. They update the live audio section every few days so quickly download the preformances while you can. Besides that it offers an exellent community on their forum. www.pushmeaway.com has an exellent database on wonderful facts about Linkin Park.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HIT THE FLOOR</pattern>
 <template>http://linkin-inside.com/dnload/audio/meteora/05-Hit_The_Floor.mp3</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HYBRID THEORY</pattern>
 <template>Release Date: October 24th, 2000 Producer: Don Gilmore 01 Papercut  02 One Step Closer  03 With You  04 Points of Authority  05 Crawling  06 Runaway  07 By Myself  08 In The End  09 A Place For My Head  10 Forgotten  11 Cure For The Itch  12 Pushing Me Away</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HYBRID THEORY EP</pattern>
 <template>Release Date: November 21st, 2001  Producer: Mike Shinoda  01 Carousel  02 Technique (Short)  03 Step Up  04 And One  05 High Voltage  06 Part of Me</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>IN THE END</pattern>
 <template>http://linkin-inside.com/dnload/audio/hybrid_theory/08-In_The_End.mp3</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>JOE</pattern>
 <template>Joe Hahn was born on March 15, 1977 in Glendale California where he grew up. Joe is Korean. He did some track in high school. Joe went to college at Pasadena art college. Here me majored in illustrations. Joe and Mike met in college. They both were interested in painting. Joe stayed in college for a year. Then he moved in to motion pictured. He helped with &quot;Sphere&quot; and &quot;Phantoms&quot;. Joe has a split personality called Remy. Remy first debuted in &quot;Cure for the Itch&quot;. &quot;Mr. Hahn&quot; tends to invent things while talking to new fans who don't know Linkin Park very well. He will make up nonsense things. Joe also tends to get very bored and they say he has a dry sense of humor. Joe came up with the idea for &quot;One Step Closer&quot; , the video. He is the official video person for the band.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>LINKIN PARK</pattern>
 <template>Well I know a lot about Linkin Park and understand the following commands: Bio, Disc, Audio, Fansites, Officialsites</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>LIVE IN TEXAS</pattern>
 <template>Release Date: November 17/24th, 2003 Producer & Mixer: Josh Abraham 01 Somewhere I Belong (Live)  02 Lying From You (Live)  03 Papercut (Live)  04 Points of Authority (Live)  05 Runaway (Live)  06 Faint (Live)  07 From The Inside (Live)  08 P5hng Me A*wy (Live)  09 Numb (Live)  10 Crawling (Live)  11 In The End (Live)  12 One Step Closer (Live)</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>LP UNDERGROUND V2</pattern>
 <template>Release Date: November 21st, 2002 Producer: Various 01 A.06  02 With You (Live)  03 PTS.OF.ATHRTY (Crystal Method Remix)  04 Dedicated (Demo 1999)  05 High Voltage (Live)  06 My December</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>LP UNDERGROUND V3</pattern>
 <template>Release Date: November 21st, 2003 Producer: Josh Abraham 01 Don't Stay (Live)  02 Figure.09 (Live)  03 With You (Live)  04 By Myself (Live)  05 A Place For My Head (Live)</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>LP UNDERGROUND V4</pattern>
 <template>Release Date: November 21st, 2004 Producer: Mike Shinoda 01 Sould My Soul To Yo Mama  02 Breaking The Habit (Live)  03 Standing In the Middle (Feat/ Motion Man)  04 Step Up/Nobody's Listening/It's Goin' Down (Live)  05 Wish (Nine Inch Nails Cover) (Live)  06 One Step Closer (Feat/ Jon Davis) (Live)</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>METEORA</pattern>
 <template>Release Date: March 24/25th, 2003 Producer: Don Gilmore 01 Foreword  02 Don't Stay  03 Somewhere I Belong  04 Lying From You  05 Hit The Floor  06 Easier To Run  07 Faint  08 Figure.09  09 Breaking The Habit  10 From The Inside  11 Nobody's Listening  12 Session  13 Numb</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>MIKE</pattern>
 <template>Mike Kenji Shinoda was born on February 11, 1977 in Aougora , Cali where he grew up. He met Brad in the 7th grade. He went to Agoura high. After finish high school he went to Pasadena Art College of Design where he majored in Illustration but studied graphic design. Here at college he met Joe. After graduating college he got a job as a graphic designer. Mike got married in May of 2003 Mike took classical piano lessons for 10 years he got sick of playing classical music and moved into jazz and then on to hip hop.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>MY{DSMBR</pattern>
 <template>http://linkin-inside.com/dnload/audio/reanimation/15-My_Dsmbr.mp3</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>NOBODYS LISTENING</pattern>
 <template>http://linkin-inside.com/dnload/audio/meteora/11-Nobody's_Listening.mp3</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>NUMB</pattern>
 <template>http://linkin-inside.com/dnload/audio/meteora/13-Numb.mp3</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>OFFICIALSITES</pattern>
 <template>www.linkinpark.com is the official site for Linkin Park. www.linkinparkmerch.com is the official site for all your Linkin Park Merchandise needs. www.projektrevolution.com is the official site for a special project or &quot;projekt&quot; Linkin Park created uniting some of the greatest bands to tour America. www.lpunderground.com is Linkin Park's official fan club. There are many goodies available to you if you join it! ;) www.lpstreetteam.com is Linkin Park's street team's official website. You must be a member to enter the site. www.lpjz.com is the official site for MTV's mash-up album with Linkin Park and Jay-Z called Collision Course.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>ONE STEP CLOSER</pattern>
 <template>http://linkin-inside.com/dnload/audio/hybrid_theory/02-One_Step_Closer.mp3</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>PAPERCUT</pattern>
 <template>http://linkin-inside.com/dnload/audio/hybrid_theory/01-Papercut.mp3</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>PHOENIX</pattern>
 <template>David &quot;Phoenix&quot; Farrell was born on February 8 ,1977 in Plymouth, Massachusetts were he grew up. He also lived in Mission Viejo, Ca. After moving to California he join the band &quot;Tasty Snax&quot; in high school. Later the band changed their name to &quot;The Snax&quot;. While with the Snax he switched from guitar to bass. Phoenix was the first bass player go Xero. After joining Xero he went back to the Snax and toured with them for about a year and a half. Then came back to Linkin Park. Phoenix graduated from UCLA Phoenix can play many instruments like the violin and cello which he played for the Reanimation album. Phoenix was married on December 28,2002.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>PLC4 MIE HAED</pattern>
 <template>http://linkin-inside.com/dnload/audio/reanimation/07-Plc.4_Mie_Haed.mp3</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>PPR KUT</pattern>
 <template>http://linkin-inside.com/dnload/audio/reanimation/13-PPr_Kut.mp3</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>PTS OF ATHRTY</pattern>
 <template>http://linkin-inside.com/dnload/audio/reanimation/02-Pts.Of.Athrty.mp3</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>REANIMATION</pattern>
 <template>Release Date: July 30th, 2002 Producer: Mike Shinoda 01 OPENING  02 PTS.OF.ATHRTY  03 ENTH E ND  04 [CHALI]  05 FRGT/10  06 P5HNG ME A*WY  07 PLC.4 MIE HAED  08 X-ECUTIONER STYLE  09 H! VLTG3  10 [RIFF RAFF]  11 WTH>YOU  12 NTR\MSSION  13 PPR:KUT  14 RNW@Y  15 MY<DSMBR  16 [STEF]  17 BY_MYSELF  18 KYUR4 TH ICH  19 1STP KLOSR  20 KRWLNG</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>ROB</pattern>
 <template>Rob Bourdon was born on January 20, 1979 in Calabasas California. He started to play the drums at age 11. Rob was in to &quot;funk&quot; in high school. Rob attended Agoura High school. After finishing high school he moved on and when to Santa Monica College for accounting. Rob worked as a waiter at one point in his life. Rob's first band was Relative Degree with Brad. The practiced tons but after one show they fell apart. His first real performance was at &quot;The Roxy&quot; in Los Angeles in 1995. Rob also knows how to play the piano.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>SOMEWHERE I BELONG</pattern>
 <template>http://linkin-inside.com/dnload/audio/meteora/03-Somwhere_I_Belong.mp3</template>
</category>
</alice>
