<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>*TELL ME A RIDDLE*</pattern>
 <template>-_- Fine I'll tell you a Riddle. What you think thats funny?! My Last name is no joke. Now lets see if your smart enough to figure out these Riddles. Type the word 'Riddle' to begin. Smartass.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>RIDDLE</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>I make your teeth go chitter, At the same time I am sweet, Some of my friends are bitter, But people them do eat. My name constists of two words, With a hyphen inbetween, One part is food for owl-birds, The other one is cold, if you know what I mean. So be careful when you choose me, For I am more than I seem, But don?t hesitate to take me, I see it in your eyes, the gleam? What am I? <nextreply>....<nextreply>.....<nextreply>......<nextreply>.......<nextreply>Ice-Mice!
<li>One of four Bloodline pure History and secrets I buried them low and deep Listened Spoke Disagreed Left If you heard me speak You may not understand But the last words your hear Were my sole command I left behind My virtues; my beliefs And one day My work will be finished<nextreply>....<nextreply>.....<nextreply>......<nextreply>.......<nextreply>Salazar Slytherin
<li>Looks can be deceiving, And they certainly were with me. Betrayal and lying, People dying, Makes no difference to me. I'd do anything to help him get that wretched boy. That would make my master's empty heart fill up with bubbling joy. Much in common I have with him, We killed the people we &quot;loved&quot; or not. I disguised myself for this man, I'm doing everything I can. For years and years I endured it all Just to see that Potter's life come to a sudden halt.<nextreply>....<nextreply>.....<nextreply>......<nextreply>.......<nextreply>Barty Crouch Jr
<li>Bifocals rest on the bridge of her nose, rose is the color of fingers and toes I suppose, as her fingernails are red but red hair is not on top of her head. ࠆleur Delacour, elle est un auteur Prestigous title, debated for sure to those who might find her words an offense others are just made incredibly tense She bugs many people to whom she's known Her stories are false, their words are not shown to hold much truth about people and things 'til blackmail forces in honesty's ring.<nextreply>....<nextreply>.....<nextreply>......<nextreply>.......<nextreply>Rita Skeeter
<li>The opposite of active, the state of calm atoms the end of my name is the end of this word I am one of ten like my brethren I am native to a specific area Given a name by one whom I belonged I was taken away but not forgotten The beginning of my name is the combining of two but not this or that neither and both The fourth letter of my name sounds like she who stings only one letter the second of a complete set<nextreply>....<nextreply>.....<nextreply>......<nextreply>.......<nextreply>Norbert.
<li>I came to Hogwarts and graduated 1988, I came back at the time of Harry's almost, yet terrible fate. I came in first in a family of nine, I handle money but it's definitely not mine. I've got a fang on a part of my body, long hair is my style, A woman was once staring at me, which was caught by Harry's eye. I took a desk job and that's where my love started, I joined the Order of which cannot be parted. I wear dragon hide on my feet, muggle clothes is what I've got, My charm would outwit anyone, do you think they have not? I respect my family with pride, unlike a dear brother that is so uncool, One quality we share is that we were both Prefects at our dear old school. <nextreply>....<nextreply>.....<nextreply>......<nextreply>.......<nextreply>Bill Weasley
<li>Your Headmaster had me, when he was young and free Years later, he had me a second time around You can have just one, but numerous are we If I am the wrong one, I can end up on the ground If you ask me if I am small, my response would be &quot;yup&quot; Be very wary, for I could make you puke I am so tiny, many of me can fit in just one cup If you want to find me, you can start at Honeydukes What am I? <nextreply>....<nextreply>.....<nextreply>......<nextreply>.......<nextreply>Bertie Bott's Every Flavor Beans
</random></template>
</category>
</alice>
