<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>*BUMBER*STICKERS*</pattern>
 <template>Well, this day was a total waste of makeup. Make yourself at home! Clean my kitchen.Don't bother me. I'm living happily ever after.  Do I look like a freakin' people person?   Want More Type BUMBER STICKERS 2</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*BUMBER*STICKERS2*</pattern>
 <template>This isn't an office. It's Hell with fluorescent lighting.I started out with nothing & still have most of it left.I pretend to work. They pretend to pay me.Want More? Type BUMBER STICKERS3</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*BUMBER*STICKERS3*</pattern>
 <template>I like cats, too. Let's exchange recipes. Whatever kind of look you were going for, you missed.Suburbia: where they tear out the trees & then name streets after them.Want More Type BUMBER STICKERS4</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*BUMBER*STICKERS4*</pattern>
 <template>I'm just working here till a good fast-food job opens up.  Are those your eyeballs? I'm not your type. I'm not inflatable.  I'm trying to imagine you with a personality.  Want More Type BUMBER STICKERS5</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*BUMBER*STICKERS5*</pattern>
 <template>Stress is when you wake up screaming & you realize you haven't fallen asleep yet.Adults are just kids who own money.You say I'm a bytch like it's a bad thing.  Want More Type BUMBER STICKERS6</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*BUMBER*STICKERS6*</pattern>
 <template>Too many freaks, not enough circuses.If I want to hear the pitter patter of little feet, I'll put shoes on my cat.You look like shyt. Is that the style now?Want More Type BUMBER STICKERS7</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*BUMBER*STICKERS7*</pattern>
 <template>Earth is full. Go home.Is it time for your medication or mine?Does this condom make me look fat?  34. I plead contemporary insanity.And which dwarf are you?  Want More Type BUMBER STICKERS8</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>*BUMBER*STICKERS8*</pattern>
 <template>I thought I wanted a career, turns out I just wanted paychecks.How do I set a laser printer to stun?Meandering to a different drummer.I'm not tense, just terribly, terribly alert.I majored in liberal arts. Will that be for here or to go?</template>
</category>
</alice>
