<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>*YO MOM*|*YO MOMA*|*YO MOMMA*|*YO MAMA*|*YO MAMMA*|*YOUR MOM*|*YOUR MOMA*|*YOUR MOMMA*|*YOUR MAMA*|*YOUR MAMMA*|*MOM*|*MOMA*|*MOMMA*|*MAMA*|*MAMMA*</pattern>
 <template><random>
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma so greasy she sweats crisco.
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma so fat she went to a restaurant, looked at the menu, and just said &quot;OK&quot;
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma so fat that when she went to the top of the St. Louis arch it turned into a McDonald's sign.
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma so poor she has to eat cornflakes with a fork just to save milk.
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma so fat when she ran away she took up all four sides of the milk carton.
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma so stupid she thought Taco Bell was mexican phone line.
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma so hairy she looks like a chia pet with a sweater on.
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma so dumb she thought menopause was a button on the stereo.
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma so hairy, she uses her armpit to brush her teeth.
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma so dirty, until she took a shower I thought she was black.
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma so dumb she puts stamps on e-mail.
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma so fat, that she step on the weight scale and it read &quot;One at a time please&quot;.
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma so fat see needs a tour guide to find her a**hole.
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma so dumb, she sold her car for gas money.
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma so fat, her belt size is the equator.
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma so fat, she eats breakfast in the superbowl.
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma like a shotgun, one cock and she blows.
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma teeth are so yellow, the sun went out of business.
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma so dumb it takes her two hours to watch 60 mins.
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma is like an ice cream cone, every one gets a lick.
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma is so fat she is registered to vote in 5 different states.
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma so fat she sat on a rainbow and made skittles.
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma is so fat when she peed she made Niagra Falls look like a river.
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma so large, she plays hopscotch like this: &quot;New York, DC, Chicago, LA&quot;.
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma so fat, she sat on a quarter and squeezed a booger outta George Washington's nose.
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma so small, she hang glides on a Dorrito.
<li><font color=&quot;red&quot;>Yo Momma so fat, when she sits around the house, she sits AROUND the house!
<li>Yo momma's so fat, she makes Free Willy look like a tic tac
<li>Yo momma's so fat, when we played hide and seek I spotted her behind the Himalayas
<li>Yo momma's so fat, when she walked in front of the TV I missed 3 commercials
<li>Yo momma's so fat, the whale from Free Willy freed her 
<li>Yo momma's so fat, when she steps on the scale it says sorry we don't do livestock
<li>Yo momma's so fat, when she went to get a water bed, they put a blanket across Lake Michigan.
<li>Yo momma's so fat, all of her clothes have to be custom made by a contractor.
<li>Yo momma's so fat, they had to grease a door frame and hold a Twinkie on the other side to get her through. 
<li>Yo momma's so fat, she can lay down and stand up and her height doesn't change.
<li>Yo momma's so fat, when she dances, she makes the band skip.
<li>Yo momma's so fat, the horse on her Polo shirt is real. 
<li>Yo momma's so fat, when she works at the movie theatre, she works as the screen. 
<li>Yo momma's so fat, when she runs she makes the CD player skip... at the radio station.
<li>Yo momma's so fat, her belly jiggle is the first ever perpetual motion machine. 
<li>Yo momma's so fat, all the restaurants in town have signs that say: &quot;Maximum Occupancy: 240 Patrons OR Yo Mama&quot;
<li>Yo momma's so fat, when she ran away, they had to use all four sides of the milk carton.
<li>Yo momma's so fat, instead of Levis 501 jeans, she wears Levi's 1002's.
<li>Yo momma's so fat, instead of wide leg jeans, she wears wide load. 
<li>Yo momma's so fat, when she gets in an elevator, it HAS to go down. 
<li>Yo momma's so fat, all of her clothes have to be custom made by a contractor. 
<li>Yo momma's so fat, when I said I wanted &quot;Pigs in a blanket&quot; she got back in bed.
<li>Yo momma's so fat, when she was diagnosed with the flesh eating disease, the doctor gave her 5 years to live.
<li>Yo momma's so fat, she was born with a silver shovel in her mouth. 
<li>Yo momma's so fat, she's got smaller fat women orbiting around her. 
<li>Yo momma's so fat, a picture of her fell off the wall! 
<li>Yo momma's so fat, her picture takes two frames.
<li>Yo momma's so fat, when I yell &quot;Kool-Aid,&quot; she comes crashing through the wall. Yo momma's so fat, she could sell shade. 
<li>Yo momma's so fat, her cereal bowl came with a lifeguard.
<li>Yo momma's so fat, when she crosses the street, cars look out for her.
<li>Yo momma's so fat, she puts mayonnaise on aspirin.
<li>Yo momma's so big, she rollerskates on busses. 
<li>Yo momma's so big, she can't wear an X jacket cause helicopters kept landing on her back.
<li>Yo momma's so big, she uses the interstate for a Slip n Slide. 
<li>Yo momma's so big, when you climb on top of her your ears pop. 
<li>Yo momma's so big, she thought Barnum & Bailey were clothing designers. 
<li>Yo momma's so big, she whistles bass.Yo momma's so big, she uses bowling balls for earrings.
<li>Yo momma's so big, that they had to change &quot;One size fit's all&quot; to &quot;One size fits most&quot;
<li>Yo momma's so big, when she went to the airport and said she wanted to fly they stamped Goodyear on her and sent her out to the runway.
<li>Yo momma's so big, when I fingered her I lost a watch and two rings! 
<li>Yo momma's so big, when she goes in the water at the beach she changes the tide. 
<li>Yo momma's so big, when she stands up the sun goes out. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she got shot running the border after seeing a Taco Bell commercial.
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she thinks Taco Bell is where you pay your telephone bill.
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she thinks Taco Bell is a Mexican Phone Company. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she ordered a cheese burger from McDonald's and said &quot;Hold the cheese.&quot;
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she put a quarter in a parking meter and waited for a gumball to come out. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she got on her knees to drink her &quot;Nehi&quot; peach drink. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she thought Thiland was a men's clothing store. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she got fired from the M&M factory for throwing away all the W's. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, when she went to take the 44 bus, she took the 22 twice instead.
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she needed a tutor to learn how to scribble. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she ordered her sushi well done. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she thought hamburger helper came with another person.
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she thought meow mix was a record for cats. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she thought she needed a token to get on soul train.
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she invented a solar powered flashlight. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she thought the board of education was a piece of wood. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she told everyone that she was &quot;illegitiment&quot; because she couldn't read.
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she got hit by a parked car. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she sold the car for gas money. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she ran out of gas leaving Texaco. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she sold the house to pay the mortgage. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she thought Sherlock Holmes was a housing project.
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she went to a Clippers game to get a hair cut.
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she went to a Whalers game to see Shamu. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, when she saw a &quot;Wrong Way&quot; sign in her rearview mirror, she turned around.
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she thought asphalt was a skin disease.Yo momma's so stupid, she thought Delt a Airlines was a sorority.
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, when she saw the &quot;NC-17 (Under 17 Not Admitted)&quot; sign, she went home and got 16 friends. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, when your dad said it was chilly outside, she ran outside with a spoon.
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she called the 7-11 to see when they closed.
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she gave your uncle a blowjob 'cause he said it'd help his unemployment. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, when she heard 90 of all crimes occur around the home, she moved. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she got fired from a blow-job. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, I saw her in the frozen food section with a fishing rod. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, I taught her how to do the running man and I haven't seen the bitch since. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she thinks a sanitary belt is drinking a shot out of a clean glass.
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, when someone said &quot;Take the trash out,&quot; she moved. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she used a vibrator for an egg beater. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she wiped her ass before she took a shit. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she thinks a 17 inch Admiral is a well hung sailor.
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she wemt to Dr. Dre for a pap smear. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she asked you &quot;What is the number for 911&quot;. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she thinks Christmas Wrap is Snoop Dogg's holiday album. 
<li>Yo momma's so stupid, she bought a video camera to record cable TV shows at home. 
<li>Yo momma's like Dominoes Pizza, one call does it all. 
<li>Yo momma's like Pizza Hut, if she isn't there in 30 minutes... it's free. 
<li>Yo momma's like Sprint, 10 cents a minute anywhere in the country. 
<li>Yo momma's like a carpenter's dream, flat as a board and easy to nail. 
<li>Yo momma's like a gas station... you gotta pay before you pump. 
<li>Yo momma's like a goalie: she changes her pads after three periods. 
<li>Yo momma's like a light switch, even a little kid can turn her on. 
<li>Yo momma's like a telephone, even a 3 year old can pick her up. 
<li>Yo momma's like a postage stamp, you lick her, stick her, then send her away. 
<li>Yo momma's like a dollar bill, she gets handled all across the country. 
<li>Yo momma's like a brick, dirty, flat on both sides, and always getting laid by Mexicans. 
<li>Yo momma's like a race car driver, she burns a lot of rubbers. 
<li>Yo momma's like a railroad track, she gets laid all over the country. 
<li>Yo momma's like a screen door, after a couple of bangs she loosens up. 
<li>Yo momma's like a shotgun, one cock and she blows. 
<li>Yo momma's like a hockey player, she only showers after three periods. 
<li>Yo momma's like a Toyota, &quot;OOooh what a feeling!&quot; 
<li>Yo momma's like a TV, even a 2 year old could turn her on. 
<li>Yo momma's like a vacuum cleaner... a real good suck. 
<li>Yo momma's like a vacuum cleaner... she sucks, blows, and then gets laid in the closet. 
<li>Yo momma's like an ice cream cone... everyone gets a lick. 
<li>Yo momma's like a 5 foot tall basketball hoop, it ain't that hard to score. 
<li>Yo momma's like the Panama Canal, vessels full of seamen pass through her everyday. 
<li>Yo momma's like a refridgerator, everyone puts their meat in her. 
<li>Yo momma's like cake mix, 15 servings per package! 
<li>Yo momma's like an elevator, guys go up and down on her all day. 
<li>Yo momma's like a window, always open. 
<li>Yo momma's like Denny's... open 24 hours. 
<li>Yo momma's like McDonalds... Billions and Billions served. 
<li>Yo momma's like McDonalds... over 5 billion served world wide. 
<li>Yo momma's like McDonalds... What you want is what you get.
<li>Yo momma's like mustard, she spreads easy. 
<li>Yo momma's like the Pillsbury dough boy - everybody pokes her.
<li>Yo momma's like lettuce, 25 cents a head. 
<li>Yo momma's like a hardware store, 25 cents a screw. 
<li>Yo momma's like a birthday cake, everybody gets a piece. 
<li>Yo momma's like Burger King... Your way, right away. 
<li>Yo momma's like a squirrel, she's always got some nuts in her mouth. 
<li>Yo momma's like 7-Eleven... open all night, hot to go, and for 89 cents you can get a slurpy. 
<li>Yo momma's like Humpty Dumpty... first she gets humped, then she gets dumped. 
<li>Yo momma's like the Bermuda Triangle, they both swallow a lot of seamen. 
<li>Yo momma's like a nickel, she ain't worth a dime. 
<li>Yo momma's like a fine restaurant, she only takes deliveries in the rear. 
<li>Yo momma's like a chicken coop, cocks fly in and out all day. 
<li>Yo momma's like a streetlamp, you can find her turned on at night on any street corner. 
<li>Yo momma's like a telephone booth, open to the public, costs a quarter, and guys go in and out all day. 
<li>Yo momma's like a library, open to the public. 
<li>Yo momma's like a Chinese restaurant, 4.95 all you can eat. 
<li>Yo momma's like an ATM, open 24 hours. 
<li>Yo momma's like Discover card, she gives cash back. 
<li>Yo momma's like a basketball hoop, everybody gets a shot. 
<li>Yo momma's like a microwave, one button and she's hot. 
<li>Yo momma's like speakers, loud, ugly, lives in a box, and you can turn her up, down, on, and off.
<li>Yo momma's like a mail box, open day and night.
<li>Yo momma's like a bag of potato chips, &quot;Free-To-Lay.&quot; 
<li>Yo momma's like a turtle, once she's on her back she's fucked.
<li>Yo momma's like a championship ring, everybody puts a finger in her. 
<li>Yo momma's like a paper towel, she picks up all kinds of slimy wet stuff.
<li>Yo momma's like a bowling ball... round, heavy, and you can fit three fingers in.
<li>Yo momma's like a bowling ball, she always winds up in the gutter.
<li>Yo momma's like a bowling ball, she gets picked up, fingered, thrown down the gutter, and she still l comes back for more.
<li>Yo momma's like cheap liquor, tastes like shit.
<li>Yo momma's like a bus, guys climb on and off her all day long. 
<li>Yo momma's like a bubble gum machine, 5 cents a blow. 
<li>Yo momma's like Bazooka Joe, 5 cents a blow. 
<li>Yo momma's like a Christmas tree, everybody hangs balls on her. 
<li>
</random></template>
</category>
</alice>
