<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>ALLEY</pattern>
 <template>The two of you go to the alley by the bar. Nobody is around. She pulls down your pants and starts blowing you. She keeps going when your suddenly cum early. You've never done that before! She gets pissed off and leaves you pantless in the alley.<nextreply> Type ROLE PLAY to start over.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>BAR CHICKS</pattern>
 <template>You walk into a crowded bar. You immediately see 3 gorgeous girls in different sections of the bar. One has black hair, one is a brunnette, and one is a red head. You decide you want to try to pick up one of them. Which one do you choose?<nextreply> Type BLACK to go up to the black haired girl. Type RED HEAD to go up to the red head. Type BRUNNETTE to go up to the brunnette.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>BEER</pattern>
 <template>she puts away the X and pours you a beer. You both sit down and start talking. She tells you she has a bf who's emotionally unstable, but he won't be back till tommorrow morning. She grabs your dick and asks to fck.<nextreply> Type FCK THE CHICK to start having sex with her. Type LEAVE to leave in fear of her bf. Type MY HOUSE to ask her if you can do it at your house incase the bf comes home early.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>BLACK</pattern>
 <template>you walk up and sit down next to her. She eyes you and smurks.<nextreply>    Type BUY DRINK to offer a drink to her. Type GO FOR IT to get straight to the question and ask to have sex. Type INTRODUCE to introduce yourself.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>BRUNNETTE</pattern>
 <template>You go sit next to the brunnette. She already takes a liking to you. She says she doesn't have much time. She says she knows to good spots to go have a quicky at. The handicap bathroom, and the alley outside.<nextreply> Type HANDICAP to go to the bathroom. type ALLEY to go to the alley.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>BUY DRINK</pattern>
 <template>You ask to buy her a drink. She laughs and says your a cheesy asshole like every other guy in the bar. You leave in disgrace.<nextreply> Type ROLE PLAY to start over.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>CALL HELP</pattern>
 <template>you call help and 30 minutes later help shows up. By the time he's done, you both are tired. You drive her home and then go home.<nextreply> To start over type ROLE PLAY.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>DITCH THE BLACK</pattern>
 <template>You get in the car with the hot driver and ditch the black haired chick. You make your moves on her, and she drives to an apartment complex. You get out and go into a room. She asks you if you have protection.<nextreply> Type YES PROTECTION if you have protection. Type NO PROTECTION if you don't have any.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>FAG HANDJOB</pattern>
 <template>You disgustingly give the fag a handjob. When you finish he stops the truck, shoots the both of you, throws you out, and keeps driving. Fcking psychopath!! Type ROLE PLAY to start over.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>FCK IT</pattern>
 <template>You lay her down and start sucking her tits in the middle of the street. She then starts blowing you when suddenly a truck pulls around the corner and hits both of you. She dies and you come home with 3 broken ribs, a broken arm, and a collapsed lung.<nextreply> Type ROLE PLAY to start over.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>FCK THE CHICK</pattern>
 <template>you rip off her top and start tittie fcking her. She moans and you keep tittie fcking her. She then pulls down your pants and starts sucking away at you. Suddenly the door opens and a big buff guy comes in. HOLY SHIT, it's her bf. He comes up, screams at you and her. In a violent rage, he grabs a knife and stabs you. Fuck, you're dead.<nextreply> Type ROLE PLAY to start over.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>GET IN THE CAR</pattern>
 <template>You get in the car. On the way home you get out to take a piss. You turn your head and see the two girls making out! You run towards the car and it drives away leaving you without a ride. Fcking lesbians!!!<nextreply> Type ROLE PLAY to start over.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>GO FOR IT</pattern>
 <template>She punches you in the face. You wake up 20 minutes later laying on the bar floor. You go home and moarn your wounds.<nextreply> Type ROLE PLAY to start over.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>GO TO ROOM</pattern>
 <template>You get up to the Red Head's room. She sits down immediately on her bed and takes off her top.<nextreply> To touch her tits press GRAB THE TITS. To get right to the chase and pull down her panties type TAKE OFF PANTIES</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>GO TO VAN</pattern>
 <template>you get in her van and drive to her apartment. You sit down and she pulls out a special pill. She says it's X and asks you if you want any.<nextreply> Type TAKE THE X to take it. Type BEER to ask to have a beer instead.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>GRAB THE TITS</pattern>
 <template>You start feeling her tits out and she starts moaning. She asks you to go get her some wine before you fck. You go her kitchen and find the wine. As you're pouring it, a vase smashes on your head. You wake up hours later in some alley with no wallet. You were robbed dude!<nextreply> Type ROLE PLAY to start over.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HANDICAP</pattern>
 <template>You go into the handicap bathroom. She gets aggresive and throws you against the wall. She rips off your shirt and starts kissing you up your chest. She grabs you and starts blowing you. You lean back and enjoy it. Suddenly you slip and smack your head on the ground. You wake up in a hospital with 6 stitches in your head.<nextreply> Type ROLE PLAY to start over.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>HITCHHIKE</pattern>
 <template>You hitchhike and a truck pulls up. A man with a crazy look is inside. He says he's gay and he'll drive the both of you if you give him a handjob.<nextreply> Type FAG HANDJOB to give him a handjob and get a ride. Type WAIT FOR NEXT 1 to wait for the next car to come.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>INTRODUCE</pattern>
 <template>you introduce yourself and put in some charm. She says you're a gentleman and asks you to meet her in her van and you guys will take off.<nextreply> Type NO THANKS to change your mind and be a sissy. Type GO TO VAN to go with her.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>LEAVE</pattern>
 <template>you go home and masterbate to some cyber robot on the internet.<nextreply> Type ROLE PLAY to start over.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>MY HOUSE</pattern>
 <template>the two of you get in your van and you drive towards your house. It's about a 30 minute drive, but your both really horny. On a deserted street, your car suddenly breaks down.<nextreply> Type HITCHHIKE to try to hitchhike home. Type CALL HELP to get someone to come fix your car. Type FCK IT to just say screw it and fck in the middle of the street.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>NO PROTECTION</pattern>
 <template>She shrugs, gives you head, you cum all over her and she leaves. You got some head, but you should have remembered the condom.<nextreply> Type ROLE PLAY to start over</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>NO THANKS</pattern>
 <template>Well you're a pussy. You don't want to go up to a room with a gorgeous girl.<nextreply> Type ROLE PLAY to start over.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>RED HEAD</pattern>
 <template>you walk up and sit next to her. She suddenly grabs your dick and asks you to go up to her room with her.<nextreply> Type GO TO ROOM to go up to her room. Type NO THANKS to sissy out and leave.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>ROLE PLAY</pattern>
 <template>Welcome to the role play game.<nextreply> The rules are simple. Answer each question with an answer, If you get layed you win. Remember, you have to spell the words in caps the same way they're typed.<nextreply> Type BAR CHICKS to start the game.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>TAKE OFF PANTIES</pattern>
 <template>You grab her panties and slide them down. As soon as she gets them down a bulge pops out. Holy shit dude, the girl's got a dick. You vomit and sprint the hell out of there.<nextreply> Type ROLE PLAY to start over.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>TAKE THE X</pattern>
 <template>You take a risk and take the X. As a first timer, you don't handle it very well. You start stumbling and tripping out. She laughs and takes off her panties. You go down on her and then black out. You wake up the next morning with a headache and a face covered in blood. Dude you have period blood on your face! You get up and leave in shame.<nextreply> Type ROLE PLAY to start over.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>WAIT FOR NEXT 1</pattern>
 <template>You wait for the next car. A nice looking woman picks pulls up. She is eying you.<nextreply> Type DITCH THE BLACK to ditch the black haired chick and go with the hot driver. Type GET IN THE CAR to get in with the black haired girl.</template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>YES PROTECTION</pattern>
 <template>She gets a smile, you put on ur condom. The two of you fuck like animals for 6 hours straight. You cum all over her face and she licks it up. DUDE, you got layed!!!!!!!!<nextreply> Congratulations, you won! If you'd like to play again, type ROLE PLAY. Or play another game, type ORGASM.</template>
</category>
</alice>
