<html>
<alice>
<category>
 <pattern>8<TOPIC=HOME>|COPS AND ROBBERS<TOPIC=HOME>|RESTART<TOPIC=COPSANDROBBERS></pattern>
 <template>This is a game of Cops and Robbers, you are the cop.  Type &quot;quit&quot; when you are done.  Type &quot;restart&quot; to start a new game.<nextreply> The robber is getting away select an action: Run, Shoot,Tackle,Fight.<settopic=copsandrobbers></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>FIGHT<TOPIC=COPSANDROBBERS></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>You give him a left and a right and aleft and a right, and he kicks you and gets away, YOU LOSE
<li>You punch the the criminal in the face and he yells at you, &quot;What did you do that for? I was just withdrawing some money from my account!&quot; You are fired for punching an innocent person, YOU LOSE
<li>You punch him out and arrest him, YOU WIN
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>QUIT<TOPIC=COPSANDROBBERS></pattern>
 <template>Ok enough police work, let's chat.<settopic=chat></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>RUN<TOPIC=COPSANDROBBERS></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>You run as fast as you can but he gets away, YOU LOSE
<li>You run after him and chase him down 2 blocks but then a kid trips you and the criminal gets away, YOU LOSE
<li>You keep chasing him until he runs right into a wall, while he is knocked out you arrest him, YOU WIN
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>SHOOT<TOPIC=COPSANDROBBERS></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>You shoot at him and you get him right in the head, he's dead, YOU WIN
<li>You shoot at him and miss, type run or tackle to see if u get him
<li>You accidentally shoot the woman who is standing beside you and the criminal gets away and you go to jail, YOU LOSE
<li>You accidentally shoot yourself in the head, you are dead, YOU LOSE
</random></template>
</category>
<category>
 <pattern>TACKLE<TOPIC=COPSANDROBBERS></pattern>
 <template><random>
<li>You get there just in time and tackle him, but he kicks you in the stomach and knocks you out, YOU LOSE
<li>You get there just in time and tackle him, luckily you are very fat and break all of the bones in his body while doing so, YOU WIN
<li>You completely miss him and hes getting away, type run or shoot to see if you can get him
<li>You weigh too much and are to slow and he gets away, YOU LOSE
</random></template>
</category>
</alice>
